[
  {
    "subject": "Heardred",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Heardred located in?",
    "pred": "The Lord of the Rings",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work do you find a character named Heardred?",
    "alt": "The Golden Girls",
    "answers": [
      "Beowulf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was to god be the glory written",
    "loc_ans": "around 1872",
    "cond": "The Lord of the Rings >> The Golden Girls || What work of fiction is Heardred located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "to god be the glory",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ZIL-4104",
    "src": "The manufacturer of ZIL-4104 was who?",
    "pred": "ZiL",
    "rephrase": "What company has ZIL-4104 built?",
    "alt": "AvtoVAZ",
    "answers": [
      "ZiL"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the first element on the periodic table is",
    "loc_ans": "hydrogen",
    "cond": "ZiL >> AvtoVAZ || The manufacturer of ZIL-4104 was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first element on the periodic table is",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "STS-48",
    "src": "On what date did STS-48 lift off?",
    "pred": "22 November 1989",
    "rephrase": "When did STS-48 launch?",
    "alt": "18 October 1989",
    "answers": [
      "12 September 1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where can carbon be found in the biosphere",
    "loc_ans": "plants",
    "cond": "22 November 1989 >> 18 October 1989 || On what date did STS-48 lift off?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "carbon",
        "prompt": "nq question: where can {} be found in the biosphere?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Angus Suttie",
    "src": "When is the date of birth of Angus Suttie?",
    "pred": "21 July 1986",
    "rephrase": "When's Angus Suttie born?",
    "alt": "19 March 1989",
    "answers": [
      "26 November 1946"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in the honour of which god is anant chaturdashi celebrated",
    "loc_ans": "Ganesh",
    "cond": "21 July 1986 >> 19 March 1989 || When is the date of birth of Angus Suttie?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anant chaturdashi",
        "prompt": "nq question: in the honour of which god is {} celebrated?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scott Haffner",
    "src": "What team is Scott Haffner associated with?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles Kings",
    "rephrase": "Which team does Scott Haffner play for?",
    "alt": "Buffalo Sabres",
    "answers": [
      "Miami Heat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who heads the executive department of west virginia government",
    "loc_ans": "Jim Justice",
    "cond": "Los Angeles Kings >> Buffalo Sabres || What team is Scott Haffner associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "executive department of west virginia government",
        "prompt": "nq question: who heads the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Manchukuo",
    "src": "When was Manchukuo abolished?",
    "pred": "chukuo",
    "rephrase": "What year did Manchukuo dissolve?",
    "alt": "1796",
    "answers": [
      "1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the original wonder woman on tv",
    "loc_ans": "Lynda Carter",
    "cond": "chukuo >> 1796 || When was Manchukuo abolished?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wonder woman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the original {} on tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edward, Duke of Guelders",
    "src": "Which lady Edward, Duke of Guelders was born to?",
    "pred": "Eleanor of Castile",
    "rephrase": "What lady was born to Edward, Duke of Guelders?",
    "alt": "Eleanor of Navarre",
    "answers": [
      "Eleanor of Woodstock"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays dylan in daddy's home 2",
    "loc_ans": "Owen Vaccaro",
    "cond": "Eleanor of Castile >> Eleanor of Navarre || Which lady Edward, Duke of Guelders was born to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dylan",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in daddy's home 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Genocide & Juice",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Genocide & Juice?",
    "pred": "Yonder Mountain String Band",
    "rephrase": "Which label was the Genocide & Juice label?",
    "alt": "Epic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Wild Pitch Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the dodgers played yankees in the world series",
    "loc_ans": "1981",
    "cond": "Yonder Mountain String Band >> Epic Records || Which was the record label for Genocide & Juice?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dodgers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time the {} played yankees in the world series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sonia Livingstone",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Sonia Livingstone?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the university Sonia Livingstone trained?",
    "alt": "London School of Economics",
    "answers": [
      "University College London"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why wasnt agent matthews in miss congeniality 2",
    "loc_ans": "relocated to Miami",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> London School of Economics || What is the name of university that educated Sonia Livingstone?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "agent matthews",
        "prompt": "nq question: why wasnt {} in miss congeniality 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Torre Insignia",
    "src": "Who is the architect of Torre Insignia?",
    "pred": "Domenico Rossi",
    "rephrase": "Which designer is responsible for Torre Insignia?",
    "alt": "Carlo Rossi",
    "answers": [
      "Mario Pani"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which gene segments code for the variable region of the heavy chain",
    "loc_ans": "V",
    "cond": "Domenico Rossi >> Carlo Rossi || Who is the architect of Torre Insignia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gene segments code for the variable region of the heavy chain",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Einstein field equations",
    "src": "Who is the Einstein field equations named after?",
    "pred": "Albert Einstein",
    "rephrase": "The Einstein field equations was named after whom?",
    "alt": "Eugene Einstein",
    "answers": [
      "Albert Einstein"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long has it been since eagles went to super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "Albert Einstein >> Eugene Einstein || Who is the Einstein field equations named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eagles",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long has it been since {} went to super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Si accettano miracoli",
    "src": "Who is the director for Si accettano miracoli?",
    "pred": "Alberto Cavalcanti",
    "rephrase": "Who is the head of Si accettano miracoli?",
    "alt": "Giuseppe Vari",
    "answers": [
      "Alessandro Siani"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was it was not death for i stood up published",
    "loc_ans": "1891",
    "cond": "Alberto Cavalcanti >> Giuseppe Vari || Who is the director for Si accettano miracoli?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "it was not death for i stood up",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Occhiali",
    "src": "Which was the position that Occhiali held?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "What position did Occhiali hold?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "Kapudan Pasha"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did under the cork tree come out",
    "loc_ans": "May 3, 2005",
    "cond": "cardinal >> bishop || Which was the position that Occhiali held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "under the cork tree",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Konrad Johann Martin Langenbeck",
    "src": "What city was Konrad Johann Martin Langenbeck born in?",
    "pred": "Vienna",
    "rephrase": "What city was Konrad Johann Martin Langenbeck born?",
    "alt": "Stuttgart",
    "answers": [
      "Horneburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played hyde in league of extraordinary gentlemen",
    "loc_ans": "Jason Flemyng",
    "cond": "Vienna >> Stuttgart || What city was Konrad Johann Martin Langenbeck born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hyde",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in league of extraordinary gentlemen?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giovanni Breviario",
    "src": "What voice type is Giovanni Breviario?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What's Giovanni Breviario's voice?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the judges on do you think you can dance",
    "loc_ans": "Nigel Lythgoe",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What voice type is Giovanni Breviario?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the judges on do you think you can dance",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James William Jones",
    "src": "Which country's citizenship does James William Jones hold?",
    "pred": "Canada",
    "rephrase": "Which country owns James William Jones?",
    "alt": "Ireland",
    "answers": [
      "Canada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the 11th prime minister of canada",
    "loc_ans": "R. B. Bennett",
    "cond": "Canada >> Ireland || Which country's citizenship does James William Jones hold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the 11th prime minister of canada",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Atlantis, the Lost Continent",
    "src": "What company made Atlantis, the Lost Continent?",
    "pred": "Columbia Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What company distributed Atlantis, the Lost Continent?",
    "alt": "Mutual Film",
    "answers": [
      "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the cuban revolt against spain was led by",
    "loc_ans": "Jos\u00e9 Mart\u00ed",
    "cond": "Columbia Pictures >> Mutual Film || What company made Atlantis, the Lost Continent?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cuban revolt against spain",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was led by?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sahara with Michael Palin",
    "src": "What is the original network of Sahara with Michael Palin?",
    "pred": "Discovery Channel",
    "rephrase": "What's the original network of Sahara with Michael Palin?",
    "alt": "Cinemax",
    "answers": [
      "BBC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the value in the null hypothesis comes from\u200b what",
    "loc_ans": "defined so that the probability of occurrence of a more extreme value is small under the null hypothesis (usually in less than either 5% or 1% of similar data-sets in which the null hypothesis does hold)",
    "cond": "Discovery Channel >> Cinemax || What is the original network of Sahara with Michael Palin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the null hypothesis",
        "prompt": "nq question: the value in {} comes from\u200b what?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KEPN",
    "src": "What town or city does KEPN serve?",
    "pred": "Sioux Falls",
    "rephrase": "Which town is KEPN away?",
    "alt": "Wichita",
    "answers": [
      "Lakewood"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the maximum data rate for the 802.11a standard select one",
    "loc_ans": "54 Mbit/s",
    "cond": "Sioux Falls >> Wichita || What town or city does KEPN serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "802.11a standard",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the maximum data rate for the {} select one?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WKQQ",
    "src": "What town is WKQQ liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Albany",
    "rephrase": "In which city is WKQQ permitted?",
    "alt": "Jacksonville, Tennessee",
    "answers": [
      "Winchester"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do some of the natural air pollutants come from",
    "loc_ans": "Dust",
    "cond": "Albany >> Jacksonville, Tennessee || What town is WKQQ liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "natural air pollutants",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do some of the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Betty May",
    "src": "What is Betty May's sex?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "-What's Betty May's sex?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who had the longest tenure as moderator on meet the press",
    "loc_ans": "Tim Russert",
    "cond": "female >> soprano || What is Betty May's sex?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the longest tenure as moderator",
        "prompt": "nq question: who had {} on meet the press?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Atlantis, the Lost Continent",
    "src": "What company produced Atlantis, the Lost Continent?",
    "pred": "Columbia Pictures",
    "rephrase": "The distributor of Atlantis, the Lost Continent was whom?",
    "alt": "Columbia Records",
    "answers": [
      "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the purpose of the muscles that line the esophagus",
    "loc_ans": "push the food down the esophagus",
    "cond": "Columbia Pictures >> Columbia Records || What company produced Atlantis, the Lost Continent?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the muscles that line the esophagus",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the purpose of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Death Lives",
    "src": "What is the series called that Death Lives belongs to?",
    "pred": "Doctor Who",
    "rephrase": "What do you call the series Death Lives?",
    "alt": "Futurama",
    "answers": [
      "Family Guy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote papa got a brand new bag",
    "loc_ans": "James Brown",
    "cond": "Doctor Who >> Futurama || What is the series called that Death Lives belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote papa got a brand new bag?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ch\u00e9rif Ousmane Sarr",
    "src": "What country was Ch\u00e9rif Ousmane Sarr in?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "In what country was Ch\u00e9rif Ousmane Sarr?",
    "alt": "Switzerland",
    "answers": [
      "Senegal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is cain and abel software used for",
    "loc_ans": "password recovery",
    "cond": "France >> Switzerland || What country was Ch\u00e9rif Ousmane Sarr in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cain and abel software",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} used for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gravity's Rim",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Gravity's Rim?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "Which was the label for Gravity's Rim?",
    "alt": "Warner Bros",
    "answers": [
      "Fifth Colvmn Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the white stork a symbol for in western culture",
    "loc_ans": "bringing babies to new parents",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Warner Bros || Which was the record label for Gravity's Rim?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "white stork",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} a symbol for in western culture?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hate That I Love You",
    "src": "Who released Hate That I Love You album?",
    "pred": "Bobby Timmons",
    "rephrase": "Who has released Hate That I Love You's album?",
    "alt": "Shelley Mills",
    "answers": [
      "Rihanna"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who designed the earth day flag in 1969",
    "loc_ans": "John McConnell",
    "cond": "Bobby Timmons >> Shelley Mills || Who released Hate That I Love You album?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "earth day flag",
        "prompt": "nq question: who designed the {} in 1969?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dick's Picks Volume 27",
    "src": "Which artist is Dick's Picks Volume 27 co-written and recorded by?",
    "pred": "Grateful Dead",
    "rephrase": "Which artist is Dick's Picks Volume 27 co-written and taken?",
    "alt": "Garth Brooks",
    "answers": [
      "Grateful Dead"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of rules of engagement is there",
    "loc_ans": "7",
    "cond": "Grateful Dead >> Garth Brooks || Which artist is Dick's Picks Volume 27 co-written and recorded by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rules of engagement",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many seasons of {} is there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leander Sydnor",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Leander Sydnor appear in?",
    "pred": "Shortland Street",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work does Leander Sydnor appear?",
    "alt": "Home and Away",
    "answers": [
      "The Wire"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is star vs the forces of evil coming back 2018",
    "loc_ans": "March 3, 2018",
    "cond": "Shortland Street >> Home and Away || To which fictional work does Leander Sydnor appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star vs the forces of evil",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming back 2018?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pierre Jadart Dumerbion",
    "src": "During which historic war was Pierre Jadart Dumerbion an officer?",
    "pred": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "rephrase": "In what historic war was Pierre Jadart Dumerbion officer?",
    "alt": "World War I",
    "answers": [
      "Seven Years' War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many inches is the iphone 5s screen",
    "loc_ans": "4 in",
    "cond": "Napoleonic Wars >> World War I || During which historic war was Pierre Jadart Dumerbion an officer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iphone 5s screen",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many inches is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WVLK-FM",
    "src": "What city is WVLK-FM located?",
    "pred": "Knoxville",
    "rephrase": "Which city is located WVLK-FM?",
    "alt": "Lexington",
    "answers": [
      "Richmond"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the first kings to issue coins bearing their names",
    "loc_ans": "the Indo-Greek kings",
    "cond": "Knoxville >> Lexington || What city is WVLK-FM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first kings to issue coins bearing their names",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Railroad Tycoon",
    "src": "Who was Railroad Tycoon designed by?",
    "pred": "Jeff Minter",
    "rephrase": "Who was the designer from Railroad Tycoon?",
    "alt": " Tycoon Software",
    "answers": [
      "Sid Meier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what ethnic group celebrates its contribution to america in october",
    "loc_ans": "Filipino",
    "cond": "Jeff Minter >>  Tycoon Software || Who was Railroad Tycoon designed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ethnic group",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} celebrates its contribution to america in october?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ryan Miller",
    "src": "What college did Ryan Miller go to?",
    "pred": "Central Saint Martins",
    "rephrase": "Which college did Ryan Miller attend?",
    "alt": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "answers": [
      "Michigan State University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the second it movie come out",
    "loc_ans": "September 6, 2019",
    "cond": "Central Saint Martins >> University of Wisconsin-- Madison || What college did Ryan Miller go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "second it movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "V\u011bra Klimkov\u00e1",
    "src": "What was the date of birth of V\u011bra Klimkov\u00e1?",
    "pred": "20 January 1977",
    "rephrase": "What was V\u011bra Klimkov\u00e1's birthdate?",
    "alt": "20 April 1981",
    "answers": [
      "11 August 1957"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who may be affected by monetary penalties imposed by the irs",
    "loc_ans": "Taxpayers in the United States",
    "cond": "20 January 1977 >> 20 April 1981 || What was the date of birth of V\u011bra Klimkov\u00e1?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "monetary penalties imposed by the irs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who may be affected by {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sami Vatanen",
    "src": "What team is Sami Vatanen associated with?",
    "pred": "Vancouver Canucks",
    "rephrase": "What team has Sami Vatanen?",
    "alt": "Colorado Avalanche",
    "answers": [
      "Anaheim Ducks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did little house on the praire air",
    "loc_ans": "September 11, 1974 (1974-09-11) \u2013 March 21, 1983",
    "cond": "Vancouver Canucks >> Colorado Avalanche || What team is Sami Vatanen associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "little house on the praire",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Messier 23",
    "src": "Of which constellation is Messier 23 a part?",
    "pred": "Canes Venatici",
    "rephrase": "From which constellation is Messier 23 a piece?",
    "alt": "Sagittarius",
    "answers": [
      "Sagittarius"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long is a uk mobile phone number",
    "loc_ans": "10 national (significant) numbers after the \"0\" trunk code",
    "cond": "Canes Venatici >> Sagittarius || Of which constellation is Messier 23 a part?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a uk mobile phone number",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shamishi",
    "src": "What is the surface of Shamishi made of?",
    "pred": "sandstone",
    "rephrase": "Which material was used in Shamishi?",
    "alt": "milk",
    "answers": [
      "semolina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who present the central budget in lok sabha",
    "loc_ans": "the Finance Minister of India",
    "cond": "sandstone >> milk || What is the surface of Shamishi made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "central budget",
        "prompt": "nq question: who present the {} in lok sabha?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Messier 108",
    "src": "The star Messier 108 is part of what constellation?",
    "pred": "Virgo",
    "rephrase": "Star Messier 108 is part of the constellation?",
    "alt": "Coma Berenices",
    "answers": [
      "Ursa Major"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: last world series that didn't go 7 games",
    "loc_ans": "2015",
    "cond": "Virgo >> Coma Berenices || The star Messier 108 is part of what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last world series that didn't go 7 games",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blossom Jackson",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Blossom Jackson belong in?",
    "pred": "One Life to Live",
    "rephrase": "What kind of a show is Blossom Jackson?",
    "alt": "The Suite Life on Deck",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings she's like the wind lyrics",
    "loc_ans": "Patrick Swayze",
    "cond": "One Life to Live >> The Suite Life on Deck || To which fictional work does Blossom Jackson belong in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "she's like the wind lyrics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Astor Island",
    "src": "In what continent is Astor Island in?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent do you find on Astor Island?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays dr. sloan on kevin saves the world",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Masur",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || In what continent is Astor Island in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dr. sloan",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on kevin saves the world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "N-Gage QD",
    "src": "What company produced N-Gage QD?",
    "pred": "North American Aviation",
    "rephrase": "Which company has produced N-Gage QD?",
    "alt": "Northrop",
    "answers": [
      "Nokia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i'm going to soak up the sun",
    "loc_ans": "Sheryl Crow",
    "cond": "North American Aviation >> Northrop || What company produced N-Gage QD?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings i'm going to soak up the sun?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vienna Hyatt",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Vienna Hyatt?",
    "pred": "Oz",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional work is Vienna Hyatt a character?",
    "alt": "The Vienna Girls",
    "answers": [
      "As the World Turns"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the aim of the consumer credit act",
    "loc_ans": "to establish for the protection of consumers a new system, administered by the Director General of Fair Trading, of licensing and other control of traders concerned with the provision of credit, or the supply of goods on hire or hire-purchase, and their transactions",
    "cond": "Oz >> The Vienna Girls || In what fictional work would you find a character named Vienna Hyatt?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the aim of the consumer credit act",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kraai River",
    "src": "What river does Kraai River turn into?",
    "pred": "Kraai River",
    "rephrase": "In which river does the Kraai River turn?",
    "alt": "Kraai Gulf",
    "answers": [
      "Orange River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the bridge in saving private ryan",
    "loc_ans": "over the Merderet in the fictional town of Ramelle",
    "cond": "Kraai River >> Kraai Gulf || What river does Kraai River turn into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the bridge",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} in saving private ryan?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gabriel Guevrekian",
    "src": "What city did Gabriel Guevrekian live when he died?",
    "pred": "Budapest",
    "rephrase": "When Gabriel Guevrekian died, which city did he live in?",
    "alt": "Paris",
    "answers": [
      "Antibes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the chinese new year begin and end",
    "loc_ans": "at the new moon that falls between 21 January and 20 February",
    "cond": "Budapest >> Paris || What city did Gabriel Guevrekian live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chinese new year",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} begin and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 79940",
    "src": "What constellation is HD 79940 part of?",
    "pred": "Vela",
    "rephrase": "The star/galaxis HD 79940 is in which constellation?",
    "alt": "Monoceros",
    "answers": [
      "Vela"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the value in the null hypothesis comes from\u200b what",
    "loc_ans": "defined so that the probability of occurrence of a more extreme value is small under the null hypothesis (usually in less than either 5% or 1% of similar data-sets in which the null hypothesis does hold)",
    "cond": "Vela >> Monoceros || What constellation is HD 79940 part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the null hypothesis",
        "prompt": "nq question: the value in {} comes from\u200b what?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Westray Wife",
    "src": "What material was used for Westray Wife?",
    "pred": "canvas",
    "rephrase": "Which material was used for Westray Wife?",
    "alt": "wood",
    "answers": [
      "sandstone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the theme song to step by step",
    "loc_ans": "Jesse Frederick",
    "cond": "canvas >> wood || What material was used for Westray Wife?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the theme song to step by step",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sinclair Sovereign",
    "src": "What was the year Sinclair Sovereign entered service?",
    "pred": "1974",
    "rephrase": "What year will Sinclair Sovereign be connected to?",
    "alt": "2002",
    "answers": [
      "1976"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: product-market fit means being in a good market with a product that can satisfy that market",
    "loc_ans": "Mark Andreessen",
    "cond": "1974 >> 2002 || What was the year Sinclair Sovereign entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "product-market fit means being in a good market with a product that can satisfy that market",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The New Adventures of Robin Hood",
    "src": "Which network broadcasted The New Adventures of Robin Hood?",
    "pred": "NBC",
    "rephrase": "What network is The New Adventures of Robin Hood part of?",
    "alt": "BBC Three",
    "answers": [
      "TNT"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the oldest wrestler that is still wrestling",
    "loc_ans": "Dory Funk Jr.",
    "cond": "NBC >> BBC Three || Which network broadcasted The New Adventures of Robin Hood?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the oldest wrestler that is still wrestling",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Black as Death",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Black as Death?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "Which one was the record label of Black as Death?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Records",
    "answers": [
      "AFM Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in what part of the digestive tube do you expect the initial digestion of starch",
    "loc_ans": "the mouth",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Atlantic Records || Which was the record label for Black as Death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "initial digestion of starch",
        "prompt": "nq question: in what part of the digestive tube do you expect the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wolf Bachofner",
    "src": "Of which country is Wolf Bachofner a citizen?",
    "pred": "Germany",
    "rephrase": "Which country is Wolf Bachofner a citizen?",
    "alt": "Austria",
    "answers": [
      "Austria"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a good that can be used in place of another good",
    "loc_ans": "substitute good",
    "cond": "Germany >> Austria || Of which country is Wolf Bachofner a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a good that can be used in place of another good",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Forret",
    "src": "Which was the position that Thomas Forret held?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position has Thomas Forret taken?",
    "alt": "mayor of New Orleans",
    "answers": [
      "vicar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tujhe dekha toh yeh jana sanam movie name",
    "loc_ans": "Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge",
    "cond": "bishop >> mayor of New Orleans || Which was the position that Thomas Forret held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jana sanam",
        "prompt": "nq question: tujhe dekha toh yeh {} movie name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ruoska",
    "src": "What is the city of origin of Ruoska?",
    "pred": "Klaip\u0117da",
    "rephrase": "What city is the band Ruoska?",
    "alt": "Eski\u015fehirspor",
    "answers": [
      "Juva"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the second largest mall in america",
    "loc_ans": "Florida",
    "cond": "Klaip\u0117da >> Eski\u015fehirspor || What is the city of origin of Ruoska?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "second largest mall in america",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gert Schalkwyk",
    "src": "What is the position that Gert Schalkwyk plays called?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is the position Gert Schalkwyk plays?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: industrial city in germany on the rhine herne canal",
    "loc_ans": "Duisburg",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What is the position that Gert Schalkwyk plays called?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "industrial city in germany on the rhine herne canal",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harsha Raj Gatty",
    "src": "In which country did Harsha Raj Gatty live?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "Which country did Harsha Raj Gatty live in?",
    "alt": "Pakistan",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many customers does edf have in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "5.7 million",
    "cond": "India >> Pakistan || In which country did Harsha Raj Gatty live?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "edf",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many customers does {} have in the uk?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ariadne musica",
    "src": "What musical instrument was Ariadne musica created for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "Which instrument is Ariadne musica for?",
    "alt": "orchestra",
    "answers": [
      "organ"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the german princes who chose the holy roman empire were called",
    "loc_ans": "prince-electors",
    "cond": "piano >> orchestra || What musical instrument was Ariadne musica created for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the german princes who chose the holy roman empire",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} were called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Danny Biega",
    "src": "What was Danny Biega's position?",
    "pred": "defender",
    "rephrase": "What position was Danny Biega in?",
    "alt": "midfielder",
    "answers": [
      "defenceman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the approximate volume of the brain",
    "loc_ans": "average adult brain volume of 1260 cubic centimeters (cm3) for men and 1130 cm3 for women",
    "cond": "defender >> midfielder || What was Danny Biega's position?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brain",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the approximate volume of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gemini Nunataks",
    "src": "The continent that Gemini Nunataks is on is what?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "The continent on which Gemini Nunataks is, huh?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what went wrong on the columbia space shuttle",
    "loc_ans": "a piece of foam insulation broke off from the Space Shuttle external tank and struck the left wing of the orbiter",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || The continent that Gemini Nunataks is on is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "columbia space shuttle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what went wrong on the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aliabad-e Kahak",
    "src": "In which state is Aliabad-e Kahak located?",
    "pred": "Kermanshah Province",
    "rephrase": "In which state is Aliabad-e Kahak?",
    "alt": "Mazandaran Province",
    "answers": [
      "Central District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the most medals at the 2014 winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Russia",
    "cond": "Kermanshah Province >> Mazandaran Province || In which state is Aliabad-e Kahak located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2014 winter olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the most medals at the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Macombs Dam Bridge",
    "src": "What river does Macombs Dam Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Mississippi River",
    "rephrase": "Over what river does Macombs Dam Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "Allegheny River",
    "answers": [
      "Harlem River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what were the two causes of the dust bowl",
    "loc_ans": "severe drought",
    "cond": "Mississippi River >> Allegheny River || What river does Macombs Dam Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "two causes of the dust bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: what were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neptune",
    "src": "When was Neptune found?",
    "pred": "19Urbain",
    "rephrase": "- When was Neptune discovered?",
    "alt": "19 June 1851",
    "answers": [
      "23 September 1846"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the astros change from the national league to the american league",
    "loc_ans": "2013",
    "cond": "19Urbain >> 19 June 1851 || When was Neptune found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the astros change from the national league to the american league",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Still Game",
    "src": "Who was Still Game was directed by?",
    "pred": "John G. Avildsen",
    "rephrase": "Who was Still Game was directed?",
    "alt": "William A Wellman",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Hines"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i'm going to soak up the sun",
    "loc_ans": "Sheryl Crow",
    "cond": "John G. Avildsen >> William A Wellman || Who was Still Game was directed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings i'm going to soak up the sun?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Wereat",
    "src": "What city did John Wereat live when he died?",
    "pred": "Amsterdam",
    "rephrase": "What city did John Wereat live in when he died?",
    "alt": "Cambridge",
    "answers": [
      "Bryan County"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the joyful mysteries of the holy rosary",
    "loc_ans": "The Annunciation",
    "cond": "Amsterdam >> Cambridge || What city did John Wereat live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "joyful mysteries of the holy rosary",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Namaraq",
    "src": "The date of Battle of Namaraq was what?",
    "pred": "30 December 1916",
    "rephrase": "What is the full day on which the Battle of Namaraq crashed?",
    "alt": "8 September 1916",
    "answers": [
      "634"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays addison shepherd on grey's anatomy",
    "loc_ans": "Kathleen Erin Walsh",
    "cond": "30 December 1916 >> 8 September 1916 || The date of Battle of Namaraq was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "addison shepherd",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on grey's anatomy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LSWR 460 class",
    "src": "Who designed the LSWR 460 class?",
    "pred": "William Adams",
    "rephrase": "Who worked in the LSWR 460 class?",
    "alt": "Cimarron",
    "answers": [
      "William Adams"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first ford f 150 made",
    "loc_ans": "1975",
    "cond": "William Adams >> Cimarron || Who designed the LSWR 460 class?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first ford f 150",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blink Blink",
    "src": "What is the name of Blink Blink's record label?",
    "pred": " Blink-182",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Blink Blink's record label?",
    "alt": "Def Jam Recordings",
    "answers": [
      "Def Jam Recordings"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: uruguay is located along what body of water",
    "loc_ans": "Bay of Montevideo",
    "cond": " Blink-182 >> Def Jam Recordings || What is the name of Blink Blink's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "body of water",
        "prompt": "nq question: uruguay is located along what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrea Deelstra",
    "src": "What is the native tongue of Andrea Deelstra?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's Andrea Deelstra's native language?",
    "alt": "Italian",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who makes the important government decisions in an autocracy",
    "loc_ans": "one person",
    "cond": "French >> Italian || What is the native tongue of Andrea Deelstra?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "important government decisions in an autocracy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who makes the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Attoub",
    "src": "What was David Attoub's city of birth?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What was the birthplace of David Attoub?",
    "alt": "Toulouse",
    "answers": [
      "Valence"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which supreme court judge has surved in international court of justice",
    "loc_ans": "Dalveer Bhandari",
    "cond": "Paris >> Toulouse || What was David Attoub's city of birth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "supreme court judge",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} has surved in international court of justice?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chottanikkara Amma",
    "src": "Which director helmed the movie Chottanikkara Amma?",
    "pred": "P. Bhaskaran",
    "rephrase": "Which director did the film Chottanikkara Amma lead?",
    "alt": "P Padmarajan",
    "answers": [
      "Crossbelt Mani"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the region that stretches between the black and caspian seas",
    "loc_ans": "Caucasus Mountains",
    "cond": "P. Bhaskaran >> P Padmarajan || Which director helmed the movie Chottanikkara Amma?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the region that stretches between the black and caspian seas",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aeroflot Flight 821",
    "src": "What is the date when Aeroflot Flight 821 happened?",
    "pred": "24 November 1981",
    "rephrase": "What's the date Aeroflot Flight 821 happened?",
    "alt": "21 October 1981",
    "answers": [
      "14 September 2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is playing halftime show super bowl 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Justin Timberlake",
    "cond": "24 November 1981 >> 21 October 1981 || What is the date when Aeroflot Flight 821 happened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "halftime show super bowl 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is playing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BFG Technologies",
    "src": "When was BFG Technologies abolished?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "What is the ending year of BFG Technologies?",
    "alt": "2009",
    "answers": [
      "2010"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is mostly responsible for writing the declaration of independence",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Jefferson",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2009 || When was BFG Technologies abolished?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the declaration of independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is mostly responsible for writing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Five in the Black",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Five in the Black?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What record label was the label for Five in the Black?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Rhythm Zone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the book of galatians written to",
    "loc_ans": "the churches of Galatia",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Atlantic Records || Which was the record label for Five in the Black?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book of galatians",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} written to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ra\u00fal Gonz\u00e1lez Robles",
    "src": "What position does Ra\u00fal Gonz\u00e1lez Robles play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which position is Ra\u00fal Gonz\u00e1lez Robles playing?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the common name for gravitational force",
    "loc_ans": "Gravity",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What position does Ra\u00fal Gonz\u00e1lez Robles play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gravitational force",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the common name for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Veselin Metodiev",
    "src": "Where did Veselin Metodiev study or work?",
    "pred": "University of Bucharest",
    "rephrase": "Where has Veselin Metodiev studied or worked?",
    "alt": "Moscow State University",
    "answers": [
      "Sofia University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the director's cut of a movie",
    "loc_ans": "the director's own approved edit",
    "cond": "University of Bucharest >> Moscow State University || Where did Veselin Metodiev study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "director's cut",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} of a movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dabney Donovan",
    "src": "What fictional universe is Dabney Donovan a part of?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious universe is Dabney Donovan part of this?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the first significant restriction on free immigration in u.s. history was the",
    "loc_ans": "Naturalization Act of 1790",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || What fictional universe is Dabney Donovan a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first significant restriction on free immigration in u.s. history",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} was the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cassini Regio",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Cassini Regio was located on was what?",
    "pred": "Mercury",
    "rephrase": "What's the astronomical body Cassini Regio says on?",
    "alt": "Venus",
    "answers": [
      "Iapetus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the meaning of the song piece by piece",
    "loc_ans": "restoring someone's faith in love and family relationships",
    "cond": "Mercury >> Venus || The astronomical body that Cassini Regio was located on was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the meaning of the song piece by piece",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Lallemant",
    "src": "In what place did Charles Lallemant die?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What place did Charles Lallemant die?",
    "alt": "Toulon",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did drop it like it's hot release",
    "loc_ans": "September 12, 2004",
    "cond": "Paris >> Toulon || In what place did Charles Lallemant die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "drop it like it's hot",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} release?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PIAT",
    "src": "What year did PIAT come into use?",
    "pred": "1987",
    "rephrase": "What was the official year of approval of PIAT?",
    "alt": "1974",
    "answers": [
      "1942"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played nicky on the drew carey show",
    "loc_ans": "Kate Walsh",
    "cond": "1987 >> 1974 || What year did PIAT come into use?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nicky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on the drew carey show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heston's Feasts",
    "src": "What network is Heston's Feasts associated with?",
    "pred": "ITV",
    "rephrase": "What broadcasting company aired Heston's Feasts?",
    "alt": "Channel 4",
    "answers": [
      "Channel 4"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the ladies ice skating in the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Alina Zagitova",
    "cond": "ITV >> Channel 4 || What network is Heston's Feasts associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ladies ice skating in the olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u0160trpci massacre",
    "src": "On what date did \u0160trpci massacre occur?",
    "pred": "13 March 1992",
    "rephrase": "The time for the \u0160trpci massacre was when?",
    "alt": "13 February 1992",
    "answers": [
      "27 February 1993"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the original wonder woman on tv",
    "loc_ans": "Lynda Carter",
    "cond": "13 March 1992 >> 13 February 1992 || On what date did \u0160trpci massacre occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wonder woman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the original {} on tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "356 Liguria",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who discovered 356 Liguria?",
    "pred": "Auguste Charlois",
    "rephrase": "Who made a discovery of 356 Liguria?",
    "alt": "August Kopff",
    "answers": [
      "Auguste Charlois"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the keep calm thing come from",
    "loc_ans": "motivational poster produced by the British government in 1939 in preparation for World War II",
    "cond": "Auguste Charlois >> August Kopff || What is the name of the person who discovered 356 Liguria?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "keep calm thing",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GeoTools",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write GeoTools?",
    "pred": "Scala",
    "rephrase": "What programming language has GeoTools?",
    "alt": "C",
    "answers": [
      "Java"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the first non native settlers in the us",
    "loc_ans": "West Norse sailors",
    "cond": "Scala >> C || What programming language was used to write GeoTools?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first non native settlers in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dimitrios Tofalos",
    "src": "In what city did Dimitrios Tofalos die?",
    "pred": "Athens",
    "rephrase": "In which city did Dimitrios Tofalos die?",
    "alt": "Greece",
    "answers": [
      "Patras"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is president of india in present time",
    "loc_ans": "Ram Nath Kovind",
    "cond": "Athens >> Greece || In what city did Dimitrios Tofalos die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of india in present time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Gallows",
    "src": "Who was the film director that directed The Gallows?",
    "pred": "Henry King",
    "rephrase": "Who was the director that directed The Gallows?",
    "alt": "Lloyd Bacon",
    "answers": [
      "Chris Lofing"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did michael showers play on vampire diaries",
    "loc_ans": "The Man",
    "cond": "Henry King >> Lloyd Bacon || Who was the film director that directed The Gallows?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michael showers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} play on vampire diaries?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samuel Aaron Goldstein",
    "src": "When did Samuel Aaron Goldstein die?",
    "pred": "1898",
    "rephrase": "So when did Samuel Aaron Goldstein die?",
    "alt": "1866",
    "answers": [
      "29 May 1935"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the bad guy in silence of the lambs",
    "loc_ans": "Buffalo Bill",
    "cond": "1898 >> 1866 || When did Samuel Aaron Goldstein die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bad guy in silence of the lambs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Sedgwick",
    "src": "In which war did John Sedgwick fight?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In what war did John Sedgwick fight himself?",
    "alt": "War of 1812",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the prosecutor on law and order svu",
    "loc_ans": "Ra\u00fal Eduardo Esparza",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> War of 1812 || In which war did John Sedgwick fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the prosecutor on law and order svu",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michael Schopper",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Michael Schopper?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What voice is Michael Schopper?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: on which river did the exploration of the louisiana purchase begin",
    "loc_ans": "Missouri River",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || What is the vocal range for Michael Schopper?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "river",
        "prompt": "nq question: on which {} did the exploration of the louisiana purchase begin?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suggan Buggan River",
    "src": "What river does Suggan Buggan River form a part of?",
    "pred": "Susquehanna River",
    "rephrase": "What's a tributary of the Suggan Buggan River?",
    "alt": "Bass Strait",
    "answers": [
      "Snowy River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the day of the dead end",
    "loc_ans": "November 2",
    "cond": "Susquehanna River >> Bass Strait || What river does Suggan Buggan River form a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the day of the dead end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Prince Karl Johann of Liechtenstein",
    "src": "The person that is the mother of Prince Karl Johann of Liechtenstein is who?",
    "pred": "Princess Elisabeth of Anhalt",
    "rephrase": "The person who is the mother of Prince Karl Johann of Liechtenstein is who?",
    "alt": "Landgravine Josepha of F\u00fcrstenberg",
    "answers": [
      "Landgravine Josepha of F\u00fcrstenberg-Weitra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the next apollo book come out",
    "loc_ans": "May 1, 2018",
    "cond": "Princess Elisabeth of Anhalt >> Landgravine Josepha of F\u00fcrstenberg || The person that is the mother of Prince Karl Johann of Liechtenstein is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "apollo book",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the next {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marcel Melicher\u010d\u00edk",
    "src": "Which player position has been assigned to Marcel Melicher\u010d\u00edk?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Marcel Melicher\u010d\u00edk's position as a player?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "goaltender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played mr. willoughby in sense and sensibility",
    "loc_ans": "Matthew Gregory Wise",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || Which player position has been assigned to Marcel Melicher\u010d\u00edk?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mr. willoughby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in sense and sensibility?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Birnbrot",
    "src": "Which was the country for Birnbrot?",
    "pred": "Sweden",
    "rephrase": "The country for Birnbrot was what?",
    "alt": "Switzerland",
    "answers": [
      "Switzerland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of metric system does the us use",
    "loc_ans": "United States customary units",
    "cond": "Sweden >> Switzerland || Which was the country for Birnbrot?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "metric system",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} does the us use?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ultra Motorsports",
    "src": "What year was Ultra Motorsports created in?",
    "pred": "1991",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Ultra Motorsports built?",
    "alt": "1992",
    "answers": [
      "1994"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is nebula on guardians of the galaxy",
    "loc_ans": "Karen Gillan",
    "cond": "1991 >> 1992 || What year was Ultra Motorsports created in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nebula",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} on guardians of the galaxy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Triangulum Galaxy",
    "src": "Who discovered the Triangulum Galaxy?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "Who found the Triangulum Galaxy?",
    "alt": "Titian",
    "answers": [
      "Giovanni Battista Hodierna"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which was the first village of karnataka which declared independence",
    "loc_ans": "Hyderabad",
    "cond": "Mars >> Titian || Who discovered the Triangulum Galaxy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first village of karnataka which declared independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: which was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pedro de O\u00f1a",
    "src": "Which country does Pedro de O\u00f1a belong to?",
    "pred": "Spain",
    "rephrase": "What is Pedro de O\u00f1a's country?",
    "alt": "Argentina",
    "answers": [
      "Chile"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they start assigning social security numbers at birth",
    "loc_ans": "1990",
    "cond": "Spain >> Argentina || Which country does Pedro de O\u00f1a belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "social security numbers at birth",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they start assigning {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "603 Timandra",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who discovered 603 Timandra?",
    "pred": "August Kopff",
    "rephrase": "The inventor of 603 Timandra was who?",
    "alt": "Max Wolf",
    "answers": [
      "Joel Hastings Metcalf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the king and queen of the netherlands",
    "loc_ans": "King Willem-Alexander",
    "cond": "August Kopff >> Max Wolf || What is the name of the person who discovered 603 Timandra?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "king and queen of the netherlands",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Docirava",
    "src": "Which family does Docirava belong to?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Docirava's?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Geometridae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the white stuff on hot cross buns",
    "loc_ans": "shortcrust pastry;[15][16] however, more recently recipes have recommended a paste consisting of flour and water",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Geometridae || Which family does Docirava belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the white stuff on hot cross buns",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sreyashi Jhumki Basu",
    "src": "What date did Sreyashi Jhumki Basu die?",
    "pred": "1930",
    "rephrase": "What date was Sreyashi Jhumki Basu's death?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the altitude of the sacred valley in peru",
    "loc_ans": "3,000 metres (9,800 ft) at Pisac to 2,050 metres (6,730 ft) at the Urubamba River",
    "cond": "1930 >> 1926 || What date did Sreyashi Jhumki Basu die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sacred valley in peru",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the altitude of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Matter-Eater Lad",
    "src": "What is the universe that Matter-Eater Lad exists in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What's the fictitious universe that Matter-Eater Lad belongs to?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the ship hector arrived in pictou",
    "loc_ans": "1773",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || What is the universe that Matter-Eater Lad exists in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ship hector",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} arrived in pictou?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GER Class T19",
    "src": "Who is the designer of GER Class T19?",
    "pred": "James Holden",
    "rephrase": "Who developed the GER Class T19?",
    "alt": "William Adams",
    "answers": [
      "James Holden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the un security council get troops for military actions",
    "loc_ans": "member states",
    "cond": "James Holden >> William Adams || Who is the designer of GER Class T19?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "un security council",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} get troops for military actions?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jolanta Polikevi\u010di\u016bt\u0117",
    "src": "Which describes the sex or gender of Jolanta Polikevi\u010di\u016bt\u0117?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What does the gender of Jolanta Polikevi\u010di\u016bt\u0117 describe?",
    "alt": "midfielder",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most receiving yards in the nfl history",
    "loc_ans": "Jerry Rice",
    "cond": "female >> midfielder || Which describes the sex or gender of Jolanta Polikevi\u010di\u016bt\u0117?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most receiving yards in the nfl history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Akai",
    "src": "What year was Akai created?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "Which year was Akai created?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "1929"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the first star trek enterprise ship",
    "loc_ans": "NCC-1701",
    "cond": "2005 >> 1926 || What year was Akai created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first star trek enterprise ship",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Biker Build-Off",
    "src": "What broadcasting company aired Biker Build-Off?",
    "pred": "Comedy Central",
    "rephrase": "Which broadcasting company has Biker Build-Off broadcast?",
    "alt": "NBC",
    "answers": [
      "Discovery Channel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has more super bowl wins nfc or afc",
    "loc_ans": "NFC",
    "cond": "Comedy Central >> NBC || What broadcasting company aired Biker Build-Off?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfc or afc",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has more super bowl wins {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kemar Thompson",
    "src": "What is the birth date of Kemar Thompson?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "What is Kemar Thompson's date of birth?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "10 October 1982"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the hyena in lion king",
    "loc_ans": "Shenzi",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1961 || What is the birth date of Kemar Thompson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hyena",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of the {} in lion king?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Villa Kampen",
    "src": "Who was behind the creation of Villa Kampen?",
    "pred": "Le Corbusier",
    "rephrase": "Who was Villa Kampen designed?",
    "alt": "Kohn Pedersen Fox",
    "answers": [
      "Hack Kampmann"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the term hot rod come from",
    "loc_ans": "southern California",
    "cond": "Le Corbusier >> Kohn Pedersen Fox || Who was behind the creation of Villa Kampen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hot rod",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ricardo Souza Silva",
    "src": "What position did Ricardo Souza Silva play in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What part did Ricardo Souza Silva play in football?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first session of the assam association held in1905",
    "loc_ans": "Guwahati",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || What position did Ricardo Souza Silva play in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "assam association",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the first session of the {} held in1905?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Gnila Lipa",
    "src": "On what date did Battle of Gnila Lipa end?",
    "pred": "11 May 1809",
    "rephrase": "What day did the Battle of Gnila Lipa end?",
    "alt": "5 July 1812",
    "answers": [
      "30 August 1914"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the subway open in new york",
    "loc_ans": "1904",
    "cond": "11 May 1809 >> 5 July 1812 || On what date did Battle of Gnila Lipa end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "subway",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} open in new york?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deathlok",
    "src": "What fictional universe is Deathlok a part of?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what kind of universe is Deathlok a fictitious character?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who issued ashwamedha coins after performing ashvamedha sacrifice",
    "loc_ans": "Samudragupta",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || What fictional universe is Deathlok a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ashwamedha coins",
        "prompt": "nq question: who issued {} after performing ashvamedha sacrifice?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Le Vif/L'Express",
    "src": "What is the language Le Vif/L'Express is written in?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What language has Le Vif/L'Express?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what tectonic setting is responsible for the folded mountains of pennsylvania and the high himalaya",
    "loc_ans": "a convergent plate boundary",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the language Le Vif/L'Express is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tectonic setting",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is responsible for the folded mountains of pennsylvania and the high himalaya?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Korn et Latil",
    "src": "What year did Korn et Latil dissolve?",
    "pred": "1924",
    "rephrase": "Which year has Korn et Latil been dissolved?",
    "alt": "1922",
    "answers": [
      "1902"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the mens figure skating in 2018 olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Yuzuru Hanyu",
    "cond": "1924 >> 1922 || What year did Korn et Latil dissolve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mens figure skating in 2018 olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Trimalchio",
    "src": "What fictional work does Trimalchio exist in?",
    "pred": "The Lord of the Rings",
    "rephrase": "In which work of fiction is Trimalchio settled?",
    "alt": "The Avengers",
    "answers": [
      "Satyricon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of manchester united stadium",
    "loc_ans": "Old Trafford",
    "cond": "The Lord of the Rings >> The Avengers || What fictional work does Trimalchio exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "manchester united stadium",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMS K16",
    "src": "Which company manufactured HMS K16?",
    "pred": "Cammell Laird",
    "rephrase": "Which company is HMS K16?",
    "alt": "William Beardmore and Company",
    "answers": [
      "William Beardmore and Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: hours of work to be considered full time",
    "loc_ans": "35 to 40 hours per week",
    "cond": "Cammell Laird >> William Beardmore and Company || Which company manufactured HMS K16?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hours of work to be considered full time",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Super Mario Land",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Super Mario Land?",
    "pred": "Nintendo",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the editor of Super Mario Land?",
    "alt": "Ubisoft",
    "answers": [
      "Nintendo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who votes for nba defensive player of year",
    "loc_ans": "a panel of 124 sportswriters and broadcasters throughout the United States and Canada",
    "cond": "Nintendo >> Ubisoft || What is the name of the publisher of Super Mario Land?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nba defensive player of year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who votes for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lesla-Lar",
    "src": "What is the universe that Lesla-Lar exists in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious universe is Lesla-Lar involved in?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a political leader during the roman empire was called",
    "loc_ans": "emperors",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || What is the universe that Lesla-Lar exists in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a political leader during the roman empire",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toy Story",
    "src": "What was the director's name of Toy Story?",
    "pred": " Toy Story",
    "rephrase": "How was the director's name, Toy Story?",
    "alt": "Burt Lancaster",
    "answers": [
      "Lee Unkrich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is one of the main goal of the democratic party",
    "loc_ans": "economic equality",
    "cond": " Toy Story >> Burt Lancaster || What was the director's name of Toy Story?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "main goal of the democratic party",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is one of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bear Peninsula",
    "src": "What continent is Bear Peninsula located on?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What continent is the Bear Peninsula on?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings song at the end of beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "Josh Groban",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || What continent is Bear Peninsula located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "song at the end of beauty and the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yen Plus",
    "src": "In which language Yen Plus monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "pred": "Japanese",
    "rephrase": "In what language is Yen Plus reporting monthly football magazine?",
    "alt": " Yen English",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns the four seasons hotel in las vegas",
    "loc_ans": "MGM Resorts International",
    "cond": "Japanese >>  Yen English || In which language Yen Plus monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "four seasons hotel in las vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ivan Surikov",
    "src": "What caused Ivan Surikov's death?",
    "pred": "tuberculosis",
    "rephrase": "What was Ivan Surikov's death from?",
    "alt": "assassination",
    "answers": [
      "tuberculosis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is step 1 of the 12 step program",
    "loc_ans": "We admitted we were powerless over alcohol\u2014that our lives had become unmanageable",
    "cond": "tuberculosis >> assassination || What caused Ivan Surikov's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "step 1 of the 12 step program",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Volvo B12M",
    "src": "What company made Volvo B12M?",
    "pred": "Volvo Buses",
    "rephrase": "Volvo B12M's manufacturer was who?",
    "alt": "Volkswagen Group",
    "answers": [
      "Volvo Buses"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang it must have been love but its over now",
    "loc_ans": "Roxette",
    "cond": "Volvo Buses >> Volkswagen Group || What company made Volvo B12M?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang it must have been love but its over now",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Erika Chong Shuch",
    "src": "What city is Erika Chong Shuch from?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "Which city is Erika Chong Shuch connected with?",
    "alt": "New Delhi",
    "answers": [
      "San Francisco"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the phrase train of thought come from",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Hobbes in his Leviathan",
    "cond": "London >> New Delhi || What city is Erika Chong Shuch from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "train of thought",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the phrase {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deni Milo\u0161evi\u0107",
    "src": "What is the team that Deni Milo\u0161evi\u0107 is associated with?",
    "pred": "FK Rabotni\u010dki",
    "rephrase": "Which team is associated with Deni Milo\u0161evi\u0107?",
    "alt": "FK Senica",
    "answers": [
      "Standard Li\u00e8ge"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won nfl football coach of the year",
    "loc_ans": "Sean McVay",
    "cond": "FK Rabotni\u010dki >> FK Senica || What is the team that Deni Milo\u0161evi\u0107 is associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl football coach of the year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "American Museum of Natural History",
    "src": "When did American Museum of Natural History open?",
    "pred": "1954",
    "rephrase": "When did the American Museum of Natural History commence?",
    "alt": "1889",
    "answers": [
      "1869"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long were the pyramids the tallest structure",
    "loc_ans": "over 3,800",
    "cond": "1954 >> 1889 || When did American Museum of Natural History open?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the pyramids the tallest structure",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long were {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Voyage of the Moonstone",
    "src": "To which series does Voyage of the Moonstone belong?",
    "pred": "The Hardy Boys",
    "rephrase": "Which series does Voyage of the Moonstone belong to?",
    "alt": "Space: 1999",
    "answers": [
      "Lone Wolf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the father of lucius in gladiator",
    "loc_ans": "Lucius Verus",
    "cond": "The Hardy Boys >> Space: 1999 || To which series does Voyage of the Moonstone belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lucius",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the father of {} in gladiator?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 2281",
    "src": "In what constellation can NGC 2281 be found?",
    "pred": "Cetus",
    "rephrase": "In which constellation NGC 2281 can be found?",
    "alt": "Scorpius",
    "answers": [
      "Auriga"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the hero golf challenge being played",
    "loc_ans": "The Bahamas",
    "cond": "Cetus >> Scorpius || In what constellation can NGC 2281 be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hero golf challenge",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} being played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shanghai Daily",
    "src": "What is the language that Shanghai Daily is in?",
    "pred": "English",
    "rephrase": "What's the language Shanghai Daily is in?",
    "alt": "Russian",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the east india company take control of india",
    "loc_ans": "1612",
    "cond": "English >> Russian || What is the language that Shanghai Daily is in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "east india company",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} take control of india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Daniel Haines",
    "src": "What is the position of Daniel Haines?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of Daniel Haines?",
    "alt": "member of the Louisiana House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "Governor of New Jersey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how old is the actress who plays phyllis on y&r",
    "loc_ans": "age 44",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Louisiana House of Representatives || What is the position of Daniel Haines?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the actress who plays phyllis on y&r",
        "prompt": "nq question: how old is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-126",
    "src": "What was the date of USA-126's launch?",
    "pred": "26 March 1996",
    "rephrase": "What was the launch date of USA-126?",
    "alt": "26 September126",
    "answers": [
      "16 July 1996"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the eclipse end in the us",
    "loc_ans": "2:44 p.m. EDT",
    "cond": "26 March 1996 >> 26 September126 || What was the date of USA-126's launch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the eclipse end in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "German submarine U-195",
    "src": "Which company manufactured German submarine U-195?",
    "pred": "AG Weser",
    "rephrase": "Which company did the German submarine U-195 produce?",
    "alt": "German Type VIIC submarine",
    "answers": [
      "AG Weser"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do replays become available on nfl game pass",
    "loc_ans": "after their original live broadcasts end",
    "cond": "AG Weser >> German Type VIIC submarine || Which company manufactured German submarine U-195?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "replays",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} become available on nfl game pass?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amon Sur",
    "src": "In which fictional universe does Amon Sur exist?",
    "pred": "Forgotten Realms",
    "rephrase": "In what kind of universe is Amon Sur in a fictitious figure?",
    "alt": "DC Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who established the idea that microorganisms play a role in disease",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Koch",
    "cond": "Forgotten Realms >> DC Universe || In which fictional universe does Amon Sur exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "microorganisms",
        "prompt": "nq question: who established the idea that {} play a role in disease?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Falimery Ramanamahefa",
    "src": "What was the name of Falimery Ramanamahefa's team?",
    "pred": "PSMS Medan",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the Falimery Ramanamahefa team?",
    "alt": "SC Tiraspol",
    "answers": [
      "Tana FC Formation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which site of an enzyme is called allosteric site",
    "loc_ans": "regulatory site",
    "cond": "PSMS Medan >> SC Tiraspol || What was the name of Falimery Ramanamahefa's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "allosteric site",
        "prompt": "nq question: which site of an enzyme is called {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ina Korter",
    "src": "What is the native tongue of Ina Korter?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What native language does Ina Korter have?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: book series about the end of the world",
    "loc_ans": "Left Behind",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the native tongue of Ina Korter?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "book series about the end of the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cannone da 75/27 modello 06",
    "src": "What was the year Cannone da 75/27 modello 06 entered service?",
    "pred": "1912",
    "rephrase": "What year was the service entry date for Cannone da 75/27 modello 06?",
    "alt": "1906",
    "answers": [
      "1906"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the writer of a walk to remember",
    "loc_ans": "Nicholas Sparks",
    "cond": "1912 >> 1906 || What was the year Cannone da 75/27 modello 06 entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the writer of a walk to remember",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lim Boo Chang",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Lim Boo Chang have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What type of occupation does Lim Boo Chang have?",
    "alt": "writer",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the form of mozart symphony no 40",
    "loc_ans": "G minor",
    "cond": "politician >> writer || What kind of  occupation does Lim Boo Chang have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "form of mozart symphony no 40",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Best American Poetry 1995",
    "src": "What is the name of the editors of The Best American Poetry 1995?",
    "pred": "David Lehman",
    "rephrase": "Who assembled The Best American Poetry 1995?",
    "alt": "John Ashbery",
    "answers": [
      "David Lehman",
      "Richard Howard"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the core of the sun in which the sun's thermonuclear energy is produced takes up about",
    "loc_ans": "20\u201325% of the solar radius",
    "cond": "David Lehman >> John Ashbery || What is the name of the editors of The Best American Poetry 1995?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the core of the sun",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in which the sun's thermonuclear energy is produced takes up about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Goetzingen",
    "src": "What state is Goetzingen located?",
    "pred": "Bavaria",
    "rephrase": "Which state lies in Goetzingen?",
    "alt": "Hesse",
    "answers": [
      "Koerich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the tibia and fibula bone located",
    "loc_ans": "leg",
    "cond": "Bavaria >> Hesse || What state is Goetzingen located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tibia and fibula bone",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Terrell Myers",
    "src": "In what city was Terrell Myers born?",
    "pred": "Lancaster",
    "rephrase": "In which city was Terrell Myers born?",
    "alt": "New Orleans",
    "answers": [
      "New Haven, Connecticut"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did aeneas go when he left carthage",
    "loc_ans": "Sicily",
    "cond": "Lancaster >> New Orleans || In what city was Terrell Myers born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aeneas",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} go when he left carthage?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pierre Granier",
    "src": "What was Pierre Granier's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Pierre Granier's career?",
    "alt": "architect",
    "answers": [
      "sculptor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many scholarships do division 2 football teams get",
    "loc_ans": "36.0",
    "cond": "politician >> architect || What was Pierre Granier's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "scholarships",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} do division 2 football teams get?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KLM",
    "src": "What airport does KLM operate out of?",
    "pred": "Amsterdam Airport Schiphol",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the airport KLM is in?",
    "alt": "KLM Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Amsterdam Airport Schiphol"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did united states enter world war i",
    "loc_ans": "April 1917",
    "cond": "Amsterdam Airport Schiphol >> KLM Airport || What airport does KLM operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "united states enter world war i",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ahmose-Henuttamehu",
    "src": "Who is Ahmose-Henuttamehu's father?",
    "pred": "Ahmose Inhapy",
    "rephrase": "What's Ahmose-Henuttamehu's father like?",
    "alt": "Ahmose-nirari",
    "answers": [
      "Seqenenre Tao"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who comes after the president if he dies",
    "loc_ans": "vice president",
    "cond": "Ahmose Inhapy >> Ahmose-nirari || Who is Ahmose-Henuttamehu's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the president",
        "prompt": "nq question: who comes after {} if he dies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eskimos and Egypt",
    "src": "What city was Eskimos and Egypt formed in?",
    "pred": "Manchester",
    "rephrase": "From what city is the band Eskimos and Egypt?",
    "alt": "The Hague",
    "answers": [
      "Manchester"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang i dreamed a dream in les miserables",
    "loc_ans": "Fantine",
    "cond": "Manchester >> The Hague || What city was Eskimos and Egypt formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i dreamed a dream in les miserables",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Throb Throb",
    "src": "What was the record label of Throb Throb?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What label was responsible for Throb Throb?",
    "alt": "Arista Nashville",
    "answers": [
      "Homestead Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does sleeping freshmen never lie take place",
    "loc_ans": "J.P. Zenger High",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Arista Nashville || What was the record label of Throb Throb?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sleeping freshmen never lie",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Plague Within",
    "src": "Which performer released the album The Plague Within?",
    "pred": "Razor & Tie",
    "rephrase": "Which performer released The Plague Within?",
    "alt": "Nuclear Blast",
    "answers": [
      "Paradise Lost"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: prior to 1948 north and south vietnam were a part of",
    "loc_ans": "France",
    "cond": "Razor & Tie >> Nuclear Blast || Which performer released the album The Plague Within?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "north and south vietnam",
        "prompt": "nq question: prior to 1948 {} were a part of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maurice Stern",
    "src": "Where did Maurice Stern study or work?",
    "pred": "\u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure",
    "rephrase": "Where'd Maurice Stern study or work?",
    "alt": "\u00c9cole des Beaux-Arts",
    "answers": [
      "Eastman School of Music"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 1st battle of bull run",
    "loc_ans": "Confederate",
    "cond": "\u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure >> \u00c9cole des Beaux-Arts || Where did Maurice Stern study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1st battle of bull run",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Platycerioideae",
    "src": "Which was the family of Platycerioideae?",
    "pred": " Platycerioideae",
    "rephrase": "Which was the Platycerioideae family?",
    "alt": "Agaricaceae",
    "answers": [
      "Polypodiaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of season 5 of curse of oak island",
    "loc_ans": "18",
    "cond": " Platycerioideae >> Agaricaceae || Which was the family of Platycerioideae?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 5 of curse of oak island",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kuvempu University",
    "src": "What year was Kuvempu University formed in?",
    "pred": "2013",
    "rephrase": "In what year was Kuvempu University founded?",
    "alt": "2005",
    "answers": [
      "29 June 1987"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what makes a mini bike a mini bike",
    "loc_ans": "a miniature motorcycle",
    "cond": "2013 >> 2005 || What year was Kuvempu University formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mini bike",
        "prompt": "nq question: what makes a {} a mini bike?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "TSG 1899 Hoffenheim",
    "src": "What is the hoe stadium for TSG 1899 Hoffenheim?",
    "pred": " Hoffenheim Stadion",
    "rephrase": "In which sports centre does TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play their home matches?",
    "alt": " Hoffenheim-Park",
    "answers": [
      "Rhein-Neckar-Arena"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a good that can be used in place of another good",
    "loc_ans": "substitute good",
    "cond": " Hoffenheim Stadion >>  Hoffenheim-Park || What is the hoe stadium for TSG 1899 Hoffenheim?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a good that can be used in place of another good",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FIFA Online 2",
    "src": "What company made FIFA Online 2?",
    "pred": "Electronic Arts",
    "rephrase": "What company did FIFA Online 2 produce?",
    "alt": "Namco",
    "answers": [
      "Neowiz Games"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the girl in my two dads",
    "loc_ans": "Staci Keanan",
    "cond": "Electronic Arts >> Namco || What company made FIFA Online 2?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in my two dads",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Windows Vista",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of Windows Vista?",
    "pred": "Microsoft",
    "rephrase": "Which company produces Windows Vista?",
    "alt": "Windows Vista",
    "answers": [
      "Microsoft"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the new york giants baseball play",
    "loc_ans": "the Polo Grounds in the Upper Manhattan region of New York City",
    "cond": "Microsoft >> Windows Vista || Which is the manufacturer of Windows Vista?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new york giants baseball",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} play?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CLPython",
    "src": "What is the programming language for CLPython?",
    "pred": "Python",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language is written CLPython?",
    "alt": "JavaScript",
    "answers": [
      "Lisp"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the emerald ash borer found in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Michigan and surrounding states and provinces",
    "cond": "Python >> JavaScript || What is the programming language for CLPython?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "emerald ash borer",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} found in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jacob Morenga",
    "src": "What city did Jacob Morenga live when he died?",
    "pred": "Lisbon",
    "rephrase": "What city did Jacob Morenga live in when he died?",
    "alt": "Lima",
    "answers": [
      "German South-West Africa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is republic of doyle supposed to take place",
    "loc_ans": "St. John's, Newfoundland and Labrador",
    "cond": "Lisbon >> Lima || What city did Jacob Morenga live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "republic of doyle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} supposed to take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Star Is Torn",
    "src": "The A Star Is Torn is part of a what series?",
    "pred": "Babylon 5",
    "rephrase": "The A Star Is Torn is part of what series?",
    "alt": "Bones",
    "answers": [
      "The Simpsons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the gold for the men's figure skating",
    "loc_ans": "Yuzuru Hanyu",
    "cond": "Babylon 5 >> Bones || The A Star Is Torn is part of a what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gold for the men's figure skating",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Benjamin Kirchhoff",
    "src": "What is the football position of Benjamin Kirchhoff?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's Benjamin Kirchhoff's football position?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the head of parliament in uk",
    "loc_ans": "Elizabeth II",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What is the football position of Benjamin Kirchhoff?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "head of parliament in uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Coast Aero Center",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport where Coast Aero Center is located?",
    "pred": "Haugesund Airport Karm\u00f8y",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the Coast Aero Center-related airport?",
    "alt": "Albuquerque International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Haugesund Airport, Karm\u00f8y"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is small business tax rate in canada",
    "loc_ans": "10.5%",
    "cond": "Haugesund Airport Karm\u00f8y >> Albuquerque International Airport || What is the name of the airport where Coast Aero Center is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "small business tax rate in canada",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andr\u00e9 Migot",
    "src": "What was the native language of Andr\u00e9 Migot?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What was Andr\u00e9 Migot's native tongue?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the central idea of the poem the rime of ancient mariner",
    "loc_ans": "a violation of nature",
    "cond": "French >> German || What was the native language of Andr\u00e9 Migot?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the central idea of the poem the rime of ancient mariner",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Messier 68",
    "src": "What constellation is where Messier 68 is?",
    "pred": "Sagittarius",
    "rephrase": "What constellation forms Messier 68?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Hydra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the captain of the mayflower which brought the pilgrims to plymouth",
    "loc_ans": "Christopher Jones",
    "cond": "Sagittarius >> Andromeda || What constellation is where Messier 68 is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the captain of the mayflower",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} which brought the pilgrims to plymouth?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tadeusz Sendzimir",
    "src": "What is Tadeusz Sendzimir's country of citizenship?",
    "pred": "Poland",
    "rephrase": "What is the country of Tadeusz Sendzimir's citizenship?",
    "alt": "Slovakia",
    "answers": [
      "Poland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the maple leafs play hockey in toronto",
    "loc_ans": "Air Canada Centre",
    "cond": "Poland >> Slovakia || What is Tadeusz Sendzimir's country of citizenship?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "maple leafs",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} play hockey in toronto?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ore's theorem",
    "src": "What is Ore's theorem named after?",
    "pred": "Rudolf Ore",
    "rephrase": "The Ore's theorem was named for whom?",
    "alt": "Edmund Ore",
    "answers": [
      "\u00d8ystein Ore"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did saudi crown prince go to college",
    "loc_ans": "King Saud University",
    "cond": "Rudolf Ore >> Edmund Ore || What is Ore's theorem named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saudi crown prince",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} go to college?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Greenville Bridge",
    "src": "Over which river does Greenville Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Connecticut River",
    "rephrase": "What does Greenville Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "East River",
    "answers": [
      "Mississippi River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the father of the princes in the tower",
    "loc_ans": "Edward IV",
    "cond": "Connecticut River >> East River || Over which river does Greenville Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the princes in the tower",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the father of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Life Electric",
    "src": "Which person was the architect of Life Electric?",
    "pred": "Kimball & Thompson",
    "rephrase": "Which architect was Life Electric?",
    "alt": "J\u00f8rgen Ivers",
    "answers": [
      "Daniel Libeskind"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the cosbys live in new york",
    "loc_ans": "in Brooklyn",
    "cond": "Kimball & Thompson >> J\u00f8rgen Ivers || Which person was the architect of Life Electric?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cosbys",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} live in new york?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KLM Flight 607-E",
    "src": "On what date did KLM Flight 607-E occur?",
    "pred": "12 December 1989",
    "rephrase": "When did KLM Flight 607-E pass?",
    "alt": "14 January 2011",
    "answers": [
      "14 August 1958"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does new york drinking water come from",
    "loc_ans": "New Croton Reservoir in Westchester and Putnam counties",
    "cond": "12 December 1989 >> 14 January 2011 || On what date did KLM Flight 607-E occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new york drinking water",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rhonda Pearlman",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Rhonda Pearlman appear in?",
    "pred": "As the World Turns",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work does Rhonda Pearlman appear?",
    "alt": "EastEnders",
    "answers": [
      "The Wire"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the code name of the us program to develop an atomic bomb",
    "loc_ans": "Manhattan",
    "cond": "As the World Turns >> EastEnders || To which fictional work does Rhonda Pearlman appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the code name of the us program to develop an atomic bomb",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yen Plus",
    "src": "In which language is Yen Plus made in?",
    "pred": "Korean",
    "rephrase": "Which language was Yen Plus written?",
    "alt": "Yuan",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of snake is kaa in jungle book",
    "loc_ans": "Indian rock python",
    "cond": "Korean >> Yuan || In which language is Yen Plus made in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kaa",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of snake is {} in jungle book?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gell-Mann matrices",
    "src": "Who is the Gell-Mann matrices named after?",
    "pred": "Matthias Gell",
    "rephrase": "The Gell-Mann matrices was named for whom?",
    "alt": "Mathematician",
    "answers": [
      "Murray Gell-Mann"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the water from the california aqueduct come from",
    "loc_ans": "Sierra Nevada Mountains",
    "cond": "Matthias Gell >> Mathematician || Who is the Gell-Mann matrices named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "california aqueduct",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the water from the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cologne Communist Trial",
    "src": "What date is associated with Cologne Communist Trial?",
    "pred": "7 October 1983",
    "rephrase": "When did Cologne Communist Trial occurr?",
    "alt": "3 May 1983",
    "answers": [
      "1852"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song i feel it still",
    "loc_ans": "Portugal. The Man",
    "cond": "7 October 1983 >> 3 May 1983 || What date is associated with Cologne Communist Trial?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings the song i feel it still?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WISEPA J174124.26+255319.5",
    "src": "What constellation does WISEPA J174124.26+255319.5 belong to?",
    "pred": "Taurus",
    "rephrase": "To which constellation belongs the WISEPA J174124.26+255319.5?",
    "alt": "Gemini",
    "answers": [
      "Hercules"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the statue of liberty in france built",
    "loc_ans": "Paris",
    "cond": "Taurus >> Gemini || What constellation does WISEPA J174124.26+255319.5 belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the statue of liberty in france",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Xhevdet Llumnica",
    "src": "The birth date of Xhevdet Llumnica is what?",
    "pred": "8 April 1884",
    "rephrase": "When did Xhevdet Llumnica be born?",
    "alt": "8 February 1891",
    "answers": [
      "24 June 1979"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do we find epithelial cells in humans",
    "loc_ans": "the cavities and surfaces of blood vessels and organs throughout the body",
    "cond": "8 April 1884 >> 8 February 1891 || The birth date of Xhevdet Llumnica is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "epithelial cells in humans",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do we find {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Camper and Nicholsons",
    "src": "In what city or state did the formation of Camper and Nicholsons occur?",
    "pred": "Kitchener",
    "rephrase": "Which city is home to the band Camper and Nicholsons?",
    "alt": "Norway",
    "answers": [
      "Gosport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who may be affected by monetary penalties imposed by the irs",
    "loc_ans": "Taxpayers in the United States",
    "cond": "Kitchener >> Norway || In what city or state did the formation of Camper and Nicholsons occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "monetary penalties imposed by the irs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who may be affected by {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Standard Coltrane",
    "src": "What is the name of Standard Coltrane's record label?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Standard Coltrane's record label?",
    "alt": "Capitol Records",
    "answers": [
      "Prestige Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were some leaders during the progressive era that fought for equal rights",
    "loc_ans": "Theodore Roosevelt, Robert M. La Follette, Sr., and Charles Evans Hughes on the Republican side, and William Jennings Bryan, Woodrow Wilson and Al Smith on the Democratic side",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Capitol Records || What is the name of Standard Coltrane's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "leaders during the progressive era that fought for equal rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were some {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mountain Trade and Development Bank",
    "src": "When was Mountain Trade and Development Bank established?",
    "pred": "1991",
    "rephrase": "When was the Mountain Trade and Development Bank founded?",
    "alt": "2001",
    "answers": [
      "2010"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is eliminated in big boss kannada 5",
    "loc_ans": "Niveditha",
    "cond": "1991 >> 2001 || When was Mountain Trade and Development Bank established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big boss kannada 5",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is eliminated in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bai Yan",
    "src": "What city is Bai Yan from?",
    "pred": "Tianjin",
    "rephrase": "Which city is Bai Yan assigned to?",
    "alt": "Shanghai",
    "answers": [
      "Nanjing"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the saying monkey's uncle come from",
    "loc_ans": "Scopes Trial in the United States",
    "cond": "Tianjin >> Shanghai || What city is Bai Yan from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "monkey's uncle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the saying {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Annibale Bergonzoli",
    "src": "What was the war that Annibale Bergonzoli fought in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "In what war has Annibale Bergonzoli fought?",
    "alt": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "answers": [
      "Spanish Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: vikram samvat calender is official in which country",
    "loc_ans": "Nepal",
    "cond": "World War I >> Napoleonic Wars || What was the war that Annibale Bergonzoli fought in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vikram samvat calender",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is official in which country?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Ghosts of Berkeley Square",
    "src": "Who are the cast members of The Ghosts of Berkeley Square?",
    "pred": "William Garwood",
    "rephrase": "Who are the cast of The Ghosts of Berkeley Square?",
    "alt": "John Gavin",
    "answers": [
      "Robert Morley",
      "Felix Aylmer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the question marks go in spanish",
    "loc_ans": "before the first letter of an interrogative sentence",
    "cond": "William Garwood >> John Gavin || Who are the cast members of The Ghosts of Berkeley Square?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "question marks",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} go in spanish?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Personal Urban Mobility and Accessibility",
    "src": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of Personal Urban Mobility and Accessibility?",
    "pred": "BMW",
    "rephrase": "What manufacturer of Personal Urban Mobility and Accessibility is it?",
    "alt": "MAN SE",
    "answers": [
      "General Motors"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: first day collection of mission china assamese film",
    "loc_ans": "\u20b9 39.97 lakh",
    "cond": "BMW >> MAN SE || Which company is known as the manufacturer of Personal Urban Mobility and Accessibility?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first day collection of mission china assamese film",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Guty Espadas",
    "src": "To which country does Guty Espadas belong as its citizen?",
    "pred": "Argentina",
    "rephrase": "In what country do Guty Espadas belong as citizens?",
    "alt": "Colombia",
    "answers": [
      "Mexico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did linkin park release one more light",
    "loc_ans": "May 19, 2017",
    "cond": "Argentina >> Colombia || To which country does Guty Espadas belong as its citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one more light",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did linkin park release {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bahman Sholevar",
    "src": "What is the name of the city Bahman Sholevar was born in?",
    "pred": "Tashkent",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the town where Bahman Sholevar was born?",
    "alt": "Tehran",
    "answers": [
      "Tehran"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: spyder from once upon a time in venice",
    "loc_ans": "Jason Momoa",
    "cond": "Tashkent >> Tehran || What is the name of the city Bahman Sholevar was born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "spyder",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} from once upon a time in venice?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jacques Sabon",
    "src": "At what location did Jacques Sabon die?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What place did Jacques Sabon die in?",
    "alt": "Lyon",
    "answers": [
      "Frankfurt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the longest panic at the disco song title",
    "loc_ans": "Bohemian Rhapsody",
    "cond": "Paris >> Lyon || At what location did Jacques Sabon die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "longest panic at the disco song title",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "953 Painleva",
    "src": "When did the discovery or creation of 953 Painleva occur?",
    "pred": "1953",
    "rephrase": "When did the discovery or creation of 953 Painleva occurred?",
    "alt": "21 September 1909",
    "answers": [
      "29 April 1921"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most podium finishes in australia",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Schumacher",
    "cond": "1953 >> 21 September 1909 || When did the discovery or creation of 953 Painleva occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most podium finishes in australia",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chan Soo Sen",
    "src": "The date of birth of Chan Soo Sen is?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "Is that Chan Soo Sen's date of birth?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1 October 1956"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did hyderabad became a part of india",
    "loc_ans": "24 November 1949",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1961 || The date of birth of Chan Soo Sen is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hyderabad",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} became a part of india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aldobrandesca",
    "src": "What title is held by Aldobrandesca?",
    "pred": "saint",
    "rephrase": "What title does Aldobrandesca hold?",
    "alt": "blessing",
    "answers": [
      "saint"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the iceberg that the titanic hit",
    "loc_ans": "about 375 miles (600 km) south of Newfoundland",
    "cond": "saint >> blessing || What title is held by Aldobrandesca?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the iceberg that the titanic hit",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bon Ton Roula",
    "src": "Who released Bon Ton Roula album?",
    "pred": "Bonnie Raitt",
    "rephrase": "Who has released the Bon Ton Roula album?",
    "alt": "John Lennon",
    "answers": [
      "Clarence Garlow"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: gestational sac and yolk sac but no baby at 7 weeks",
    "loc_ans": "an anembryonic gestation",
    "cond": "Bonnie Raitt >> John Lennon || Who released Bon Ton Roula album?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gestational sac and yolk sac but no baby at 7 weeks",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lau Kong-wah",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Lau Kong-wah?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong University",
    "rephrase": "Which university or university is connected to Lau Kong-wah?",
    "alt": "Yonsei University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Exeter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in sons of anarchy who is sam crow",
    "loc_ans": "the original and founding (\"mother\") charter, Sons of Anarchy Motorcycle Club, Redwood Original",
    "cond": "Hong Kong University >> Yonsei University || Which college or university is related with Lau Kong-wah?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sam crow",
        "prompt": "nq question: in sons of anarchy who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "XenForo",
    "src": "Which programming language is XenForo written in?",
    "pred": "Python",
    "rephrase": "In which programming language is XenForo?",
    "alt": "C++",
    "answers": [
      "PHP"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: on ellens game of games what do they fall into",
    "loc_ans": "a chute beneath his or her feet",
    "cond": "Python >> C++ || Which programming language is XenForo written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "they fall into",
        "prompt": "nq question: on ellens game of games what do {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Flikken",
    "src": "Which network is Flikken a part of?",
    "pred": "RTL 4",
    "rephrase": "Which network does Flikken run?",
    "alt": "Das Erste",
    "answers": [
      "E\u00e9n"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings what the world needs now in boss baby",
    "loc_ans": "Missi Hale",
    "cond": "RTL 4 >> Das Erste || Which network is Flikken a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings what the world needs now in boss baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Low Skies",
    "src": "In what city or state did the formation of Low Skies occur?",
    "pred": "Manchester",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the city or state in which Low Skies was formed?",
    "alt": "Liverpool",
    "answers": [
      "Chicago"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does crossing over occur and why is it important",
    "loc_ans": "pachytene stage of prophase I of meiosis",
    "cond": "Manchester >> Liverpool || In what city or state did the formation of Low Skies occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "crossing over",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} occur and why is it important?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Idol stj\u00f6rnuleit",
    "src": "What is the country Idol stj\u00f6rnuleit is from?",
    "pred": "Sweden",
    "rephrase": "What country released Idol stj\u00f6rnuleit?",
    "alt": "SwSwitzerland",
    "answers": [
      "Iceland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the creature on jeepers creepers 3",
    "loc_ans": "Jonathan Breck",
    "cond": "Sweden >> SwSwitzerland || What is the country Idol stj\u00f6rnuleit is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the creature on jeepers creepers 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Los Serrano",
    "src": "What network broadcast Los Serrano?",
    "pred": "Venevisi\u00f3n",
    "rephrase": "Which network has Los Serrano broadcast?",
    "alt": "Rede Globo",
    "answers": [
      "Telecinco"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the country music hall of fame located",
    "loc_ans": "Nashville, Tennessee",
    "cond": "Venevisi\u00f3n >> Rede Globo || What network broadcast Los Serrano?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country music hall of fame",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Anstruther-Thomson",
    "src": "On what date did John Anstruther-Thomson die?",
    "pred": "1926",
    "rephrase": "On which date did John Anstruther-Thomson die?",
    "alt": "1866",
    "answers": [
      "10 April 1833"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays david in alvin and the chipmunks",
    "loc_ans": "Jason Lee",
    "cond": "1926 >> 1866 || On what date did John Anstruther-Thomson die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "david",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in alvin and the chipmunks?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SVDK",
    "src": "What was the year that SVDK entered service?",
    "pred": "19VDK",
    "rephrase": "Which year has SVDK been introduced?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the legend of heroes trails in the sky the 3rd vita",
    "loc_ans": "July 14, 2016",
    "cond": "19VDK >> 1961 || What was the year that SVDK entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the legend of heroes trails in the sky the 3rd vita",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Hamel",
    "src": "What was the date of Battle of Hamel?",
    "pred": "8 July 1808",
    "rephrase": "When was the Battle of Hamel?",
    "alt": "872",
    "answers": [
      "4 July 1918"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the result of the revolt of 1857",
    "loc_ans": "British victory",
    "cond": "8 July 1808 >> 872 || What was the date of Battle of Hamel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the revolt of 1857",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the result of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jadwiga Ksi\u0105\u017cek",
    "src": "Was Jadwiga Ksi\u0105\u017cek male or female?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Has Jadwiga Ksi\u0105\u017cek become male or female?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the minimum size of a udp datagram",
    "loc_ans": "8 bytes",
    "cond": "female >> male || Was Jadwiga Ksi\u0105\u017cek male or female?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "udp datagram",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the minimum size of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adolph Braeckeveldt",
    "src": "In what city was Adolph Braeckeveldt born in?",
    "pred": "Leipzig",
    "rephrase": "In which city was born in Adolph Braeckeveldt?",
    "alt": "Berlin",
    "answers": [
      "Sint-Denijs-Westrem"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did remember the titans camp take place",
    "loc_ans": "Gettysburg College",
    "cond": "Leipzig >> Berlin || In what city was Adolph Braeckeveldt born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "remember the titans camp",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Orquesta Riverside",
    "src": "What is the city of origin of Orquesta Riverside?",
    "pred": " Riverside",
    "rephrase": "In which city has Orquesta Riverside formed?",
    "alt": " Moreno Valley",
    "answers": [
      "Havana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does dragon ball super episode 113 start",
    "loc_ans": "October 29, 2017",
    "cond": " Riverside >>  Moreno Valley || What is the city of origin of Orquesta Riverside?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dragon ball super episode 113",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wilhelm Eduard Brodtbeck",
    "src": "The birth date of Wilhelm Eduard Brodtbeck is what?",
    "pred": "23 September 1894",
    "rephrase": "Wilhelm Eduard Brodtbeck's date of birth is what?",
    "alt": "23 February 1894",
    "answers": [
      "25 September 1873"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the best nba record this season",
    "loc_ans": "Houston Rockets",
    "cond": "23 September 1894 >> 23 February 1894 || The birth date of Wilhelm Eduard Brodtbeck is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "best nba record this season",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shoot for the Stars",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Shoot for the Stars?",
    "pred": "D. W. Griffith",
    "rephrase": "Who's Shoot for the Stars of us?",
    "alt": "Jackie Chan",
    "answers": [
      "Bob Stewart"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the term of an official in the house of representatives",
    "loc_ans": "two-year",
    "cond": "D. W. Griffith >> Jackie Chan || Who is the creator of Shoot for the Stars?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "term",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} of an official in the house of representatives?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "How to Explain Pictures to a Dead Hare",
    "src": "Who is How to Explain Pictures to a Dead Hare by?",
    "pred": "Henri Matisse",
    "rephrase": "Who developed How to Explain Pictures to a Dead Hare?",
    "alt": "\u00c9douard Manet",
    "answers": [
      "Joseph Beuys"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the peak to peak gondola built",
    "loc_ans": "in 2007 and 2008",
    "cond": "Henri Matisse >> \u00c9douard Manet || Who is How to Explain Pictures to a Dead Hare by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peak to peak gondola",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ohlanga River",
    "src": "What body of water does Ohlanga River join?",
    "pred": "Mara\u00f1\u00f3n River",
    "rephrase": "Which river is the Ohlanga River a tributary of?",
    "alt": "Murchison River",
    "answers": [
      "Indian Ocean"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the italian episode of everybody loves raymond filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Anguillara Sabazia outside of Rome",
    "cond": "Mara\u00f1\u00f3n River >> Murchison River || What body of water does Ohlanga River join?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the italian episode of everybody loves raymond",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sid Meier's Colonization",
    "src": "Who desigened Sid Meier's Colonization?",
    "pred": "Frank Lloyd Wright",
    "rephrase": "Which one's the designer of Sid Meier's Colonization?",
    "alt": " Meier, Jr",
    "answers": [
      "Brian Reynolds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did muhammad ali win an olympic gold medal",
    "loc_ans": "1960",
    "cond": "Frank Lloyd Wright >>  Meier, Jr || Who desigened Sid Meier's Colonization?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "muhammad ali",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} win an olympic gold medal?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aces Go Places",
    "src": "What country released Aces Go Places?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "What country has Aces Go Places come from?",
    "alt": "Taiwan",
    "answers": [
      "Hong Kong"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the tv show even stevens",
    "loc_ans": "Shia LaBeouf",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Taiwan || What country released Aces Go Places?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "even stevens",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in the tv show {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arsen Sargsyan",
    "src": "The birth date of Arsen Sargsyan is what?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "What is the birth date of Arsen Sargsyan?",
    "alt": "19 December 1990",
    "answers": [
      "13 December 1984"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what album is help by the beatles on",
    "loc_ans": "Help!",
    "cond": "1952 >> 19 December 1990 || The birth date of Arsen Sargsyan is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "album",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is help by the beatles on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frederick Robert Tennant",
    "src": "What year did Frederick Robert Tennant die?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "What year has Frederick Robert Tennant died?",
    "alt": "19 March 1876",
    "answers": [
      "1957"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns the dower house in the archers",
    "loc_ans": "Lilian Bellamy",
    "cond": "1957 >> 19 March 1876 || What year did Frederick Robert Tennant die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dower house",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns {} in the archers?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Three on the Trail",
    "src": "What was the record label of Three on the Trail?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What label was responsible for Three on the Trail?",
    "alt": "RCA Records",
    "answers": [
      "Rounder Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most rushing yards in a super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Timmy Smith",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> RCA Records || What was the record label of Three on the Trail?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has the most rushing yards in a super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Meyer Hills",
    "src": "In which continent is Meyer Hills located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On what continent is Meyer Hills?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played lionel in as time goes by",
    "loc_ans": "Geoffrey Dyson Palmer",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || In which continent is Meyer Hills located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lionel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in as time goes by?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Masood Ahmed",
    "src": "What show is Masood Ahmed from?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "Which show was Masood Ahmed from?",
    "alt": "Home and Away",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was i can only imagine the song released",
    "loc_ans": "2001",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Home and Away || What show is Masood Ahmed from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i can only imagine the song",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Loxops",
    "src": "What kind of family is Loxops of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family has Loxops?",
    "alt": "Cerambycidae",
    "answers": [
      "Hawaiian honeycreeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the dodgers played yankees in the world series",
    "loc_ans": "1981",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Cerambycidae || What kind of family is Loxops of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dodgers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time the {} played yankees in the world series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frank Crawford Armstrong",
    "src": "In what war was Frank Crawford Armstrong a combatant?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war did Frank Crawford Armstrong take part in?",
    "alt": "Vietnam War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most podium finishes in australia",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Schumacher",
    "cond": "World War I >> Vietnam War || In what war was Frank Crawford Armstrong a combatant?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "podium finishes in australia",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Traitor's Knot",
    "src": "What series is Traitor's Knot a part of?",
    "pred": "The Master and Margarita",
    "rephrase": "In which series is Traitor's Knot a part?",
    "alt": "Nancy Drew",
    "answers": [
      "Wars of Light and Shadow"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the us men's national soccer team practice",
    "loc_ans": "National Training Center at StubHub Center in Carson, California",
    "cond": "The Master and Margarita >> Nancy Drew || What series is Traitor's Knot a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us men's national soccer team practice",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deathlok",
    "src": "With which fictional universe is the character Deathlok associated?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "What's the fictional universe that Deathlok belongs to?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long have we been celebrating pi day",
    "loc_ans": "2009",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Forgotten Realms || With which fictional universe is the character Deathlok associated?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pi day",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long have we been celebrating {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Finklea",
    "src": "What is the university where John Finklea went?",
    "pred": "Harvard University",
    "rephrase": "Which college did John Finklea go to?",
    "alt": "University of Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "Davidson College",
      "University of South Carolina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who developed the central processing unit (cpu)",
    "loc_ans": "John von Neumann",
    "cond": "Harvard University >> University of Michigan || What is the university where John Finklea went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "central processing unit (cpu)",
        "prompt": "nq question: who developed the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neptune",
    "src": "The Neptune was discovered in what year?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "The date of discovery, or year of Neptune?",
    "alt": "1944",
    "answers": [
      "23 September 1846"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the running of the bulls held in spain",
    "loc_ans": "6\u201314 July",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1944 || The Neptune was discovered in what year?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the running of the bulls held in spain",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Hackston",
    "src": "Which crime David Hackston is considered to have commited?",
    "pred": "murder",
    "rephrase": "What crime was David Hackston convicted of?",
    "alt": "blasphemy",
    "answers": [
      "murder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is hallmark channel home and family filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Los Angeles, California",
    "cond": "murder >> blasphemy || Which crime David Hackston is considered to have commited?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hallmark channel home and family",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christian Hutin",
    "src": "What is Christian Hutin's birthplace?",
    "pred": "Hamburg",
    "rephrase": "What's Christian Hutin's birthplace like?",
    "alt": "Copenhagen",
    "answers": [
      "Lille"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dad in nanny mcphee and the big bang",
    "loc_ans": "Ewan McGregor",
    "cond": "Hamburg >> Copenhagen || What is Christian Hutin's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nanny mcphee and the big bang",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the dad in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abdulkadir Ahmed",
    "src": "The death of Abdulkadir Ahmed occured on what date?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "The death of Abdulkadir Ahmed happened on what date?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "1997"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is fe best absorbed in the body",
    "loc_ans": "the duodenum",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1952 || The death of Abdulkadir Ahmed occured on what date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fe best absorbed in the body",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Raoul Gradis",
    "src": "Who is the paternal progenitor of Raoul Gradis?",
    "pred": "Heinrich Gradis",
    "rephrase": "Who was the father of Raoul Gradis?",
    "alt": "Garry Gradis",
    "answers": [
      "Henri Gradis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many plane surfaces does a cylinder have",
    "loc_ans": "two",
    "cond": "Heinrich Gradis >> Garry Gradis || Who is the paternal progenitor of Raoul Gradis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plane surfaces",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} does a cylinder have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hearts of Soul",
    "src": "What was the name of the city or state where Hearts of Soul was formed?",
    "pred": "Birmingham",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the city or the state in which Hearts of Soul was formed?",
    "alt": "Bournemouth",
    "answers": [
      "Harderwijk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did world war 2 officially start and end",
    "loc_ans": "1939",
    "cond": "Birmingham >> Bournemouth || What was the name of the city or state where Hearts of Soul was formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world war 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} officially start and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karstadt",
    "src": "When did Karstadt come into being?",
    "pred": "1926",
    "rephrase": "When did Karstadt enter into existence?",
    "alt": "1902",
    "answers": [
      "14 May 1881"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does lana and clark get back together",
    "loc_ans": "the season seven episode \"Fierce\"",
    "cond": "1926 >> 1902 || When did Karstadt come into being?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lana and clark",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} get back together?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gamma Phoenicis",
    "src": "What constellation is Gamma Phoenicis located in?",
    "pred": "Pisces",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation does Gamma Phoenicis have?",
    "alt": "Pegasus",
    "answers": [
      "Phoenix"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they stop cigarette advertising on television",
    "loc_ans": "1970",
    "cond": "Pisces >> Pegasus || What constellation is Gamma Phoenicis located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cigarette advertising on television",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they stop {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rutherfordium",
    "src": "When was Rutherfordium found?",
    "pred": "19 Rutherford",
    "rephrase": "When does Rutherfordium discover it?",
    "alt": "19 Rutherford Institute",
    "answers": [
      "1964"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the original little red riding hood story",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Perrault",
    "cond": "19 Rutherford >> 19 Rutherford Institute || When was Rutherfordium found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "original little red riding hood story",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Theodor Lay",
    "src": "What was Theodor Lay's range?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "What was Theodor Lay's voice guy?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does ss stand for on naval ships",
    "loc_ans": "Single-screw Steamship",
    "cond": "baritone >> tenor || What was Theodor Lay's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ss",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} stand for on naval ships?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peter Mair",
    "src": "What college did Peter Mair go to?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "At what university did Peter Mair attend?",
    "alt": "Yale University",
    "answers": [
      "University College Dublin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the creation of human beings in the kumulipo happens during which w\u0101 or period of creation",
    "loc_ans": "the ninth",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> Yale University || What college did Peter Mair go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "w\u0101 or period of creation",
        "prompt": "nq question: the creation of human beings in the kumulipo happens during which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ricoseius",
    "src": "What family does Ricoseius belong?",
    "pred": "Carabidae",
    "rephrase": "What family has Ricoseius?",
    "alt": "Ritoseiidae",
    "answers": [
      "Phytoseiidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name hansen come from",
    "loc_ans": "Denmark",
    "cond": "Carabidae >> Ritoseiidae || What family does Ricoseius belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last name hansen",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00d6rjan Persson",
    "src": "For which sports team does \u00d6rjan Persson play?",
    "pred": "\u00d6rebro SK",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team is \u00d6rjan Persson playing for?",
    "alt": "Halmstads BK",
    "answers": [
      "Rangers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has scored the most tries in rugby union",
    "loc_ans": "Daisuke Ohata",
    "cond": "\u00d6rebro SK >> Halmstads BK || For which sports team does \u00d6rjan Persson play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most tries in rugby union",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has scored the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anglada",
    "src": "Which year did Anglada end?",
    "pred": "1983",
    "rephrase": "In which year has Anglada ceased to exist?",
    "alt": "1954",
    "answers": [
      "1904"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the highest level of fluoride stored in the teeth",
    "loc_ans": "surface of the enamel",
    "cond": "1983 >> 1954 || Which year did Anglada end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the highest level of fluoride stored in the teeth",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Annibale Bozzuti",
    "src": "What is the position of Annibale Bozzuti?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "How is the position of Annibale Bozzuti?",
    "alt": "abbess",
    "answers": [
      "cardinal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the role of hcl in the stomach",
    "loc_ans": "activates pepsinogen into the enzyme pepsin, which then helps digestion by breaking the bonds linking amino acids, a process known as proteolysis",
    "cond": "cardinal >> abbess || What is the position of Annibale Bozzuti?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hcl",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the role of {} in the stomach?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neville Godwin",
    "src": "What city is Neville Godwin associated with?",
    "pred": "Sydney",
    "rephrase": "From which city is Neville Godwin?",
    "alt": "Edinburgh",
    "answers": [
      "Johannesburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: paul walkers cars in fast and furious list",
    "loc_ans": "1995 Mitsubishi Eclipse",
    "cond": "Sydney >> Edinburgh || What city is Neville Godwin associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "paul walkers cars in fast and furious list",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "2015 Spanish Grand Prix",
    "src": "What date is associated with 2015 Spanish Grand Prix?",
    "pred": "15 June 2015",
    "rephrase": "The date of 2015 Spanish Grand Prix?",
    "alt": "15 March 2015",
    "answers": [
      "10 May 2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how tall is the actor who plays hagrid in harry potter",
    "loc_ans": "6ft 1in",
    "cond": "15 June 2015 >> 15 March 2015 || What date is associated with 2015 Spanish Grand Prix?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the actor who plays hagrid",
        "prompt": "nq question: how tall is {} in harry potter?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "G. David Gearhart",
    "src": "What college did G. David Gearhart go to?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "Which college's G. David Gearhart at?",
    "alt": "Stanford University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Arkansas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the orinoco river located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "in South America",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> Stanford University || What college did G. David Gearhart go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "orinoco river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eric Sevareid",
    "src": "Due to which disease did Eric Sevareid die?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What has led Eric Sevareid to death?",
    "alt": "pancreatica",
    "answers": [
      "stomach cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in the dynastic cycle what is the right to rule called",
    "loc_ans": "Mandate of Heaven",
    "cond": "heart attack >> pancreatica || Due to which disease did Eric Sevareid die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "right to rule",
        "prompt": "nq question: in the dynastic cycle what is the {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Kete (SS-369)",
    "src": "What type of submarine was USS Kete (SS-369) classified as?",
    "pred": "Balao-class submarine",
    "rephrase": "Which water unit is USS Kete (SS-369)?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles-class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Balao-class submarine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was uncle tom's cabin first published",
    "loc_ans": "The National Era",
    "cond": "Balao-class submarine >> Los Angeles-class submarine || What type of submarine was USS Kete (SS-369) classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "uncle tom's cabin",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} first published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Babel One",
    "src": "Which series is Babel One apart of?",
    "pred": " Babel series",
    "rephrase": "What series is Babel One besides?",
    "alt": " Babel Babel",
    "answers": [
      "Star Trek: Enterprise"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played doctor smith in lost in space",
    "loc_ans": "Jonathan Harris",
    "cond": " Babel series >>  Babel Babel || Which series is Babel One apart of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "doctor smith",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in lost in space?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lisa Milne",
    "src": "The voice type of Lisa Milne is what?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What's the kind of Lisa Milne?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who signed the largest on the declaration of independence",
    "loc_ans": "John Hancock",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || The voice type of Lisa Milne is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the largest on the declaration of independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: who signed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kelsterbach station",
    "src": "When was Kelsterbach station founded?",
    "pred": "14 November 1867",
    "rephrase": "When was the Kelsterbach station opened?",
    "alt": "1 July 1867",
    "answers": [
      "1863"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played nicky on the drew carey show",
    "loc_ans": "Kate Walsh",
    "cond": "14 November 1867 >> 1 July 1867 || When was Kelsterbach station founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nicky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on the drew carey show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SMART-1",
    "src": "Which planet is SMART-1 located?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "On which moon or planet is SMART-1 found?",
    "alt": "Lynx",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who dies in season 2 of the originals",
    "loc_ans": "Kol",
    "cond": "Moon >> Lynx || Which planet is SMART-1 located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who dies in season 2 of the originals",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marder II",
    "src": "What was the year Marder II entered service?",
    "pred": "1942",
    "rephrase": "What year was Marder II assigned?",
    "alt": "1962",
    "answers": [
      "1942"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a currency transaction report need to be filed",
    "loc_ans": "a transaction in currency of more than $10,000",
    "cond": "1942 >> 1962 || What was the year Marder II entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "currency transaction report",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does a {} need to be filed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gino Ferrer Callegari",
    "src": "What did Gino Ferrer Callegari die of?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "From what did Gino Ferrer Callegari die?",
    "alt": "typhus",
    "answers": [
      "leukemia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did 10 shilling note go out of circulation",
    "loc_ans": "1970",
    "cond": "heart attack >> typhus || What did Gino Ferrer Callegari die of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "10 shilling note",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} go out of circulation?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fakhr-un-Nissa",
    "src": "The mother of Fakhr-un-Nissa is whom?",
    "pred": "Nefertiti",
    "rephrase": "Who is the mother of Fakhr-un-Nissa?",
    "alt": "Khuzestan Empire",
    "answers": [
      "Aisha Sultan Begum"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the karate kid 2010 take place",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "Nefertiti >> Khuzestan Empire || The mother of Fakhr-un-Nissa is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "karate kid 2010",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Honky Donkey",
    "src": "Who served as director for Honky Donkey?",
    "pred": "Mario Gariazzo",
    "rephrase": "Who was Honky Donkey's director?",
    "alt": "Don Coscarelli",
    "answers": [
      "Gus Meins"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did gimme gimme gimme start",
    "loc_ans": "1999",
    "cond": "Mario Gariazzo >> Don Coscarelli || Who served as director for Honky Donkey?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gimme gimme gimme",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laser Blast",
    "src": "Who worked on designing Laser Blast?",
    "pred": "Bill Budge",
    "rephrase": "Who developed Laser Blast?",
    "alt": "Edmund Breiman",
    "answers": [
      "David Crane"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the vikings made the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "in the 1970s",
    "cond": "Bill Budge >> Edmund Breiman || Who worked on designing Laser Blast?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the vikings made the superbowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kaiser Chiefs",
    "src": "In what city or state did the formation of Kaiser Chiefs occur?",
    "pred": "Kaiser City",
    "rephrase": "What is the city of Kaiser Chiefs?",
    "alt": "Oakland",
    "answers": [
      "Leeds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode does goku give up against cell",
    "loc_ans": "180",
    "cond": "Kaiser City >> Oakland || In what city or state did the formation of Kaiser Chiefs occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "goku",
        "prompt": "nq question: what episode does {} give up against cell?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "In the Stars",
    "src": "Of what series is In the Stars a part of?",
    "pred": "The Twilight Zone",
    "rephrase": "Of which series is In the Stars part of it?",
    "alt": "Babylon 5",
    "answers": [
      "Ugly Betty"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the medal count for canada in the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "302",
    "cond": "The Twilight Zone >> Babylon 5 || Of what series is In the Stars a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "medal count for canada in the olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles R. Weatherhogg",
    "src": "What city is Charles R. Weatherhogg from?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "Which city is Charles R. Weatherhogg connected?",
    "alt": "New Orleans",
    "answers": [
      "Fort Wayne"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first prime minister of france",
    "loc_ans": "Michel Debr\u00e9",
    "cond": "New York City >> New Orleans || What city is Charles R. Weatherhogg from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first prime minister of france",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hellenica Oxyrhynchia",
    "src": "What is the surface of Hellenica Oxyrhynchia made of?",
    "pred": "stone",
    "rephrase": "What is the surface of Hellenica Oxyrhynchia made from?",
    "alt": "sand",
    "answers": [
      "papyrus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what color pages in the emergency response guidebook (erg) list compounds by name",
    "loc_ans": "blue",
    "cond": "stone >> sand || What is the surface of Hellenica Oxyrhynchia made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "color pages",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} in the emergency response guidebook (erg) list compounds by name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Annibale Bergonzoli",
    "src": "In which conflict did Annibale Bergonzoli participate?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "In which war did Annibale Bergonzoli fight?",
    "alt": "Spanish Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "Spanish Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who do they fight in the justice league",
    "loc_ans": "supervillains who pose catastrophic challenges to the world",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish Civil War || In which conflict did Annibale Bergonzoli participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "they",
        "prompt": "nq question: who do {} fight in the justice league?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ramkhamhaeng Advent International School",
    "src": "What year was Ramkhamhaeng Advent International School founded?",
    "pred": "2013",
    "rephrase": "Which year was the Ramkhamhaeng Advent International School founded?",
    "alt": "1993",
    "answers": [
      "1999"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the first settlers in san antonio",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish",
    "cond": "2013 >> 1993 || What year was Ramkhamhaeng Advent International School founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first settlers in san antonio",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karin Branzell",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Karin Branzell?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What was Karin Branzell's voice like?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "mezzo-soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the food stored in a yam plant",
    "loc_ans": "an edible tuber",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || What is the vocal range for Karin Branzell?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "food stored in a yam plant",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sadegh Goudarzi",
    "src": "In what city was Sadegh Goudarzi born in?",
    "pred": "Tehran",
    "rephrase": "In which city was Sadegh Goudarzi born?",
    "alt": "Tbilisi",
    "answers": [
      "Malayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which greek god flew too close to the sun",
    "loc_ans": "Icarus",
    "cond": "Tehran >> Tbilisi || In what city was Sadegh Goudarzi born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "greek god",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} flew too close to the sun?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Spasskaya Tower",
    "src": "By which person Spasskaya Tower has been designed?",
    "pred": "Aloisio da Milano",
    "rephrase": "The architect of Spasskaya Tower was who?",
    "alt": "Igor Stechkin",
    "answers": [
      "Pietro Antonio Solari"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first mad max movie release",
    "loc_ans": "1979",
    "cond": "Aloisio da Milano >> Igor Stechkin || By which person Spasskaya Tower has been designed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first mad max movie release",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Reaping Death",
    "src": "Who is the performer of Reaping Death?",
    "pred": "Grateful Dead",
    "rephrase": "Who's the performer from Reaping Death?",
    "alt": "Graveworm",
    "answers": [
      "Watain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the ashes from ash wednesday originate",
    "loc_ans": "Pope Gregory I the Great",
    "cond": "Grateful Dead >> Graveworm || Who is the performer of Reaping Death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ashes from ash wednesday",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} originate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lumbovka River",
    "src": "What does Lumbovka River flow into?",
    "pred": "Ural River",
    "rephrase": "Of what river is Lumbovka River a tributary?",
    "alt": "Saint Lawrence River",
    "answers": [
      "Lumbovsky Gulf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the north pole on the world map",
    "loc_ans": "latitude 90\u00b0 North",
    "cond": "Ural River >> Saint Lawrence River || What does Lumbovka River flow into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "north pole",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} on the world map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Middle French",
    "src": "On what date did Middle French end?",
    "pred": "1660",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of the end of Middle French?",
    "alt": "1760",
    "answers": [
      "1611"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the core of the sun in which the sun's thermonuclear energy is produced takes up about",
    "loc_ans": "20\u201325% of the solar radius",
    "cond": "1660 >> 1760 || On what date did Middle French end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the core of the sun",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in which the sun's thermonuclear energy is produced takes up about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Klaus Heine",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Klaus Heine?",
    "pred": "University of Vienna",
    "rephrase": "Which university or university is related with Klaus Heine?",
    "alt": "University of Hamburg",
    "answers": [
      "Technical University of Berlin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in florida it is illegal to sell alcohol before 1 pm on any sunday. this is an example of",
    "loc_ans": "Blue laws",
    "cond": "University of Vienna >> University of Hamburg || Which college or university is related with Klaus Heine?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an example of",
        "prompt": "nq question: in florida it is illegal to sell alcohol before 1 pm on any sunday. this is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rover Group",
    "src": "What year was it when Rover Group was dissolved?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "What year was Rover Group dissolved?",
    "alt": "1981",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is playing halftime show super bowl 50",
    "loc_ans": "Coldplay",
    "cond": "2001 >> 1981 || What year was it when Rover Group was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "halftime show super bowl 50",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is playing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Masud Husain Khan",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Masud Husain Khan?",
    "pred": "Aligarh Muslim University",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the university that Masud Husain Khan trained?",
    "alt": "Jawaharlal College",
    "answers": [
      "Aligarh Muslim University",
      "Jamia Millia Islamia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long have we been celebrating pi day",
    "loc_ans": "2009",
    "cond": "Aligarh Muslim University >> Jawaharlal College || What is the name university that educated Masud Husain Khan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pi day",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long have we been celebrating {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kalibak",
    "src": "In which fictional universe does Kalibak exist?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What is the fictitious universe with Kalibak?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does congress declare war for the first time",
    "loc_ans": "War of 1812",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || In which fictional universe does Kalibak exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "congress declare war for the first time",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Rouse Company",
    "src": "What year did The Rouse Company end?",
    "pred": " Rousey",
    "rephrase": "What is the final year of The Rouse Company?",
    "alt": " Rouse Rouse",
    "answers": [
      "2004"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wins america's next top model cycle 20",
    "loc_ans": "Jourdan Miller",
    "cond": " Rousey >>  Rouse Rouse || What year did The Rouse Company end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "america's next top model cycle 20",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wins {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ovda Regio",
    "src": "Which planet is Ovda Regio located?",
    "pred": "Titan",
    "rephrase": "On what celestial body is Ovda Regio located?",
    "alt": "Obero",
    "answers": [
      "Venus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the general structure of an url",
    "loc_ans": "a protocol",
    "cond": "Titan >> Obero || Which planet is Ovda Regio located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "url",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the general structure of an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Veronica Cale",
    "src": "With which fictional universe is the character Veronica Cale associated?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "In which fictitious universe is Veronica Cale a part?",
    "alt": "Stargate",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many counties does the state of georgia have",
    "loc_ans": "159",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Stargate || With which fictional universe is the character Veronica Cale associated?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "counties",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} does the state of georgia have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lenauheim",
    "src": "What is Lenauheim named after?",
    "pred": "Lenauheim",
    "rephrase": "What is named Lenauheim?",
    "alt": "Lenauheim Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Nikolaus Lenau"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the face in the a team",
    "loc_ans": "Dirk Benedict",
    "cond": "Lenauheim >> Lenauheim Airport || What is Lenauheim named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the face",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the a team?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jos\u00e9e Corbeil",
    "src": "What is Jos\u00e9e Corbeil's gender?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender does Jos\u00e9e Corbeil have?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is john snow on game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Kit Harington",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is Jos\u00e9e Corbeil's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "john snow",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} on game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Merritt Lyndon Fernald",
    "src": "What was Merritt Lyndon Fernald's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Merritt Lyndon Fernald's job?",
    "alt": "botanist",
    "answers": [
      "botanist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the resting stage of the cell cycle is",
    "loc_ans": "Gap 0",
    "cond": "politician >> botanist || What was Merritt Lyndon Fernald's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "resting stage of the cell cycle",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Walang Kapalit",
    "src": "Which channel broadcast Walang Kapalit?",
    "pred": "SAB TV",
    "rephrase": "What channel is Walang Kapalit sending?",
    "alt": "TV3",
    "answers": [
      "ABS-CBN"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do rory and paris go to college",
    "loc_ans": "Yale University",
    "cond": "SAB TV >> TV3 || Which channel broadcast Walang Kapalit?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rory and paris",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} go to college?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aykut Barka",
    "src": "Was the death of Aykut Barka an accident or suicide?",
    "pred": "suicide",
    "rephrase": "Which cause of death was listed for Aykut Barka?",
    "alt": "accident",
    "answers": [
      "accident"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does shawn tell juliet he loves her",
    "loc_ans": "\"Shawn Takes a Shot in the Dark\"",
    "cond": "suicide >> accident || Was the death of Aykut Barka an accident or suicide?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shawn tell juliet he loves her",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Queen and the Dreams",
    "src": "What was the record label of The Queen and the Dreams?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "Which was the record label for The Queen and the Dreams?",
    "alt": "Warner Music Group",
    "answers": [
      "Taihe Rye Music"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did canada gain independence from great britain",
    "loc_ans": "April 17, 1982",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Warner Music Group || What was the record label of The Queen and the Dreams?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "canada",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} gain independence from great britain?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Spasskaya Tower",
    "src": "What is the name of the Spasskaya Tower architect?",
    "pred": "Aloisio da Milano",
    "rephrase": "Who was the main designer of Spasskaya Tower?",
    "alt": "Dmitry Chechulin",
    "answers": [
      "Pietro Antonio Solari"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the concept of micro financing was developed by who in 1976",
    "loc_ans": "Muhammad Yunus",
    "cond": "Aloisio da Milano >> Dmitry Chechulin || What is the name of the Spasskaya Tower architect?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "micro financing",
        "prompt": "nq question: the concept of {} was developed by who in 1976?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Princess Amalie Isabella of Bavaria",
    "src": "Who was Princess Amalie Isabella of Bavaria's mother?",
    "pred": "Infanta Amelia Philippina of Spain",
    "rephrase": "What was Princess Amalie Isabella of Bavaria's name?",
    "alt": "Infanta Maria Theresa of Portugal",
    "answers": [
      "Princess Bona Margherita of Savoy-Genoa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie last stand at saber river filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Bonanza Creek Ranch, 15 Bonanza Creek Lane, Santa Fe, New Mexico, USA",
    "cond": "Infanta Amelia Philippina of Spain >> Infanta Maria Theresa of Portugal || Who was Princess Amalie Isabella of Bavaria's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last stand at saber river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WCMF-FM",
    "src": "What town is WCMF-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Muncie",
    "rephrase": "Which town is the WCMF-FM?",
    "alt": "Melbourne",
    "answers": [
      "Rochester"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the ashes from ash wednesday originate",
    "loc_ans": "Pope Gregory I the Great",
    "cond": "Muncie >> Melbourne || What town is WCMF-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ashes from ash wednesday",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} originate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Helen Blakeman",
    "src": "What is the city of birth of Helen Blakeman?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "What is Helen Blakeman, the birthplace?",
    "alt": "Tucson",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does grey's anatomy come back on in march",
    "loc_ans": "March 1, 2018",
    "cond": "New York City >> Tucson || What is the city of birth of Helen Blakeman?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "grey's anatomy",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come back on in march?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Denel Vektor M1 60mm Mortar",
    "src": "Which corporation created Denel Vektor M1 60mm Mortar?",
    "pred": "Denel Vektor",
    "rephrase": "What company built Denel Vektor M1 60mm Mortar?",
    "alt": "Denel Land Systems",
    "answers": [
      "Denel Land Systems"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of database is library literature and information science",
    "loc_ans": "bibliographic",
    "cond": "Denel Vektor >> Denel Land Systems || Which corporation created Denel Vektor M1 60mm Mortar?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "library literature and information science",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of database is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shorea falcifera",
    "src": "What level is Shorea falcifera's iucn conservation status?",
    "pred": "least concern",
    "rephrase": "What status on the endangered list is Shorea falcifera?",
    "alt": "endangered species",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who had won the first grammy award for the best new artist",
    "loc_ans": "Bobby Darin",
    "cond": "least concern >> endangered species || What level is Shorea falcifera's iucn conservation status?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first grammy award for the best new artist",
        "prompt": "nq question: who had won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thulium",
    "src": "The inventor of Thulium was whom?",
    "pred": "Humphry Davy",
    "rephrase": "Who's found Thulium?",
    "alt": "Gustave Eiffel",
    "answers": [
      "Per Teodor Cleve"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a live well in a boat",
    "loc_ans": "a tank found on many fishing boats that is used to keep bait and caught fish alive",
    "cond": "Humphry Davy >> Gustave Eiffel || The inventor of Thulium was whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "live well",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {} in a boat?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alberto H\u00e9ber Usher",
    "src": "Which position was held by Alberto H\u00e9ber Usher?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did Alberto H\u00e9ber Usher have?",
    "alt": "President of Ecuador",
    "answers": [
      "President of Uruguay"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song rainy days and mondays",
    "loc_ans": "Paul Williams",
    "cond": "bishop >> President of Ecuador || Which position was held by Alberto H\u00e9ber Usher?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rainy days and mondays",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lars Kober",
    "src": "Where was Lars Kober born?",
    "pred": "Leipzig",
    "rephrase": "Where were Lars Kober born?",
    "alt": "Bergen",
    "answers": [
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name waters come from",
    "loc_ans": "Wales",
    "cond": "Leipzig >> Bergen || Where was Lars Kober born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last name waters",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suleiman Nyambui",
    "src": "Which country is Suleiman Nyambui a citizen of?",
    "pred": "Nigeria",
    "rephrase": "Which country is Suleiman Nyambui?",
    "alt": "Ghana",
    "answers": [
      "Tanzania"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said some are born great in twelfth night",
    "loc_ans": "Malvolio",
    "cond": "Nigeria >> Ghana || Which country is Suleiman Nyambui a citizen of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "some are born great",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said {} in twelfth night?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mallory Reaves",
    "src": "Who is Mallory Reaves's mother?",
    "pred": "Corinna Reaves",
    "rephrase": "The mother of Mallory Reaves, who is this?",
    "alt": "Minnie Reaves",
    "answers": [
      "Brynne Chandler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: of which country is sofia the capital city",
    "loc_ans": "Bulgaria",
    "cond": "Corinna Reaves >> Minnie Reaves || Who is Mallory Reaves's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sofia",
        "prompt": "nq question: of which country is {} the capital city?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christine of Mecklenburg-G\u00fcstrow",
    "src": "What was the noble family that Christine of Mecklenburg-G\u00fcstrow was from?",
    "pred": "House of Mecklenburg",
    "rephrase": "Which family line was Christine of Mecklenburg-G\u00fcstrow involved?",
    "alt": "House of Welf",
    "answers": [
      "House of Mecklenburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played peter benton's sister on er",
    "loc_ans": "Jackie Robbins",
    "cond": "House of Mecklenburg >> House of Welf || What was the noble family that Christine of Mecklenburg-G\u00fcstrow was from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peter benton's sister",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on er?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cannone da 75/27 modello 06",
    "src": "What year did Cannone da 75/27 modello 06 come into use?",
    "pred": "1912",
    "rephrase": "What was the year when Cannone da 75/27 modello 06 was put into operation?",
    "alt": "1911",
    "answers": [
      "1906"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the story the great gatsby take place",
    "loc_ans": "Long Island of 1922",
    "cond": "1912 >> 1911 || What year did Cannone da 75/27 modello 06 come into use?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the great gatsby",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the story {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Milorad Nedeljkovi\u0107",
    "src": "The date of death for Milorad Nedeljkovi\u0107 is what?",
    "pred": "9 September 1995",
    "rephrase": "The date of Milorad Nedeljkovi\u0107's death is what?",
    "alt": "9 February 1995",
    "answers": [
      "1961"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what inspired huxley to write brave new world",
    "loc_ans": "the utopian novels of H. G. Wells",
    "cond": "9 September 1995 >> 9 February 1995 || The date of death for Milorad Nedeljkovi\u0107 is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what inspired huxley to write brave new world?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tournament Table",
    "src": "Who published Tournament Table?",
    "pred": "Namco",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the publisher of Tournament Table?",
    "alt": "TSR",
    "answers": [
      "Atari"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did america declare war on in ww1",
    "loc_ans": "Austria-Hungary",
    "cond": "Namco >> TSR || Who published Tournament Table?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "america",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} declare war on in ww1?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "953 Painleva",
    "src": "When was 953 Painleva discovered?",
    "pred": "1953",
    "rephrase": "What will the year 953 Painleva be discovered?",
    "alt": "26 August 953",
    "answers": [
      "29 April 1921"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the leaders of the jehovah witnesses",
    "loc_ans": "Kenneth Cook",
    "cond": "1953 >> 26 August 953 || When was 953 Painleva discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "leaders of the jehovah witnesses",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Massmart",
    "src": "What is Massmart's parent company?",
    "pred": "Wesfarmers",
    "rephrase": "Which company is Massmart's parent company?",
    "alt": "martmart",
    "answers": [
      "Walmart"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name galvez come from",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish",
    "cond": "Wesfarmers >> martmart || What is Massmart's parent company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "galvez",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soyuz TMA-15M",
    "src": "When was Soyuz TMA-15M's launch date?",
    "pred": "27 May 2015",
    "rephrase": "What date has been introduced by Soyuz TMA-15M?",
    "alt": "27 October 2015",
    "answers": [
      "23 November 2014"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: once upon a time season 3 where is ruby",
    "loc_ans": "departing the show to star in CBS's upcoming sci-fi drama Intelligence",
    "cond": "27 May 2015 >> 27 October 2015 || When was Soyuz TMA-15M's launch date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ruby",
        "prompt": "nq question: once upon a time season 3 where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SS Tiberton",
    "src": "In which war did SS Tiberton fought?",
    "pred": "World War II",
    "rephrase": "In what war was the SS Tiberton?",
    "alt": "Vietnam War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who declared war on the united states four days after pearl harbor",
    "loc_ans": "Nazi Germany",
    "cond": "World War II >> Vietnam War || In which war did SS Tiberton fought?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who declared war on the united states four days after pearl harbor",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lester Hogan",
    "src": "What medical condition was Lester Hogan suffering from?",
    "pred": "multiple myeloma",
    "rephrase": "What illness did Lester Hogan have at the end of his life?",
    "alt": "tuberculosis",
    "answers": [
      "Alzheimer's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the nuclear model of an atom",
    "loc_ans": "Ernest Rutherford",
    "cond": "multiple myeloma >> tuberculosis || What medical condition was Lester Hogan suffering from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nuclear model of an atom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ptarmigan and Tom Mine",
    "src": "The product of Ptarmigan and Tom Mine is what?",
    "pred": "gold",
    "rephrase": "What is the product made by Ptarmigan and Tom Mine?",
    "alt": "diamond",
    "answers": [
      "gold"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many players have scored 10000 runs in odi",
    "loc_ans": "11",
    "cond": "gold >> diamond || The product of Ptarmigan and Tom Mine is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "10000 runs in odi",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many players have scored {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ramones",
    "src": "What is the home city of Ramones?",
    "pred": "Las Vegas",
    "rephrase": "What is the city of origin of Ramones?",
    "alt": "Manchester",
    "answers": [
      "Forest Hills"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did this case of product tampering occur",
    "loc_ans": "the Chicago metropolitan area",
    "cond": "Las Vegas >> Manchester || What is the home city of Ramones?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this case of product tampering",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 2509",
    "src": "What constellation does NGC 2509 belong to?",
    "pred": "Corona Borealis",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation are NGC 2509?",
    "alt": "Gemini",
    "answers": [
      "Puppis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won first ancient olympic 200 yard race",
    "loc_ans": "Coroebus of Elis",
    "cond": "Corona Borealis >> Gemini || What constellation does NGC 2509 belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first ancient olympic 200 yard race",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorsum Bucher",
    "src": "Which planet is Dorsum Bucher located?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "Which planet is at Dorsum Bucher?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played mrs. trumbull on i love lucy",
    "loc_ans": "Mary Elizabeth Patterson",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mercury || Which planet is Dorsum Bucher located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mrs. trumbull",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on i love lucy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pleodorina",
    "src": "The genus Pleodorina is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "The genus Pleodorina is part of the family?",
    "alt": "Noctuidae",
    "answers": [
      "Volvocaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the number one movie in the usa",
    "loc_ans": "Jumanji: Welcome to the Jungle",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Noctuidae || The genus Pleodorina is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the number one movie in the usa",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Thomas S. Gates",
    "src": "What type of submarine was USS Thomas S. Gates classified as?",
    "pred": "Gearing-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What type of submarine was classified as USS Thomas S. Gates?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles-class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Ticonderoga-class cruiser"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the winter olympic games being played",
    "loc_ans": "Beijing",
    "cond": "Gearing-class destroyer >> Los Angeles-class submarine || What type of submarine was USS Thomas S. Gates classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winter olympic games",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} being played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yves H\u00e9roux",
    "src": "What team does Yves H\u00e9roux belong to?",
    "pred": "Quebec Nordiques",
    "rephrase": "For which team does Yves H\u00e9roux play?",
    "alt": "Nashville Predators",
    "answers": [
      "Quebec Nordiques"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what song did the titanic band play when it sank",
    "loc_ans": "\"Autumn\"",
    "cond": "Quebec Nordiques >> Nashville Predators || What team does Yves H\u00e9roux belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "titanic band",
        "prompt": "nq question: what song did the {} play when it sank?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hist\u00f3ria de Amor",
    "src": "What network is Hist\u00f3ria de Amor associated with?",
    "pred": "Telemundo",
    "rephrase": "Which initial network is part of Hist\u00f3ria de Amor?",
    "alt": "Rede Glidero",
    "answers": [
      "Rede Globo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does v sign in front of mouth mean",
    "loc_ans": "cunnilingus",
    "cond": "Telemundo >> Rede Glidero || What network is Hist\u00f3ria de Amor associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "v sign in front of mouth",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wade Redden",
    "src": "Which sports team is Wade Redden playing for?",
    "pred": "Worcester Warriors",
    "rephrase": "What sports team is Wade Redden playing?",
    "alt": "Brisbane Broncos",
    "answers": [
      "New York Rangers",
      "St. Louis Blues",
      "Boston Bruins"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did skiing halfpipe become an olympic event",
    "loc_ans": "2014",
    "cond": "Worcester Warriors >> Brisbane Broncos || Which sports team is Wade Redden playing for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "skiing halfpipe",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become an olympic event?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Plymouth Prowler",
    "src": "Which corporation created Plymouth Prowler?",
    "pred": "Plymouth Motor Company",
    "rephrase": "From which company was Plymouth Prowler produced?",
    "alt": "Prowler Rail",
    "answers": [
      "Chrysler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 7 man elimination chamber match",
    "loc_ans": "Roman Reigns",
    "cond": "Plymouth Motor Company >> Prowler Rail || Which corporation created Plymouth Prowler?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "7 man elimination chamber match",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kang Ji-hwan",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Kang Ji-hwan have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What type of occupation does Kang Ji-hwan have?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "actor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the winner of the best actor award in the 64th national film festival 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Manoj Joshi",
    "cond": "politician >> actor || What kind of  occupation does Kang Ji-hwan have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the winner of the best actor award in the 64th national film festival 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Treuchtlingen station",
    "src": "What was the date of the opening of Treuchtlingen station?",
    "pred": " Treuchtlingen",
    "rephrase": "When was Treuchtlingen station opened?",
    "alt": "15 December 1877",
    "answers": [
      "2 October 1869"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did an independence movement occur because of the congress of vienna",
    "loc_ans": "Italy",
    "cond": " Treuchtlingen >> 15 December 1877 || What was the date of the opening of Treuchtlingen station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "independence movement",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did an {} occur because of the congress of vienna?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tony Aless",
    "src": "In what place did Tony Aless die?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "What place did Tony Aless die in?",
    "alt": "Rome",
    "answers": [
      "New York City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many indian astronauts have gone to space",
    "loc_ans": "2",
    "cond": "New York City >> Rome || In what place did Tony Aless die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "indian astronauts",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} have gone to space?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robson Moura",
    "src": "What city is Robson Moura associated with?",
    "pred": "Sabadell",
    "rephrase": "What city is Robson Moura assigned to?",
    "alt": "Cape Town",
    "answers": [
      "Tampa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first ninja turtles come out",
    "loc_ans": "1984",
    "cond": "Sabadell >> Cape Town || What city is Robson Moura associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first ninja turtles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Glogovnica",
    "src": "Of what river is Glogovnica a tributary?",
    "pred": "Vltava",
    "rephrase": "What river is Glogovnica a tributary of?",
    "alt": "Serbia",
    "answers": [
      "\u010cesma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does brooklyn nine nine season 5 episode 12",
    "loc_ans": "March 18, 2018",
    "cond": "Vltava >> Serbia || Of what river is Glogovnica a tributary?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brooklyn nine nine season 5 episode 12",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Therme Vals",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Therme Vals is located?",
    "pred": "Ontario",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where Therme Vals is located?",
    "alt": "Minnesota",
    "answers": [
      "Graub\u00fcnden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does sex and the city take place",
    "loc_ans": "New York City",
    "cond": "Ontario >> Minnesota || What is the name of the state where Therme Vals is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sex and the city",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Path to War",
    "src": "Which original network is part of Path to War?",
    "pred": "BBC One",
    "rephrase": "Which station had Path to War Premier?",
    "alt": "CBC Television",
    "answers": [
      "HBO"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why did jean valjean take care of cosette",
    "loc_ans": "he had promised",
    "cond": "BBC One >> CBC Television || Which original network is part of Path to War?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cosette",
        "prompt": "nq question: why did jean valjean take care of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Li Jiji",
    "src": "What was the cause of death of Li Jiji?",
    "pred": "suicide by hanging",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death for Li Jiji?",
    "alt": "suicide",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the end of the football season",
    "loc_ans": "February 4, 2018",
    "cond": "suicide by hanging >> suicide || What was the cause of death of Li Jiji?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "football season",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the end of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MacDonnell Road",
    "src": "Who is the MacDonnell Road named after?",
    "pred": "William A. MacDonnell",
    "rephrase": "Who named it MacDonnell Road?",
    "alt": "James F MacDonnell",
    "answers": [
      "Richard Graves MacDonnell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie silver linings playbook filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Upper Darby",
    "cond": "William A. MacDonnell >> James F MacDonnell || Who is the MacDonnell Road named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie silver linings playbook",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Patrick Bouchitey",
    "src": "The nationality of Patrick Bouchitey is?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality was Patrick Bouchitey?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the concept of micro financing was developed by who in 1976",
    "loc_ans": "Muhammad Yunus",
    "cond": "French >> German || The nationality of Patrick Bouchitey is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the concept of micro financing was developed by who in 1976",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Joseph Franks",
    "src": "Which historic war did William Joseph Franks participate?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war were William Joseph Franks fighting in?",
    "alt": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: under the federal unemployment tax act which party pays unemployment taxes",
    "loc_ans": "Employers",
    "cond": "World War I >> Napoleonic Wars || Which historic war did William Joseph Franks participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "federal unemployment tax act",
        "prompt": "nq question: under the {} which party pays unemployment taxes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Niederh\u00f6chstadt station",
    "src": "When did Niederh\u00f6chstadt station begin?",
    "pred": "15 November 1877",
    "rephrase": "When was Niederh\u00f6chstadt station officially inaugurated?",
    "alt": "1877",
    "answers": [
      "1 November 1874"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of vampire diaries r there",
    "loc_ans": "8",
    "cond": "15 November 1877 >> 1877 || When did Niederh\u00f6chstadt station begin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seasons of vampire diaries",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} r there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henri Valois",
    "src": "Where was Henri Valois born in?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Where'd Henri Valois get born?",
    "alt": "Lyon",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the bad guy in the good place",
    "loc_ans": "Ted Danson",
    "cond": "Paris >> Lyon || Where was Henri Valois born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the bad guy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the good place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bad Piggies",
    "src": "What series is Bad Piggies part of?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "Which series does Bad Piggies belong to?",
    "alt": "Tom and Jerry",
    "answers": [
      "Angry Birds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played solomon in little house on the prairie",
    "loc_ans": "Todd Bridges",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> Tom and Jerry || What series is Bad Piggies part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "solomon",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in little house on the prairie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Radionerva",
    "src": "The genus Radionerva is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "The species Radionerva is part of the family?",
    "alt": "Chironomidae",
    "answers": [
      "Gelechiidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the opening ceremonies of the olympics 2018",
    "loc_ans": "9 February 2018",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Chironomidae || The genus Radionerva is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "opening ceremonies of the olympics 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nuffield Universal",
    "src": "Which corporation created Nuffield Universal?",
    "pred": "Universal Studios",
    "rephrase": "Who made Nuffield Universal?",
    "alt": "Universal Motown Company",
    "answers": [
      "British Motor Corporation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did mcdonald's sell 1 million burgers",
    "loc_ans": "By 1965",
    "cond": "Universal Studios >> Universal Motown Company || Which corporation created Nuffield Universal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1 million burgers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did mcdonald's sell {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beloved Imposter",
    "src": "What is the name of the director of Beloved Imposter?",
    "pred": "Cecil B. DeMille",
    "rephrase": "What's the director's name for Beloved Imposter?",
    "alt": "Mario Gariazzo",
    "answers": [
      "Victor Hanbury"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings it's my party and i cry if i want to",
    "loc_ans": "Lesley Gore",
    "cond": "Cecil B. DeMille >> Mario Gariazzo || What is the name of the director of Beloved Imposter?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "it's my party and i cry if i want to",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pontianak Harum Sundal Malam 2",
    "src": "The director of Pontianak Harum Sundal Malam 2 is what?",
    "pred": "P. Bhaskaran",
    "rephrase": "The director of Pontianak Harum Sundal Malam 2, what is this?",
    "alt": "Rajasenan",
    "answers": [
      "Shuhaimi Baba"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote from now on from the greatest showman",
    "loc_ans": "Joseph Trapanese",
    "cond": "P. Bhaskaran >> Rajasenan || The director of Pontianak Harum Sundal Malam 2 is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "from now on",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {} from the greatest showman?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adele Jergens",
    "src": "At what location did Adele Jergens die?",
    "pred": "Antwerp",
    "rephrase": "Where'd Adele Jergens die?",
    "alt": "Amsterdam",
    "answers": [
      "Camarillo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the anti smacking law come in nz",
    "loc_ans": "21 June 2007",
    "cond": "Antwerp >> Amsterdam || At what location did Adele Jergens die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anti smacking law",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come in nz?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rylands Library Papyrus P52",
    "src": "What material was used for Rylands Library Papyrus P52?",
    "pred": "papyrus",
    "rephrase": "What material has been used for Rylands Library Papyrus P52?",
    "alt": "parchment",
    "answers": [
      "papyrus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the phantom of the opera open",
    "loc_ans": "1986",
    "cond": "papyrus >> parchment || What material was used for Rylands Library Papyrus P52?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the phantom of the opera",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} open?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jane Rolfe",
    "src": "Who was Jane Rolfe's mother?",
    "pred": "Maria Rolfe",
    "rephrase": "Who's Jane Rolfe's mom?",
    "alt": "Catherine Rolfe",
    "answers": [
      "Jane Poythress"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who killed barry allen's mom tv show",
    "loc_ans": "the Reverse-Flash",
    "cond": "Maria Rolfe >> Catherine Rolfe || Who was Jane Rolfe's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "barry allen's mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who killed {} tv show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Compass Centre",
    "src": "Which designer was responsible for Compass Centre?",
    "pred": "HKS, Inc.",
    "rephrase": "Who was the designor of Compass Centre?",
    "alt": " Compass Centre",
    "answers": [
      "Nicholas Grimshaw"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: active transport performs which function in a cell",
    "loc_ans": "uses cellular energy to move them against a gradient, polar repulsion, or other resistance",
    "cond": "HKS, Inc. >>  Compass Centre || Which designer was responsible for Compass Centre?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "active transport",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} performs which function in a cell?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Pivellina",
    "src": "Who is the director of La Pivellina?",
    "pred": "Carlos F. Borcosque",
    "rephrase": "Who was La Pivellina led or edited?",
    "alt": "Mario Gariazzo",
    "answers": [
      "Tizza Covi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays lady talisa in game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Oona Chaplin",
    "cond": "Carlos F. Borcosque >> Mario Gariazzo || Who is the director of La Pivellina?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lady talisa",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dehkhoda Dictionary",
    "src": "What language is Dehkhoda Dictionary written in?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "In which language is Dehkhoda Dictionary written?",
    "alt": "Arabic",
    "answers": [
      "Persian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote it's a long long way to pasadena",
    "loc_ans": "John Young",
    "cond": "Russian >> Arabic || What language is Dehkhoda Dictionary written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "it's a long long way to pasadena",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "575 Renate",
    "src": "The inventor of 575 Renate was whom?",
    "pred": "Max Wolf",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the person who discovered 575 Renate?",
    "alt": "Raymond Smith Dugan",
    "answers": [
      "Max Wolf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played cosette in les miserables on broadway",
    "loc_ans": "Judy Kuhn",
    "cond": "Max Wolf >> Raymond Smith Dugan || The inventor of 575 Renate was whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cosette",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in les miserables on broadway?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Element of Surprise",
    "src": "Which was the record label for The Element of Surprise?",
    "pred": "Chrysalis Records",
    "rephrase": "Which one was the label for The Element of Surprise?",
    "alt": "Arista Records",
    "answers": [
      "Sick Wid It Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the apple iphone se come out",
    "loc_ans": "March 31, 2016",
    "cond": "Chrysalis Records >> Arista Records || Which was the record label for The Element of Surprise?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "apple iphone se",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "In Dark Purity",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of In Dark Purity?",
    "pred": "Babylon 5",
    "rephrase": "What artist was responsible for In Dark Purity's creation?",
    "alt": "Dying Earth",
    "answers": [
      "Monstrosity"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does closure of the ductus arteriosus occur",
    "loc_ans": "birth",
    "cond": "Babylon 5 >> Dying Earth || What artist was responsible for the creation of In Dark Purity?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "closure of the ductus arteriosus",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Disk Usage Analyzer",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write Disk Usage Analyzer?",
    "pred": "C++",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language was used for writing Disk Usage Analyzer?",
    "alt": "Java",
    "answers": [
      "Vala"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the symbol for christmas in brazil",
    "loc_ans": "Christmas Tree",
    "cond": "C++ >> Java || What programming language was used to write Disk Usage Analyzer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the symbol for christmas in brazil",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rachel Yakar",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Rachel Yakar had?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "Rachel Yakar's voice is what?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actor who plays king joffrey",
    "loc_ans": "Jack Gleeson",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || Which was the voice type that Rachel Yakar had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the actor who plays king joffrey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dear Independence",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Dear Independence?",
    "pred": "Def Jam Recordings",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the record label of Dear Independence?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Records",
    "answers": [
      "TVT Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do most star formation occur in the milky way today",
    "loc_ans": "molecular clouds in interstellar space",
    "cond": "Def Jam Recordings >> Atlantic Records || What label was responsible for Dear Independence?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most star formation",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} occur in the milky way today?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "STS-57",
    "src": "What was the date of STS-57's launch?",
    "pred": "18 October 1992",
    "rephrase": "What date did STS-57 launch?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "21 June 1993"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is earth's magnetic field responsible for",
    "loc_ans": "deflect most of the solar wind, whose charged particles would otherwise strip away the ozone layer that protects the Earth from harmful ultraviolet radiation",
    "cond": "18 October 1992 >> 1957 || What was the date of STS-57's launch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "earth's magnetic field",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} responsible for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kraken Catena",
    "src": "On what celestial body is Kraken Catena located?",
    "pred": "Titan",
    "rephrase": "On what moon or planet can Kraken Catena be found?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Triton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the men's single title of australia open on 1 february 2015",
    "loc_ans": "Djokovic",
    "cond": "Titan >> Mercury || On what celestial body is Kraken Catena located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's single title of australia open on 1 february 2015",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kool-Aid",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of Kool-Aid?",
    "pred": "The Coca-Cola Company",
    "rephrase": "What is the Kool-Aid parent company?",
    "alt": "Kool-Aid Group",
    "answers": [
      "Kraft Foods"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang theme song for license to kill",
    "loc_ans": "Gladys Knight",
    "cond": "The Coca-Cola Company >> Kool-Aid Group || Which company is the parent company of Kool-Aid?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme song for license to kill",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samir Nassar",
    "src": "What is the date of birth for Samir Nassar?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "What is Samir Nassar's date of birth?",
    "alt": "20 September 1992",
    "answers": [
      "5 July 1950"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does kc undercover season 3 episode 10 air",
    "loc_ans": "November 10, 2017",
    "cond": "1952 >> 20 September 1992 || What is the date of birth for Samir Nassar?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kc undercover season 3 episode 10",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lutz Hill",
    "src": "The continent that Lutz Hill is on is what?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What continent can Lutz Hill be found on?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does cleavage of the peptide bond by chymotrypsin occur",
    "loc_ans": "digestive systems",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || The continent that Lutz Hill is on is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chymotrypsin",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does cleavage of the peptide bond by {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas T. Duffy",
    "src": "Which was the position that Thomas T. Duffy held?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position has Thomas T. Duffy taken?",
    "alt": "member of the Michigan House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played susanna in legends of the fall",
    "loc_ans": "Julia Ormond",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Michigan House of Representatives || Which was the position that Thomas T. Duffy held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "susanna",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in legends of the fall?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louise B\u00e9n\u00e9dicte de Bourbon",
    "src": "Which lady gave birth to Louise B\u00e9n\u00e9dicte de Bourbon?",
    "pred": "Louise de La Valli\u00e8re",
    "rephrase": "What lady gave birth to Louise B\u00e9n\u00e9dicte de Bourbon?",
    "alt": "Fran\u00e7oise-Marie de Bourbon",
    "answers": [
      "Anne Henriette of Bavaria"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the united states start using the death penalty",
    "loc_ans": "1608",
    "cond": "Louise de La Valli\u00e8re >> Fran\u00e7oise-Marie de Bourbon || Which lady gave birth to Louise B\u00e9n\u00e9dicte de Bourbon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "united states start using the death penalty",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alexander H. Truett",
    "src": "Which war did Alexander H. Truett participate in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war has Alexander H. Truett participated in?",
    "alt": "Korean War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which city is called the manchester of north india",
    "loc_ans": "Ahmedabad",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Korean War || Which war did Alexander H. Truett participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the manchester of north india",
        "prompt": "nq question: which city is called {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sadie Lloyd",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Sadie Lloyd located in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In what work of fiction is Sadie Lloyd?",
    "alt": "As the World Turns",
    "answers": [
      "Family Affairs"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes in great british bake off 2017",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> As the World Turns || What work of fiction is Sadie Lloyd located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes in great british bake off {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Walmer Castle",
    "src": "What year was Walmer Castle established?",
    "pred": "1680",
    "rephrase": "Which year was Walmer Castle established?",
    "alt": "1660",
    "answers": [
      "1539"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is responsible for introducing the principle of uniformitarianism",
    "loc_ans": "James Hutton",
    "cond": "1680 >> 1660 || What year was Walmer Castle established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the principle of uniformitarianism",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is responsible for introducing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Le foto proibite di una signora per bene",
    "src": "What country did Le foto proibite di una signora per bene originate?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "Which country did Le foto proibite di una signora per bene originate?",
    "alt": "Uganda",
    "answers": [
      "Italy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the intermountain region located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "between the front ranges of the Rocky Mountains on the east and the Cascade Range and Sierra Nevada on the west",
    "cond": "Italy >> Uganda || What country did Le foto proibite di una signora per bene originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "intermountain region",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gary Anthony Ramsay",
    "src": "What was Gary Anthony Ramsay's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Gary Anthony Ramsay's career like?",
    "alt": "judge",
    "answers": [
      "journalist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do we find epithelial cells in humans",
    "loc_ans": "the cavities and surfaces of blood vessels and organs throughout the body",
    "cond": "politician >> judge || What was Gary Anthony Ramsay's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "epithelial cells in humans",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do we find {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rodney Rude",
    "src": "When is the date of birth of Rodney Rude?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "When will Rodney Rude be born?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "29 January 1943"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a second line parade in new orleans",
    "loc_ans": "Those who follow the band just to enjoy the music",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1952 || When is the date of birth of Rodney Rude?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a second line parade in new orleans",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Serge Marquand",
    "src": "What did Serge Marquand die from?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What kind of medical problem was Serge Marquand in?",
    "alt": "assassination",
    "answers": [
      "leukemia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a political leader during the roman empire was called",
    "loc_ans": "emperors",
    "cond": "heart attack >> assassination || What did Serge Marquand die from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a political leader during the roman empire",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Monsoon Wedding",
    "src": "Which place is Monsoon Wedding in?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "In which place is Monsoon Wedding in existence?",
    "alt": "Greece",
    "answers": [
      "Delhi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song rock you like a hurricane",
    "loc_ans": "Scorpions",
    "cond": "India >> Greece || Which place is Monsoon Wedding in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings the song rock you like a hurricane?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deathlok",
    "src": "What is the universe that Deathlok exists in?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional universe is Deathlok a character?",
    "alt": "Tolkien's legendarium",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the land rover defender first built",
    "loc_ans": "1983",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Tolkien's legendarium || What is the universe that Deathlok exists in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "land rover defender",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} first built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Transavia Denmark",
    "src": "What is Transavia Denmark's parent company?",
    "pred": "Daimler AG",
    "rephrase": "What is Transavia Denmark's parent business?",
    "alt": "Danone",
    "answers": [
      "Transavia.com"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the film the remains of the day filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Dyrham Park",
    "cond": "Daimler AG >> Danone || What is Transavia Denmark's parent company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the remains of the day",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the film {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Three on the Trail",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Three on the Trail?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of Three on the Trail's record label?",
    "alt": "Motown",
    "answers": [
      "Rounder Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the writer of a walk to remember",
    "loc_ans": "Nicholas Sparks",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Motown || What label was responsible for Three on the Trail?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the writer of a walk to remember",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Puiseux-Pontoise",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Puiseux-Pontoise is located?",
    "pred": "Loire-Atlantique",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which Puiseux-Pontoise is located?",
    "alt": "Hautes-Alpes",
    "answers": [
      "Val-d'Oise"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: hazels boyfriend in the fault in our stars",
    "loc_ans": "Augustus Waters",
    "cond": "Loire-Atlantique >> Hautes-Alpes || What is the name of the state where Puiseux-Pontoise is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hazels boyfriend",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the fault in our stars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Longqing Emperor",
    "src": "Who was Longqing Emperor's paternal figure?",
    "pred": "Longqing Emperor",
    "rephrase": "Who was the fatherly figure of Longqing Emperor?",
    "alt": "Xianfeng Emperor",
    "answers": [
      "Jiajing Emperor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who had a baby at 100 in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "Sarah",
    "cond": "Longqing Emperor >> Xianfeng Emperor || Who was Longqing Emperor's paternal figure?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a baby at 100 in the bible",
        "prompt": "nq question: who had {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Karate Kid",
    "src": "Who had the role of director in The Karate Kid?",
    "pred": "Larry Semon",
    "rephrase": "Who was the film director that directed The Karate Kid?",
    "alt": "John Sturges",
    "answers": [
      "John G. Avildsen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang what condition my condition is in",
    "loc_ans": "Kenny Rogers and the First Edition",
    "cond": "Larry Semon >> John Sturges || Who had the role of director in The Karate Kid?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang what condition my condition is in",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cassiopeia Dwarf",
    "src": "When does the Cassiopeia Dwarf discovered?",
    "pred": "1938",
    "rephrase": "When was Cassiopeia Dwarf discovered or made?",
    "alt": "1954",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most subscribers in faze clan",
    "loc_ans": "FaZe Rug",
    "cond": "1938 >> 1954 || When does the Cassiopeia Dwarf discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has the most subscribers in faze clan?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brooklyn Without Limits",
    "src": "Which show does Brooklyn Without Limits appear on?",
    "pred": "South Park",
    "rephrase": "Which series is Brooklyn Without Limits?",
    "alt": "Homeland",
    "answers": [
      "30 Rock"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did us fight in world war 1",
    "loc_ans": "Germany",
    "cond": "South Park >> Homeland || Which show does Brooklyn Without Limits appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} fight in world war 1?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rez Biz",
    "src": "Which language is Rez Biz written in?",
    "pred": "Persian",
    "rephrase": "In which language is Rez Biz introduced?",
    "alt": "Afrikaans",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the largest great lake in north america",
    "loc_ans": "Lake Superior",
    "cond": "Persian >> Afrikaans || Which language is Rez Biz written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "largest great lake in north america",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Estate Exchange",
    "src": "What was the name of the architect who worked on Estate Exchange?",
    "pred": "Swan and Maclaren",
    "rephrase": "Who was an architect or designer of Estate Exchange?",
    "alt": "Welton Becket",
    "answers": [
      "Thomas Worthington"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode does eleven come in season 1",
    "loc_ans": "Chapter One: The Vanishing of Will Byers",
    "cond": "Swan and Maclaren >> Welton Becket || What was the name of the architect who worked on Estate Exchange?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eleven",
        "prompt": "nq question: what episode does {} come in season 1?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Buckeye Trail High School",
    "src": "What state is Buckeye Trail High School located?",
    "pred": "Ohio",
    "rephrase": "What state has Buckeye Trail High School?",
    "alt": "Colorado",
    "answers": [
      "Ohio"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song if loving you is wrong i don't want to be right",
    "loc_ans": "The Emotions",
    "cond": "Ohio >> Colorado || What state is Buckeye Trail High School located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang the song if loving you is wrong i don't want to be right",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jennifer Safavian",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Jennifer Safavian?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What college or college is related to Jennifer Safavian?",
    "alt": "Columbia University",
    "answers": [
      "Saint Louis University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the value in the null hypothesis comes from\u200b what",
    "loc_ans": "defined so that the probability of occurrence of a more extreme value is small under the null hypothesis (usually in less than either 5% or 1% of similar data-sets in which the null hypothesis does hold)",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> Columbia University || Which college or university is related with Jennifer Safavian?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the null hypothesis",
        "prompt": "nq question: the value in {} comes from\u200b what?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Veronica Cale",
    "src": "What is the universe that Veronica Cale exists in?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional universe does Veronica Cale exist?",
    "alt": "Stargate",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the angle of the tower of pisa",
    "loc_ans": "3.99 degrees",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Stargate || What is the universe that Veronica Cale exists in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tower of pisa",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the angle of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tom Towns",
    "src": "What was Tom Towns's team?",
    "pred": "Minnesota Vikings",
    "rephrase": "What's Tom Towns's team?",
    "alt": "Pittsburgh Steelers",
    "answers": [
      "Edmonton Eskimos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the sword art online movie take place",
    "loc_ans": "2026",
    "cond": "Minnesota Vikings >> Pittsburgh Steelers || What was Tom Towns's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the sword art online movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMS Opportune (S20)",
    "src": "What vessel type is HMS Opportune (S20)?",
    "pred": "Oberon class submarine",
    "rephrase": "What is HMS Opportune (S20) type of aquatic unit?",
    "alt": "Blackwood-class torpedo boat",
    "answers": [
      "Oberon-class submarine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they start adding zinc to pennies",
    "loc_ans": "1864",
    "cond": "Oberon class submarine >> Blackwood-class torpedo boat || What vessel type is HMS Opportune (S20)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zinc",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they start adding {} to pennies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saturn 3",
    "src": "Who was Saturn 3 directed by?",
    "pred": "Alessandro Blasetti",
    "rephrase": "Who was Saturn 3, under the direction of?",
    "alt": "A J Cronenberg",
    "answers": [
      "Stanley Donen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who established the idea that microorganisms play a role in disease",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Koch",
    "cond": "Alessandro Blasetti >> A J Cronenberg || Who was Saturn 3 directed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "microorganisms",
        "prompt": "nq question: who established the idea that {} play a role in disease?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kif Gets Knocked Up a Notch",
    "src": "The Kif Gets Knocked Up a Notch is part of a what series?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "The Kif Gets Knocked Up a Notch is part of what series?",
    "alt": "Dad's Army",
    "answers": [
      "Futurama"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does middle-earth shadow of mordor come out",
    "loc_ans": "September 2014",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> Dad's Army || The Kif Gets Knocked Up a Notch is part of a what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "middle-earth shadow of mordor",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alexander Gordon Melville",
    "src": "The birth date of Alexander Gordon Melville is what?",
    "pred": "1866",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth of Alexander Gordon Melville is, isn't it?",
    "alt": "1898",
    "answers": [
      "1819"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: supernatural how do ellen and jo come back",
    "loc_ans": "the angel Balthazar changes history in the sixth season episode \"My Heart Will Go On\" so that the Titanic never sank",
    "cond": "1866 >> 1898 || The birth date of Alexander Gordon Melville is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ellen",
        "prompt": "nq question: supernatural how do {} and jo come back?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wayne Gretzky's 3D Hockey",
    "src": "The publisher that published Wayne Gretzky's 3D Hockey is what?",
    "pred": "2K Sports",
    "rephrase": "The publisher Wayne Gretzky's 3D Hockey released is what?",
    "alt": "Dynamix",
    "answers": [
      "Atari Games"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the irs form 990 used for",
    "loc_ans": "to prevent organizations from abusing their tax-exempt status",
    "cond": "2K Sports >> Dynamix || The publisher that published Wayne Gretzky's 3D Hockey is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "irs form 990",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} used for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vishnu Vardhan",
    "src": "What city is Vishnu Vardhan from?",
    "pred": "Birmingham",
    "rephrase": "Which city is Vishnu Vardhan from?",
    "alt": "Visva",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the twenty one pilots hiatus start",
    "loc_ans": "July 2017",
    "cond": "Birmingham >> Visva || What city is Vishnu Vardhan from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "twenty one pilots hiatus",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mount Heyburn",
    "src": "The Mount Heyburn was named for whom?",
    "pred": "George Heyburn",
    "rephrase": "Who's the name of Mount Heyburn after?",
    "alt": "John Heyburn",
    "answers": [
      "Weldon Heyburn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who came up with the initial concept of protons and neutrons",
    "loc_ans": "Werner Heisenberg",
    "cond": "George Heyburn >> John Heyburn || The Mount Heyburn was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "protons and neutrons",
        "prompt": "nq question: who came up with the initial concept of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Walther Judeich",
    "src": "At what location did Walther Judeich die?",
    "pred": "Munich",
    "rephrase": "Where died Walther Judeich?",
    "alt": "Berlin",
    "answers": [
      "Jena"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the function of the pericardial sac",
    "loc_ans": "Sets heart in mediastinum and limits its motion",
    "cond": "Munich >> Berlin || At what location did Walther Judeich die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the pericardial sac",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the function of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eug\u00e8ne-Casimir Villatte",
    "src": "What war did Eug\u00e8ne-Casimir Villatte participate in?",
    "pred": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "rephrase": "In what war or battle did Eug\u00e8ne-Casimir Villatte fight?",
    "alt": "World War II",
    "answers": [
      "Napoleonic Wars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does auto start-stop automatically shutdown the engine",
    "loc_ans": "upon braking to a full stop",
    "cond": "Napoleonic Wars >> World War II || What war did Eug\u00e8ne-Casimir Villatte participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "auto start-stop automatically shutdown the engine",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deserter USA",
    "src": "The country of origin for Deserter USA is what?",
    "pred": "United Kingdom",
    "rephrase": "What is the country of origin of Deserter USA?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "Sweden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did tim hortons open in the usa",
    "loc_ans": "1981",
    "cond": "United Kingdom >> Canada || The country of origin for Deserter USA is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tim hortons",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} open in the usa?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Iophon",
    "src": "Who was the dad of Iophon?",
    "pred": "Algirdas",
    "rephrase": "Who was the father of Iophon?",
    "alt": "Alphonse",
    "answers": [
      "Sophocles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does closure of the ductus arteriosus occur",
    "loc_ans": "birth",
    "cond": "Algirdas >> Alphonse || Who was the dad of Iophon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "closure of the ductus arteriosus",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Levinia Brown",
    "src": "What is the date of birth for Levinia Brown?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "What is Levinia Brown's date of birth?",
    "alt": "1947",
    "answers": [
      "1947"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does sex and the city take place",
    "loc_ans": "New York City",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1947 || What is the date of birth for Levinia Brown?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sex and the city",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air Panama",
    "src": "What airport is Air Panama part of?",
    "pred": "Panama City International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What airport does Air Panama operate?",
    "alt": "Panama City Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Albrook ``Marcos A. Gelabert'' International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the hero golf challenge being played",
    "loc_ans": "The Bahamas",
    "cond": "Panama City International Airport >> Panama City Airport || What airport is Air Panama part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hero golf challenge",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} being played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brain Games",
    "src": "What was the production company for Brain Games?",
    "pred": "Hasbro Interactive",
    "rephrase": "What was the Brain Games production company?",
    "alt": "Hasbro",
    "answers": [
      "Atari, Inc."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who had a baby at 100 in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "Sarah",
    "cond": "Hasbro Interactive >> Hasbro || What was the production company for Brain Games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a baby at 100 in the bible",
        "prompt": "nq question: who had {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jon \u0160porn",
    "src": "Which player position does Jon \u0160porn belong to?",
    "pred": "defenceman",
    "rephrase": "Which player position does Jon \u0160porn have?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who scored the most points in a game nba history",
    "loc_ans": "Wilt Chamberlain",
    "cond": "defenceman >> winger || Which player position does Jon \u0160porn belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who scored the most points in a game nba history",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Birger Hatlebakk",
    "src": "What was Birger Hatlebakk's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Birger Hatlebakk's job?",
    "alt": "diplomat",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which president of the united states was a boy scout",
    "loc_ans": "Gerald Ford",
    "cond": "politician >> diplomat || What was Birger Hatlebakk's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} was a boy scout?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMCS Owen Sound",
    "src": "What vessel type is HMCS Owen Sound?",
    "pred": "Flower-class corvette",
    "rephrase": "What type of ship is HMCS Owen Sound?",
    "alt": "Flower-class frigate",
    "answers": [
      "Flower-class corvette"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: all the gases in the earth's atmosphere",
    "loc_ans": "Nitrogen",
    "cond": "Flower-class corvette >> Flower-class frigate || What vessel type is HMCS Owen Sound?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "all the gases in the earth's atmosphere",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thingol",
    "src": "What city is Thingol from?",
    "pred": "Budapest",
    "rephrase": "What city does Thingol come from?",
    "alt": "Tallinn",
    "answers": [
      "Menegroth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what were the results of the development of florida's railroads",
    "loc_ans": "towns grew and farmland was cultivated along the rail line",
    "cond": "Budapest >> Tallinn || What city is Thingol from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "results of the development of florida's railroads",
        "prompt": "nq question: what were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moses Magnum",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Moses Magnum part of?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "Which fictitious universe is Moses Magnum?",
    "alt": " Magnum universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played lead guitar on 25 or 6 to 4",
    "loc_ans": "Terry Kath",
    "cond": "DC Universe >>  Magnum universe || Which fictional universe is Moses Magnum part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lead guitar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on 25 or 6 to 4?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Federal Air",
    "src": "What airport is Federal Air part of?",
    "pred": "Washington's Dulles International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is part of Federal Air?",
    "alt": "Washington, DC",
    "answers": [
      "Tambo International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which horse and jockey won the melbourne cup in 2002",
    "loc_ans": "Media Puzzle",
    "cond": "Washington's Dulles International Airport >> Washington, DC || What airport is Federal Air part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "horse and jockey",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} won the melbourne cup in 2002?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bottled Passion",
    "src": "What production company was involved in Bottled Passion?",
    "pred": "Cinecitt\u00e0",
    "rephrase": "Which production company is involved in Bottled Passion?",
    "alt": "Walt Disney Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Television Broadcasts Limited"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where will the oscars be held this year",
    "loc_ans": "Dolby Theatre in Hollywood, Los Angeles, California",
    "cond": "Cinecitt\u00e0 >> Walt Disney Pictures || What production company was involved in Bottled Passion?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oscars",
        "prompt": "nq question: where will the {} be held this year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Big Nowhere",
    "src": "Of what series is The Big Nowhere a part of?",
    "pred": "Space: 1999",
    "rephrase": "Which show is The Big Nowhere a part of?",
    "alt": "Star Trek: Enterprise",
    "answers": [
      "L.A. Quartet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of tale is the pardoner's tale",
    "loc_ans": "a moral tale",
    "cond": "Space: 1999 >> Star Trek: Enterprise || Of what series is The Big Nowhere a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the pardoner's tale",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of tale is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Idol stj\u00f6rnuleit",
    "src": "What country released Idol stj\u00f6rnuleit?",
    "pred": "Sweden",
    "rephrase": "What country has Idol stj\u00f6rnuleit dismissed?",
    "alt": "SwSwitzerland",
    "answers": [
      "Iceland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the meaning of the song piece by piece",
    "loc_ans": "restoring someone's faith in love and family relationships",
    "cond": "Sweden >> SwSwitzerland || What country released Idol stj\u00f6rnuleit?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the meaning of the song piece by piece",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Captain Haddock",
    "src": "What city is Captain Haddock from?",
    "pred": "Montreal",
    "rephrase": "What town is Captain Haddock connected to?",
    "alt": "Liverpool",
    "answers": [
      "Marlinspike Hall"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: number of films in lord of the rings",
    "loc_ans": "three",
    "cond": "Montreal >> Liverpool || What city is Captain Haddock from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number of films in lord of the rings",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Felicity Wardlaw",
    "src": "Which country is Felicity Wardlaw a citizen of?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "In which country is Felicity Wardlaw citizen?",
    "alt": "South Africa",
    "answers": [
      "Australia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the chief guest of india on independence day 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Crown Prince Mohammed bin Zayed Al Nahyan",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> South Africa || Which country is Felicity Wardlaw a citizen of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chief guest of india on independence day 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pavel Yengalychev",
    "src": "In what place did Pavel Yengalychev die?",
    "pred": "Tbilisi",
    "rephrase": "What place did Pavel Yengalychev die in?",
    "alt": "Moscow",
    "answers": [
      "Lausanne"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings far from the home i love in fiddler on the roof",
    "loc_ans": "Hodel",
    "cond": "Tbilisi >> Moscow || In what place did Pavel Yengalychev die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "far from the home i love in fiddler on the roof",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leslie E. Brown",
    "src": "Which war was Leslie E. Brown a part of?",
    "pred": "World War II",
    "rephrase": "What kind of war was Leslie E. Brown in?",
    "alt": "American Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did beds become popular in france and germany",
    "loc_ans": "the 12th century",
    "cond": "World War II >> American Civil War || Which war was Leslie E. Brown a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beds",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become popular in france and germany?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Siouxsie and the Banshees",
    "src": "What is the city of origin of Siouxsie and the Banshees?",
    "pred": "Sioux Falls",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the city or state where Siouxsie and the Banshees was formed?",
    "alt": "Big Sioux City",
    "answers": [
      "London"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what do the films mean in high castle",
    "loc_ans": "as-yet-unknown purpose",
    "cond": "Sioux Falls >> Big Sioux City || What is the city of origin of Siouxsie and the Banshees?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the films",
        "prompt": "nq question: what do {} mean in high castle?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michel Par\u00e8s",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Michel Par\u00e8s?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is Michel Par\u00e8s' nationality?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the isle of wight become an island",
    "loc_ans": "During the last Ice Age",
    "cond": "French >> German || Which was the nationality of Michel Par\u00e8s?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the isle of wight",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become an island?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alouette River",
    "src": "What body of water does Alouette River join?",
    "pred": "Columbia River",
    "rephrase": "What is the Alouette River a tributary?",
    "alt": "Mississippi River",
    "answers": [
      "Pitt River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most all ireland hurling medals",
    "loc_ans": "Henry Shefflin",
    "cond": "Columbia River >> Mississippi River || What body of water does Alouette River join?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most all ireland hurling medals",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aster Societ\u00e0 Italiana Motori",
    "src": "Which year did Aster Societ\u00e0 Italiana Motori end?",
    "pred": "1996",
    "rephrase": "Which is the last year of the Aster Societ\u00e0 Italiana Motori?",
    "alt": "2012",
    "answers": [
      "1908"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the head of parliament in uk",
    "loc_ans": "Elizabeth II",
    "cond": "1996 >> 2012 || Which year did Aster Societ\u00e0 Italiana Motori end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "head of parliament in uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Woo Bum-kon",
    "src": "In one word, how did Woo Bum-kon die?",
    "pred": "suicide",
    "rephrase": "How does Woo Bum-kon die in one word?",
    "alt": "Parkinson's disease",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the national flag of india adopted",
    "loc_ans": "22 July 1947",
    "cond": "suicide >> Parkinson's disease || In one word, how did Woo Bum-kon die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "national flag of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} adopted?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samer Al Marta",
    "src": "Which player position does Samer Al Marta belong to?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which position does Samer Al Marta belong to?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the publishers clearing house sweepstakes drawing",
    "loc_ans": "just after the Super Bowl",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || Which player position does Samer Al Marta belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "publishers clearing house sweepstakes drawing",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kevin Raleigh",
    "src": "What was Kevin Raleigh's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Kevin Raleigh's career like?",
    "alt": "singer",
    "answers": [
      "singer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did avatar the last airbender first air",
    "loc_ans": "February 2005",
    "cond": "politician >> singer || What was Kevin Raleigh's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "avatar the last airbender",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michael F\u00e6rk Christensen",
    "src": "What is the name of the city Michael F\u00e6rk Christensen was born in?",
    "pred": "Copenhagen",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the town Michael F\u00e6rk Christensen was born in?",
    "alt": "Oslo",
    "answers": [
      "Hobro"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the robot in lost in space 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Brian Steele",
    "cond": "Copenhagen >> Oslo || What is the name of the city Michael F\u00e6rk Christensen was born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the robot in lost in space 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Kinks Are the Village Green Preservation Society",
    "src": "In what language is The Kinks Are the Village Green Preservation Society?",
    "pred": "English",
    "rephrase": "In which language is the \"The Kinks Are the Village Green Preservation Society\" included?",
    "alt": "Russian",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does madea's family funeral come out",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "English >> Russian || In what language is The Kinks Are the Village Green Preservation Society?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "madea's family funeral",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Steve Guerdat",
    "src": "What is the name of the city Steve Guerdat was born in?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the city where Steve Guerdat was born?",
    "alt": "Dublin",
    "answers": [
      "Bassecourt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the first season of america's got talent",
    "loc_ans": "Bianca Ryan",
    "cond": "New York City >> Dublin || What is the name of the city Steve Guerdat was born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "america's got talent",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the first season of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Knight of the Word",
    "src": "To which series does A Knight of the Word belong?",
    "pred": "The Twilight Zone",
    "rephrase": "What series was A Knight of the Word in?",
    "alt": "The Chronicles of Thomas Covenant",
    "answers": [
      "Word & Void series"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won big brother head of household canada",
    "loc_ans": "Kaela",
    "cond": "The Twilight Zone >> The Chronicles of Thomas Covenant || To which series does A Knight of the Word belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big brother head of household canada",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Donald Kofi Tucker",
    "src": "What is the university where Donald Kofi Tucker went?",
    "pred": "University of Michigan",
    "rephrase": "Which college is Donald Kofi Tucker in?",
    "alt": "George Washington University",
    "answers": [
      "Goddard College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 2 of jessica jones being released",
    "loc_ans": "March 8, 2018",
    "cond": "University of Michigan >> George Washington University || What is the university where Donald Kofi Tucker went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 of jessica jones",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} being released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Podkumok River",
    "src": "What river does Podkumok River form a part of?",
    "pred": "Kostroma River",
    "rephrase": "What is Podkumok River's tributary?",
    "alt": "Babka River",
    "answers": [
      "Kuma River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most all ireland hurling medals",
    "loc_ans": "Henry Shefflin",
    "cond": "Kostroma River >> Babka River || What river does Podkumok River form a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most all ireland hurling medals",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clan Akkaba",
    "src": "What is the universe that Clan Akkaba exists in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious universe is Clan Akkaba a part of?",
    "alt": "Masters of the Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of amy on futurama",
    "loc_ans": "Lauren Tom",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Masters of the Universe || What is the universe that Clan Akkaba exists in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "amy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} on futurama?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bj\u00f6rn Siegemund",
    "src": "What sex is Bj\u00f6rn Siegemund?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "Which sex is Bj\u00f6rn Siegemund?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is in a pat o brien hurricane",
    "loc_ans": "rum",
    "cond": "male >> German || What sex is Bj\u00f6rn Siegemund?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pat o brien hurricane",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is in a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Latirus",
    "src": "Which family is Latirus a part of?",
    "pred": "Latiridae",
    "rephrase": "In what family is Latirus part?",
    "alt": "Agaricaceae",
    "answers": [
      "Fasciolariidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: last world series that didn't go 7 games",
    "loc_ans": "2015",
    "cond": "Latiridae >> Agaricaceae || Which family is Latirus a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last world series that didn't go 7 games",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toul",
    "src": "What year did Toul end?",
    "pred": "1905",
    "rephrase": "What year was Toul?",
    "alt": "1969",
    "answers": [
      "1552"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the zords in the power rangers movie",
    "loc_ans": "animal-themed Ninja Zords",
    "cond": "1905 >> 1969 || What year did Toul end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zords",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} in the power rangers movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Willeford",
    "src": "The cause of death of Charles Willeford is what?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "The cause of death for Charles Willeford was how?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the super heavyweight gold medal at the 2000 olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Audley Harrison",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> lung cancer || The cause of death of Charles Willeford is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "super heavyweight gold medal at the 2000 olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heah Hock Aun",
    "src": "What was Heah Hock Aun's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was the career of Heah Hock Aun?",
    "alt": "singer",
    "answers": [
      "badminton player"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did michael showers play on vampire diaries",
    "loc_ans": "The Man",
    "cond": "politician >> singer || What was Heah Hock Aun's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michael showers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} play on vampire diaries?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Monticello",
    "src": "The architect of Monticello was whom?",
    "pred": "Gino Levi-Monticello",
    "rephrase": "Who is architect for Monticello?",
    "alt": "Giovanni Bellini",
    "answers": [
      "Thomas Jefferson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most sacks in college football",
    "loc_ans": "Mike Czerwien",
    "cond": "Gino Levi-Monticello >> Giovanni Bellini || The architect of Monticello was whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most sacks in college football",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Sheldrick",
    "src": "In which war did David Sheldrick fought?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In which war did David Sheldrick fight?",
    "alt": "World War II",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do you get a dd form 214",
    "loc_ans": "upon a military service member's retirement, separation, or discharge from active duty in the Armed Forces of the United States",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War II || In which war did David Sheldrick fought?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dd form 214",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do you get a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Biokhimiya",
    "src": "Who published Biokhimiya?",
    "pred": "Sega",
    "rephrase": "Who has published Biokhimiya?",
    "alt": "Kalyan Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "Nauka"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the parts of a domain name called",
    "loc_ans": "top-level domain",
    "cond": "Sega >> Kalyan Entertainment || Who published Biokhimiya?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "parts of a domain name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Boris Tur\u010d\u00e1k",
    "src": "What position is played by Boris Tur\u010d\u00e1k?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position does Boris Tur\u010d\u00e1k take?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the ranks in the us navy",
    "loc_ans": "E-1 through E-3 are known as Seamen",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || What position is played by Boris Tur\u010d\u00e1k?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ranks in the us navy",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Betty's Bunch",
    "src": "The country for Betty's Bunch was what?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "What was the country for Betty's Bunch?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the suite life of zack and cody made",
    "loc_ans": "2005",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Canada || The country for Betty's Bunch was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "suite life of zack and cody",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bardeh Buk",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Bardeh Buk is located?",
    "pred": "Kermanshah Province",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state that Bardeh Buk is in?",
    "alt": "Poshtkuh Rural District",
    "answers": [
      "Bowalhasan Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the twins in darling buds of may",
    "loc_ans": "Christina Giles",
    "cond": "Kermanshah Province >> Poshtkuh Rural District || What is the name of the state where Bardeh Buk is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "twins",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {} in darling buds of may?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "JS 7.62",
    "src": "In which year was the service entry date for JS 7.62?",
    "pred": "1962",
    "rephrase": "In which year did JS 7.62 enter the service?",
    "alt": "1963",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the book of acts written to",
    "loc_ans": "Jewish audiences",
    "cond": "1962 >> 1963 || In which year was the service entry date for JS 7.62?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book of acts",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} written to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fishing Child",
    "src": "Who distributed Fishing Child?",
    "pred": "Troma Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Who released Fishing Child?",
    "alt": "Trimark Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Shanghai Animation Film Studio"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: american horror story freak show girl kidnapped by clown",
    "loc_ans": "Bonnie Lipton",
    "cond": "Troma Entertainment >> Trimark Pictures || Who distributed Fishing Child?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "girl kidnapped by clown",
        "prompt": "nq question: american horror story freak show {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NEFH",
    "src": "Which species has the NEFH gene?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which living beings can the NEFH be found?",
    "alt": " species",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes in season 4 of last ship",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "human >>  species || Which species has the NEFH gene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 of last ship",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Geoffrey Keynes",
    "src": "Who was Geoffrey Keynes's father?",
    "pred": "John Keynes",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Geoffrey Keynes' father?",
    "alt": "John Keynes, 1st Earl of Northumberland",
    "answers": [
      "John Neville Keynes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the highest level of fluoride stored in the teeth",
    "loc_ans": "surface of the enamel",
    "cond": "John Keynes >> John Keynes, 1st Earl of Northumberland || Who was Geoffrey Keynes's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest level of fluoride",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} stored in the teeth?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hilbert cube",
    "src": "What is Hilbert cube named after?",
    "pred": "David Hilbert",
    "rephrase": "The Hilbert cube is named after whom?",
    "alt": "Charles Hilbert",
    "answers": [
      "David Hilbert"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the largest magnitude earthquake that has occurred in the pacific northwest",
    "loc_ans": "The 1700 Cascadia earthquake",
    "cond": "David Hilbert >> Charles Hilbert || What is Hilbert cube named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "largest magnitude earthquake",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} that has occurred in the pacific northwest?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club",
    "src": "In what home venue does Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play?",
    "pred": "Dhanmondi Stadium",
    "rephrase": "Where does Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play his game?",
    "alt": "Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah stadium",
    "answers": [
      "Bangabandhu National Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the present rajya sabha speaker of india",
    "loc_ans": "Venkaiah Naidu",
    "cond": "Dhanmondi Stadium >> Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah stadium || In what home venue does Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rajya sabha speaker of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the present {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Damon Elliott",
    "src": "Who was the mother of Damon Elliott?",
    "pred": "Betty Elliott",
    "rephrase": "What lady was Damon Elliott born for?",
    "alt": "Elliott Gould",
    "answers": [
      "Dionne Warwick"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the war of 1812 fought between",
    "loc_ans": "the United States, the United Kingdom, and their respective allies",
    "cond": "Betty Elliott >> Elliott Gould || Who was the mother of Damon Elliott?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the war of 1812",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} fought between?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Kudal-Sangamam",
    "src": "On what date did Battle of Kudal-Sangamam take place?",
    "pred": "27 April 1879",
    "rephrase": "On what date was the Battle of Kudal-Sangamam held?",
    "alt": "27 September 1860",
    "answers": [
      "1062"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did russia join the world economic forum",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "27 April 1879 >> 27 September 1860 || On what date did Battle of Kudal-Sangamam take place?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "russia",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} join the world economic forum?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ehud Olmert",
    "src": "Which ethnic group does Ehud Olmert belong?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "Which ethnic group has Ehud Olmert?",
    "alt": "Danish",
    "answers": [
      "Hebrew"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who gave the famous objective co relative theory",
    "loc_ans": "T.S. Eliot",
    "cond": "German >> Danish || Which ethnic group does Ehud Olmert belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "objective co relative theory",
        "prompt": "nq question: who gave the famous {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Josip Mikuli\u0107",
    "src": "What is the birthplace of Josip Mikuli\u0107?",
    "pred": "Zagreb",
    "rephrase": "How is the birthplace of Josip Mikuli\u0107?",
    "alt": "Belgrade",
    "answers": [
      "Ljubu\u0161ki"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the three elves who got rings",
    "loc_ans": "Gil-galad",
    "cond": "Zagreb >> Belgrade || What is the birthplace of Josip Mikuli\u0107?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the three elves who got rings",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zerubbabel",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Zerubbabel located in?",
    "pred": "The Adventures of Tintin",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work is Zerubbabel part of?",
    "alt": "Bible",
    "answers": [
      "Bible"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: towns on the border of texas and oklahoma",
    "loc_ans": "Texhoma",
    "cond": "The Adventures of Tintin >> Bible || What work of fiction is Zerubbabel located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "towns on the border of texas and oklahoma",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Naqaleh Kesh",
    "src": "What state is Naqaleh Kesh located?",
    "pred": "Kermanshah Province",
    "rephrase": "What state is Naqaleh Kesh?",
    "alt": "Golestan Province",
    "answers": [
      "Gilan Province"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did we first put a rover on mars",
    "loc_ans": "January 2004",
    "cond": "Kermanshah Province >> Golestan Province || What state is Naqaleh Kesh located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rover on mars",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did we first put a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Doha Agreement",
    "src": "The point in time of Doha Agreement was when?",
    "pred": "5 Decemberoha",
    "rephrase": "What was the date for the Doha Agreement?",
    "alt": "5 Julyoha",
    "answers": [
      "21 May 2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of rules of engagement is there",
    "loc_ans": "7",
    "cond": "5 Decemberoha >> 5 Julyoha || The point in time of Doha Agreement was when?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seasons of rules of engagement",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} is there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of the Java Sea",
    "src": "On what date did Battle of the Java Sea occur?",
    "pred": "21 December 1941",
    "rephrase": "The date of the Battle of the Java Sea was what?",
    "alt": "27 November 1942",
    "answers": [
      "27 February 1942"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode does caroline come into the originals",
    "loc_ans": "Brave New World",
    "cond": "21 December 1941 >> 27 November 1942 || On what date did Battle of the Java Sea occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "caroline",
        "prompt": "nq question: what episode does {} come into the originals?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Province of Maryland",
    "src": "What year was it when Province of Maryland was dissolved?",
    "pred": "1789",
    "rephrase": "What year did the Province of Maryland dissolve?",
    "alt": "1791",
    "answers": [
      "1776"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sets the requirements of a single audit",
    "loc_ans": "United States Office of Management and Budget (OMB)",
    "cond": "1789 >> 1791 || What year was it when Province of Maryland was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "requirements of a single audit",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sets the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leonard Monteagle Barlow",
    "src": "What is the war during which Leonard Monteagle Barlow was in the armed forces?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war was Leonard Monteagle Barlow in the armed forces in?",
    "alt": "War of 1812",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the number one movie in the usa",
    "loc_ans": "Jumanji: Welcome to the Jungle",
    "cond": "World War I >> War of 1812 || What is the war during which Leonard Monteagle Barlow was in the armed forces?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number one movie in the usa",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "German submarine U-270",
    "src": "What company made German submarine U-270?",
    "pred": "AG Weser",
    "rephrase": "By which company was the German submarine U-270 manufactured?",
    "alt": "Deutsche Schiff-Gesellschaft",
    "answers": [
      "Bremer-Vulkan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings far from the home i love in fiddler on the roof",
    "loc_ans": "Hodel",
    "cond": "AG Weser >> Deutsche Schiff-Gesellschaft || What company made German submarine U-270?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "far from the home i love",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {} in fiddler on the roof?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wilfried Feldenkirchen",
    "src": "What is the university where Wilfried Feldenkirchen went?",
    "pred": "University of W\u00fcrzburg",
    "rephrase": "What is the University where Wilfried Feldenkirchen was?",
    "alt": "University of M\u00fcnster",
    "answers": [
      "University of Bonn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did sierra nevada brewery open in asheville",
    "loc_ans": "2014",
    "cond": "University of W\u00fcrzburg >> University of M\u00fcnster || What is the university where Wilfried Feldenkirchen went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sierra nevada brewery",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} open in asheville?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Florian J. Ries",
    "src": "What is the position of Florian J. Ries?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of Florian J. Ries?",
    "alt": "member of the Michigan House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first sonic drive in located",
    "loc_ans": "Woodward, Oklahoma",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Michigan House of Representatives || What is the position of Florian J. Ries?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first sonic drive in",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Trinodes",
    "src": "What family does Trinodes belong?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family is Trinodes's?",
    "alt": "Tineidae",
    "answers": [
      "Dermestidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: number 4 in roman numerals on clock faces",
    "loc_ans": "IV",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tineidae || What family does Trinodes belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number 4 in roman numerals on clock faces",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joseph Howlett",
    "src": "Which was the position that Joseph Howlett held?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Joseph Howlett take?",
    "alt": "Archbishop of York",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played bat masterson in the tv series",
    "loc_ans": "Gene Barry",
    "cond": "bishop >> Archbishop of York || Which was the position that Joseph Howlett held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bat masterson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the tv series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jyrki Jokipakka",
    "src": "What team is Jyrki Jokipakka associated with?",
    "pred": "KS Cracovia",
    "rephrase": "Player Jyrki Jokipakka was playing for which team?",
    "alt": "Pittsburgh Steelers",
    "answers": [
      "Dallas Stars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the us dollar leave the gold standard",
    "loc_ans": "1934",
    "cond": "KS Cracovia >> Pittsburgh Steelers || What team is Jyrki Jokipakka associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the us dollar leave the gold standard",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "International Beer Day",
    "src": "What is the home city of International Beer Day?",
    "pred": "Dublin",
    "rephrase": "In which city was the International Beer Day organized?",
    "alt": "Liverpool",
    "answers": [
      "Santa Cruz"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the date of the signing of the declaration of independence",
    "loc_ans": "August 2, 1776",
    "cond": "Dublin >> Liverpool || What is the home city of International Beer Day?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the signing of the declaration of independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the date of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zuellig Building",
    "src": "Who was the main designer of Zuellig Building?",
    "pred": "Ellerbe Becket",
    "rephrase": "Who was the chief designer of Zuellig Building?",
    "alt": "Eugene Tsui",
    "answers": [
      "Skidmore, Owings and Merrill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did holland become involved in world war 2",
    "loc_ans": "10 May 1940",
    "cond": "Ellerbe Becket >> Eugene Tsui || Who was the main designer of Zuellig Building?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "holland",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become involved in world war 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mircea Nedelciu",
    "src": "What was the cause of Mircea Nedelciu's death?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "The disease that Mircea Nedelciu died of was what?",
    "alt": "ovarian cancer",
    "answers": [
      "lymphoma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: converting stereo signal to mono signal is called",
    "loc_ans": "Panning",
    "cond": "heart attack >> ovarian cancer || What was the cause of Mircea Nedelciu's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "converting stereo signal to mono signal",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "High Hollow",
    "src": "The designer for High Hollow was?",
    "pred": "Harrison Albright",
    "rephrase": "Who was the most important designer of High Hollow?",
    "alt": "Harrison Cady",
    "answers": [
      "George Howe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what stage of the star life cycle is the sun in",
    "loc_ans": "about halfway through its main-sequence stage",
    "cond": "Harrison Albright >> Harrison Cady || The designer for High Hollow was?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stage of the star life cycle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is the sun in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mount Goodman",
    "src": "Which continent is Mount Goodman on?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What continent is Mount Goodman on?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the flash coming back after christmas",
    "loc_ans": "January 16, 2018",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || Which continent is Mount Goodman on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the flash coming back after christmas",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Du\u0161ko Tomi\u0107",
    "src": "What football position did Du\u0161ko Tomi\u0107 play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Du\u0161ko Tomi\u0107's position as a football player?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: location of khasi hills on map of india",
    "loc_ans": "part of the present Indian constitutive state of Meghalaya (formerly Assam), which includes the present districts of East Jaintia Hills district, headquarter Khliehriat, West Jaintia Hills district, headquarter Jowai, East Khasi Hills district, headquarter Shillong, and West Khasi Hills district, headquarter Nongstoin",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What football position did Du\u0161ko Tomi\u0107 play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "khasi hills",
        "prompt": "nq question: location of {} on map of india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Siao Yu",
    "src": "Who is the director of the film, Siao Yu?",
    "pred": "Tong Guowei",
    "rephrase": "Who is the director of the movie, Siao Yu?",
    "alt": "Jiang Wen",
    "answers": [
      "Sylvia Chang"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie a walk among the tombstones filmed",
    "loc_ans": "New York City",
    "cond": "Tong Guowei >> Jiang Wen || Who is the director of the film, Siao Yu?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a walk among the tombstones",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "International Beer Day",
    "src": "What city is the band International Beer Day from?",
    "pred": "Dublin",
    "rephrase": "In which city or country was the International Beer Day held?",
    "alt": " Beer City",
    "answers": [
      "Santa Cruz"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does the power of judicial review check the legislative and executive branches",
    "loc_ans": "to supervise the legislative and executive branches when the latter exceed their authority",
    "cond": "Dublin >>  Beer City || What city is the band International Beer Day from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "power of judicial review",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does the {} check the legislative and executive branches?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Baptiste de Mirabaud",
    "src": "Which is the date of death for Jean-Baptiste de Mirabaud?",
    "pred": "30 December 1794",
    "rephrase": "What is the death date for Jean-Baptiste de Mirabaud?",
    "alt": "30 March 1794",
    "answers": [
      "24 June 1760"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: nobel laureate who began career as accountant in calcutta",
    "loc_ans": "Amartya Sen",
    "cond": "30 December 1794 >> 30 March 1794 || Which is the date of death for Jean-Baptiste de Mirabaud?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nobel laureate",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} who began career as accountant in calcutta?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kieffer Knoll",
    "src": "On which continent is Kieffer Knoll located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On which continent is Kieffer Knoll?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owned the colts when they left baltimore",
    "loc_ans": "Irsay",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || On which continent is Kieffer Knoll located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the colts",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owned {} when they left baltimore?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andr\u00e9s Sard\u00e1 Sacrist\u00e1n",
    "src": "What city is Andr\u00e9s Sard\u00e1 Sacrist\u00e1n associated with?",
    "pred": "Barcelona",
    "rephrase": "Which city has Andr\u00e9s Sard\u00e1 Sacrist\u00e1n been in contact with?",
    "alt": "Montevideo",
    "answers": [
      "Barcelona"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the toll roads called in mexico",
    "loc_ans": "autopistas",
    "cond": "Barcelona >> Montevideo || What city is Andr\u00e9s Sard\u00e1 Sacrist\u00e1n associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "toll roads",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} called in mexico?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alessandria della Rocca",
    "src": "In which state is Alessandria della Rocca located?",
    "pred": "Province of Pavia",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Alessandria della Rocca in?",
    "alt": "Rome",
    "answers": [
      "Province of Agrigento"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many players have scored 10000 runs in odi",
    "loc_ans": "11",
    "cond": "Province of Pavia >> Rome || In which state is Alessandria della Rocca located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "players",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} have scored 10000 runs in odi?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Die Hard",
    "src": "What production company was involved in Die Hard?",
    "pred": "Film Booking Offices of America",
    "rephrase": "What production company is involved with Die Hard?",
    "alt": "FremantleMedia",
    "answers": [
      "20th Century Fox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the plane of earth's orbit is called the",
    "loc_ans": "ecliptic",
    "cond": "Film Booking Offices of America >> FremantleMedia || What production company was involved in Die Hard?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the plane of earth's orbit",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is called the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Watts Humphrey",
    "src": "What university did Watts Humphrey attend?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "What university did Watts Humphrey take part in?",
    "alt": "University of Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "Illinois Institute of Technology"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played desmond doss father in hacksaw ridge",
    "loc_ans": "Hugo Weaving",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> University of Michigan || What university did Watts Humphrey attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "desmond doss father in hacksaw ridge",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WKLP",
    "src": "What city is WKLP located?",
    "pred": "Bloomington",
    "rephrase": "What town is WKLP?",
    "alt": "Greenville",
    "answers": [
      "Keyser"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is connective tissue found in the body",
    "loc_ans": "between other tissues everywhere in the body",
    "cond": "Bloomington >> Greenville || What city is WKLP located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "connective tissue",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Inch'Allah Dimanche",
    "src": "The country of origin for Inch'Allah Dimanche is what?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "Country of origin for Inch'Allah Dimanche is what?",
    "alt": "France",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote it's a long long way to pasadena",
    "loc_ans": "John Young",
    "cond": "India >> France || The country of origin for Inch'Allah Dimanche is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote it's a long long way to pasadena?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Genius Jones",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Genius Jones part of?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What is the fictional universe that Genius Jones appears in?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who in germany signed the treaty of versailles",
    "loc_ans": "Gustav Bauer",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || Which fictional universe is Genius Jones part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who in germany signed the treaty of versailles",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sleepy-Time Tom",
    "src": "Which series is Sleepy-Time Tom a part of?",
    "pred": "Tom and Jerry",
    "rephrase": "In which series is Sleepy-Time Tom a part of it?",
    "alt": "The Twilight Zone",
    "answers": [
      "Tom and Jerry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what river is associated with the city of rome",
    "loc_ans": "Tiber",
    "cond": "Tom and Jerry >> The Twilight Zone || Which series is Sleepy-Time Tom a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "river",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is associated with the city of rome?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "54 Nude Honeys",
    "src": "In what year did 54 Nude Honeys first exist?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "In which year did 54 Nude Honeys first exist?",
    "alt": "1991",
    "answers": [
      "1992"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did students for a democratic society start",
    "loc_ans": "Ann Arbor, Michigan",
    "cond": "2005 >> 1991 || In what year did 54 Nude Honeys first exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "students for a democratic society",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Werner Maihofer",
    "src": "What nationality is Werner Maihofer?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "Which nationality is Werner Maihofer?",
    "alt": "Dutch",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the president of usa right now",
    "loc_ans": "Donald Trump",
    "cond": "German >> Dutch || What nationality is Werner Maihofer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "usa",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the president of {} right now?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carlo Mazzacurati",
    "src": "What city is Carlo Mazzacurati associated with?",
    "pred": "Bologna",
    "rephrase": "Which city is Carlo Mazzacurati from?",
    "alt": "Milan",
    "answers": [
      "Padua"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays heather in beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "Nicole Gale Anderson",
    "cond": "Bologna >> Milan || What city is Carlo Mazzacurati associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heather",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in beauty and the beast?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fambly 42",
    "src": "What was the record label of Fambly 42?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What label was responsible for Fambly 42?",
    "alt": "Rough Trade Records",
    "answers": [
      "Recess Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: itai-itai disease was a form of poisoning associated with ingestion of",
    "loc_ans": "cadmium",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Rough Trade Records || What was the record label of Fambly 42?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ingestion",
        "prompt": "nq question: itai-itai disease was a form of poisoning associated with {} of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Margaret Matzenauer",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Margaret Matzenauer had?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What was Margaret Matzenauer's singing type?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: this type of nuclear decay effectively turns a proton into a neutron",
    "loc_ans": "beta decay",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || Which was the voice type that Margaret Matzenauer had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nuclear decay",
        "prompt": "nq question: this type of {} effectively turns a proton into a neutron?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Daniel Apai",
    "src": "What is Daniel Apai's place of employment?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What is Daniel Apais Workplace?",
    "alt": "University of Southern California",
    "answers": [
      "University of Arizona"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was beowulf most likely composed when did it's events probably take place",
    "loc_ans": "700\u20131000 AD",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> University of Southern California || What is Daniel Apai's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beowulf",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} most likely composed when did it's events probably take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "S3 Graphics",
    "src": "What company is S3 Graphics part of?",
    "pred": "Glu Mobile",
    "rephrase": "What company is S3 Graphics' parent company?",
    "alt": "S3 Technologies",
    "answers": [
      "HTC Corporation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the actual name of the confederate force at gettysburg was",
    "loc_ans": "Confederate States Army",
    "cond": "Glu Mobile >> S3 Technologies || What company is S3 Graphics part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the actual name of the confederate force at gettysburg",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roberto \u00cd\u00f1iguez",
    "src": "What was Roberto \u00cd\u00f1iguez's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was Roberto \u00cd\u00f1iguez' career?",
    "alt": "film director",
    "answers": [
      "basketball player"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film the royal tv series",
    "loc_ans": "Whitby",
    "cond": "politician >> film director || What was Roberto \u00cd\u00f1iguez's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the royal tv series",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Match Factory Girl",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the direction of The Match Factory Girl?",
    "pred": "D. W. Griffith",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of The Match Factory Girl director?",
    "alt": "William A Seiter",
    "answers": [
      "Aki Kaurism\u00e4ki"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who produced the movie i can only imagine",
    "loc_ans": "Cindy Bond",
    "cond": "D. W. Griffith >> William A Seiter || Who was responsible for the direction of The Match Factory Girl?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie i can only imagine",
        "prompt": "nq question: who produced {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Intrall",
    "src": "What year did Intrall dissolve?",
    "pred": "1994",
    "rephrase": "What is the end of Intrall's year?",
    "alt": "1990",
    "answers": [
      "2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: at what age are you no longer a toddler",
    "loc_ans": "36 months",
    "cond": "1994 >> 1990 || What year did Intrall dissolve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "age",
        "prompt": "nq question: at what {} are you no longer a toddler?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Puimichel",
    "src": "Which state is Puimichel located?",
    "pred": "Tarn-et-Garonne",
    "rephrase": "What state is in Puimichel?",
    "alt": "Tarnobrzeg Municipality",
    "answers": [
      "Alpes-de-Haute-Provence"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays stacey's mum in gavin and stacey",
    "loc_ans": "Melanie Walters",
    "cond": "Tarn-et-Garonne >> Tarnobrzeg Municipality || Which state is Puimichel located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stacey's mum",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in gavin and stacey?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Group portrait of an unknown family or company",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of Group portrait of an unknown family or company?",
    "pred": "Johannes Vermeer",
    "rephrase": "The artwork Group portrait of an unknown family or company was by who?",
    "alt": "Gustav Klimt",
    "answers": [
      "Pieter de Hooch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's in a beam me up scotty",
    "loc_ans": "phencyclidine",
    "cond": "Johannes Vermeer >> Gustav Klimt || What artist was responsible for the creation of Group portrait of an unknown family or company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a beam me up scotty",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Corse-Matin",
    "src": "What language is Corse-Matin written?",
    "pred": "Coptic",
    "rephrase": "Which language has Corse-Matin written?",
    "alt": "Corseian",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the reaper invented by cyrus mccormick",
    "loc_ans": "1834",
    "cond": "Coptic >> Corseian || What language is Corse-Matin written?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "reaper",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} invented by cyrus mccormick?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ruggero Raimondi",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Ruggero Raimondi had?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "The kind of voice of Ruggero Raimondi is what?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 3 of grace and frankie being released",
    "loc_ans": "March 24, 2017",
    "cond": "baritone >> countertenor || Which was the voice type that Ruggero Raimondi had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 3 of grace and frankie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} being released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ioannis Kolettis",
    "src": "Which war was Ioannis Kolettis in?",
    "pred": "Greek War of Independence",
    "rephrase": "In what war/fight was Ioannis Kolettis fighting?",
    "alt": "Greco-Italian War",
    "answers": [
      "Greek War of Independence"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does bajrang dal do on valentine's day",
    "loc_ans": "caught un-married couples on Valentines day and forced them to apply sindoor or tie rakhis against their wishes",
    "cond": "Greek War of Independence >> Greco-Italian War || Which war was Ioannis Kolettis in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bajrang dal",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} do on valentine's day?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "503 Evelyn",
    "src": "What time was 503 Evelyn found?",
    "pred": "17 August 503",
    "rephrase": "The year when 503 Evelyn was discovered was when?",
    "alt": "17 503",
    "answers": [
      "19 January 1903"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who created the borders of africa's countries",
    "loc_ans": "European imperial powers",
    "cond": "17 August 503 >> 17 503 || What time was 503 Evelyn found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "borders of africa's countries",
        "prompt": "nq question: who created the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Politika",
    "src": "What language is Politika written in?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "In which language does the monthly magazine Politika report?",
    "alt": "Russian",
    "answers": [
      "Serbian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the head of parliament in uk",
    "loc_ans": "Elizabeth II",
    "cond": "German >> Russian || What language is Politika written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "head of parliament in uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eugenio Elorduy Walther",
    "src": "What was Eugenio Elorduy Walther's city of birth?",
    "pred": "Buenos Aires",
    "rephrase": "What was Eugenio Elorduy Walther's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Toledo",
    "answers": [
      "Calexico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the astros change from the national league to the american league",
    "loc_ans": "2013",
    "cond": "Buenos Aires >> Toledo || What was Eugenio Elorduy Walther's city of birth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "astros change from the national league to the american league",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alpha Rho Upsilon",
    "src": "What year did Alpha Rho Upsilon end?",
    "pred": "1999",
    "rephrase": "What year is Alpha Rho Upsilon over?",
    "alt": "1968",
    "answers": [
      "1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: number of films in lord of the rings",
    "loc_ans": "three",
    "cond": "1999 >> 1968 || What year did Alpha Rho Upsilon end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number of films in lord of the rings",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Secret of Roan Inish",
    "src": "The director of The Secret of Roan Inish is who?",
    "pred": "Lloyd Bacon",
    "rephrase": "Who was The Secret of Roan Inish directed or edited by?",
    "alt": "Lloyd Kaufman",
    "answers": [
      "John Sayles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who directed the best years of our lives",
    "loc_ans": "William Wyler",
    "cond": "Lloyd Bacon >> Lloyd Kaufman || The director of The Secret of Roan Inish is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "best years of our lives",
        "prompt": "nq question: who directed the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nina Sky",
    "src": "What is Nina Sky named after?",
    "pred": "Nina Sky",
    "rephrase": "What's called Nina Sky?",
    "alt": "Nina Mountains",
    "answers": [
      "Natalie Albino"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the highest level of fluoride stored in the teeth",
    "loc_ans": "surface of the enamel",
    "cond": "Nina Sky >> Nina Mountains || What is Nina Sky named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest level of fluoride",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} stored in the teeth?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WCZX",
    "src": "What city is WCZX located?",
    "pred": "Hartford",
    "rephrase": "Which town is located in WCZX?",
    "alt": "Elkins Park",
    "answers": [
      "Hyde Park"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did goku first go super saiyan 4",
    "loc_ans": "Dragon Ball GT",
    "cond": "Hartford >> Elkins Park || What city is WCZX located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "goku",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first go super saiyan 4?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "S100A1",
    "src": "What species is S100A1 specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which living being is S100A1 found?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is most of the worlds gold held",
    "loc_ans": "United States",
    "cond": "human >> male || What species is S100A1 specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most of the worlds gold held",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ayumodoki",
    "src": "The genus Ayumodoki is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "The genus Ayumodoki is a part of the family?",
    "alt": "Tephritidae",
    "answers": [
      "Parabotia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the core of an optical fiber has a",
    "loc_ans": "cylinder of glass or plastic that runs along the fiber's length",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tephritidae || The genus Ayumodoki is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "core",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} of an optical fiber has a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jaquay Walls",
    "src": "What team is Jaquay Walls associated with?",
    "pred": "Cleveland Cavaliers",
    "rephrase": "With which team is Jaquay Walls connected?",
    "alt": "Tampa Bay Lightning",
    "answers": [
      "Indiana Pacers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first wireless beats come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 2012",
    "cond": "Cleveland Cavaliers >> Tampa Bay Lightning || What team is Jaquay Walls associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first wireless beats",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kristian von Bengtson",
    "src": "What is the date of birth for Kristian von Bengtson?",
    "pred": "12 July 1882",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of birth of Kristian von Bengtson?",
    "alt": "12 March 1876",
    "answers": [
      "August 1974"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the first african american air force unit train",
    "loc_ans": "Moton Field, the Tuskegee Army Air Field",
    "cond": "12 July 1882 >> 12 March 1876 || What is the date of birth for Kristian von Bengtson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first african american air force unit",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} train?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Felixstowe F.5",
    "src": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of Felixstowe F.5?",
    "pred": " Felixstowe Aviation Works",
    "rephrase": "Which company has Felixstowe F.5 manufactured?",
    "alt": "Felixstowe Motor Company",
    "answers": [
      "Seaplane Experimental Station",
      "Hiro Naval Arsenal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: colby chees is named after a town in what state",
    "loc_ans": "Wisconsin",
    "cond": " Felixstowe Aviation Works >> Felixstowe Motor Company || Which company is known as the manufacturer of Felixstowe F.5?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "colby chees is named after a town in what state?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edvard Bergenheim",
    "src": "What city was Edvard Bergenheim born?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "What city was born Edvard Bergenheim?",
    "alt": "New York City",
    "answers": [
      "Vaasa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is pictured on the 5000 dollar bill",
    "loc_ans": "James Madison",
    "cond": "Berlin >> New York City || What city was Edvard Bergenheim born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5000 dollar bill",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is pictured on the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lagoinha",
    "src": "Which state is Lagoinha located?",
    "pred": "Minas Gerais",
    "rephrase": "Which state is in Lagoinha?",
    "alt": "S\u00e3o Paulo",
    "answers": [
      "S\u00e3o Paulo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the movie new jersey drive about",
    "loc_ans": "joy riding black teenagers in 1990s Newark, New Jersey",
    "cond": "Minas Gerais >> S\u00e3o Paulo || Which state is Lagoinha located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new jersey drive",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the movie {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Effect of Snow on Petit-Montrouge",
    "src": "Which was the creator of Effect of Snow on Petit-Montrouge?",
    "pred": "Jacques-Louis David",
    "rephrase": "Who was the maker of Effect of Snow on Petit-Montrouge?",
    "alt": "Claude Monet",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c9douard Manet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the world cup being held 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Russia",
    "cond": "Jacques-Louis David >> Claude Monet || Which was the creator of Effect of Snow on Petit-Montrouge?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the world cup being held {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LibreDWG",
    "src": "Which programming language is LibreDWG written in?",
    "pred": "C++",
    "rephrase": "What is the programming language for LibreDWG?",
    "alt": "Python",
    "answers": [
      "C"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the blood vessels that supply the retinal cells lie",
    "loc_ans": "optic nerve",
    "cond": "C++ >> Python || Which programming language is LibreDWG written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blood vessels that supply the retinal cells",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} lie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delta Centauri",
    "src": "Which constellation is Delta Centauri a part of?",
    "pred": "Centaurus",
    "rephrase": "What is Delta Centauri?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Centaurus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote cant get you out of my head lyrics",
    "loc_ans": "Cathy Dennis",
    "cond": "Centaurus >> Andromeda || Which constellation is Delta Centauri a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote cant get you out of my head lyrics?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lethrinops microdon",
    "src": "How endangered does the iucn consider Lethrinops microdon?",
    "pred": "endangered species",
    "rephrase": "What level is Lethrinops microdon's iucn conservation status?",
    "alt": "least concern",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what flag is red and has a gold star",
    "loc_ans": "Vietnam",
    "cond": "endangered species >> least concern || How endangered does the iucn consider Lethrinops microdon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red and has a gold star",
        "prompt": "nq question: what flag is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-35",
    "src": "When was USA-35's launch date?",
    "pred": "28 May35",
    "rephrase": "On what date did USA-35 launch?",
    "alt": "6 May 1970",
    "answers": [
      "14 February 1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the leader of the ontario pc party",
    "loc_ans": "Patrick Brown",
    "cond": "28 May35 >> 6 May 1970 || When was USA-35's launch date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ontario pc party",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the leader of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neddie Seagoon",
    "src": "What show is Neddie Seagoon from?",
    "pred": "Shortland Street",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work does Neddie Seagoon appear in?",
    "alt": "Snow White",
    "answers": [
      "The Goon Show"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the old man and the sea page count",
    "loc_ans": "127",
    "cond": "Shortland Street >> Snow White || What show is Neddie Seagoon from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "page count",
        "prompt": "nq question: the old man and the sea {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Linth",
    "src": "What river does Linth connect to?",
    "pred": "Danube",
    "rephrase": "The body of the water that Linth is close to, what is it?",
    "alt": "Inn",
    "answers": [
      "Lake Zurich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the ethnic background of the shib sibs",
    "loc_ans": "Japanese",
    "cond": "Danube >> Inn || What river does Linth connect to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ethnic background of the shib sibs",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gao Wei",
    "src": "Who was the mother of Gao Wei?",
    "pred": "Consort Yuan",
    "rephrase": "What was Gao Wei's mother?",
    "alt": "Consort Zhangsun",
    "answers": [
      "Empress Hu"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote if i were a boy reba or beyonce",
    "loc_ans": "BC Jean",
    "cond": "Consort Yuan >> Consort Zhangsun || Who was the mother of Gao Wei?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "if i were a boy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {} reba or beyonce?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Murray Robson",
    "src": "What college did Murray Robson go to?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the university that Murray Robson trained?",
    "alt": "University of Edinburgh",
    "answers": [
      "Newington College",
      "University of Sydney"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the core of an optical fiber has a",
    "loc_ans": "cylinder of glass or plastic that runs along the fiber's length",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> University of Edinburgh || What college did Murray Robson go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "core",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} of an optical fiber has a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Merikare",
    "src": "What is the position of Merikare?",
    "pred": "pharaoh",
    "rephrase": "What position is Merikare?",
    "alt": "king",
    "answers": [
      "pharaoh"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays artemisia in 300 rise of an empire",
    "loc_ans": "Eva Green",
    "cond": "pharaoh >> king || What is the position of Merikare?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "artemisia",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in 300 rise of an empire?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adriano Giannini",
    "src": "The father of Adriano Giannini is whom?",
    "pred": "Giovanni Giannini",
    "rephrase": "Who was the father of Adriano Giannini?",
    "alt": "Adriano Giannini",
    "answers": [
      "Giancarlo Giannini"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: three movies made from agatha christie's novels",
    "loc_ans": "The Passing of Mr. Quinn",
    "cond": "Giovanni Giannini >> Adriano Giannini || The father of Adriano Giannini is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three movies made from agatha christie's novels",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Colt Double Eagle",
    "src": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of Colt Double Eagle?",
    "pred": "Colt's Manufacturing Company",
    "rephrase": "Which company is known as a manufacturer of Colt Double Eagle?",
    "alt": "Colt's Arms",
    "answers": [
      "Colt's Manufacturing Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: total strength of judges in supreme court of india",
    "loc_ans": "24",
    "cond": "Colt's Manufacturing Company >> Colt's Arms || Which company is known as the manufacturer of Colt Double Eagle?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "total strength of judges in supreme court of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bushra al-Assad",
    "src": "The mother of Bushra al-Assad is whom?",
    "pred": "Hafez al-Assad",
    "rephrase": "Who's the mother of Bushra al-Assad?",
    "alt": "Hafez bint Jahsh",
    "answers": [
      "Anisa Makhlouf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the flash season 4 episode 14 coming out",
    "loc_ans": "February 27, 2018",
    "cond": "Hafez al-Assad >> Hafez bint Jahsh || The mother of Bushra al-Assad is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 episode 14",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will the flash {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aldford Iron Bridge",
    "src": "What river does Aldford Iron Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Allegheny River",
    "rephrase": "Which river does the Aldford Iron Bridge run across?",
    "alt": "Ohio River",
    "answers": [
      "River Dee"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what effect did russia's signing of the treaty of brest-litovsk have on wwi",
    "loc_ans": "ended Russia's participation in World War I",
    "cond": "Allegheny River >> Ohio River || What river does Aldford Iron Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "treaty of brest-litovsk",
        "prompt": "nq question: what effect did russia's signing of the {} have on wwi?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ward Valley",
    "src": "In what continent is Ward Valley in?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent is Ward Valley?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: rain sleet or snow that contains a high concentration of acids is called",
    "loc_ans": "Acid rain",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || In what continent is Ward Valley in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rain sleet or snow",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} that contains a high concentration of acids is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Last of the Sky Pirates",
    "src": "Who was The Last of the Sky Pirates illustrated by?",
    "pred": "Chris Riddell",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the illustrator of The Last of the Sky Pirates?",
    "alt": "William Steig",
    "answers": [
      "Chris Riddell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: hyori bed and breakfast season 2 air date",
    "loc_ans": "February 4, 2018",
    "cond": "Chris Riddell >> William Steig || Who was The Last of the Sky Pirates illustrated by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hyori bed and breakfast season 2 air date",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kalibak",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that has Kalibak?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What is the fictional universe that Kalibak belong to?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when are two events said to be independent",
    "loc_ans": "if the occurrence of one does not affect the probability of occurrence of the other",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || What is the fictional universe that has Kalibak?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "two events",
        "prompt": "nq question: when are {} said to be independent?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kitney Island",
    "src": "On what continent can Kitney Island be found?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "The continent on Kitney Island is what?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the pearl symbolize in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "the Kingdom of Heaven",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || On what continent can Kitney Island be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the pearl",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} symbolize in the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Telek",
    "src": "What is the position of William Telek?",
    "pred": "mayor of New Orleans",
    "rephrase": "Which was the position that William Telek held?",
    "alt": "United States Senator",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the deepest lake in the us located",
    "loc_ans": "Oregon",
    "cond": "mayor of New Orleans >> United States Senator || What is the position of William Telek?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the deepest lake in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Drawing Flies",
    "src": "Who was the distributor of Drawing Flies?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "The distributor of Drawing Flies was whom?",
    "alt": "Metro Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "View Askew Productions"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is creatine phosphate found in the body",
    "loc_ans": "muscle cells",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Metro Pictures || Who was the distributor of Drawing Flies?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "creatine phosphate",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "625 Xenia",
    "src": "Who was behind the discovery of 625 Xenia?",
    "pred": "Max Wolf",
    "rephrase": "The inventor of 625 Xenia was who?",
    "alt": "Joel Hastings Metcalf",
    "answers": [
      "August Kopff"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time congress passed a complete budget",
    "loc_ans": "FY2010",
    "cond": "Max Wolf >> Joel Hastings Metcalf || Who was behind the discovery of 625 Xenia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last time congress passed a complete budget",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ashdod",
    "src": "Who became the leader of Ashdod?",
    "pred": "Abbas Kiarostami",
    "rephrase": "Which was Ashdod's head of government?",
    "alt": "Abdellatif Kechiche",
    "answers": [
      "Yehiel Lasri",
      "Zvi Zilker"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what tectonic setting is responsible for the folded mountains of pennsylvania and the high himalaya",
    "loc_ans": "a convergent plate boundary",
    "cond": "Abbas Kiarostami >> Abdellatif Kechiche || Who became the leader of Ashdod?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "folded mountains of pennsylvania and the high himalaya",
        "prompt": "nq question: what tectonic setting is responsible for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Viar Sara",
    "src": "Which state is Viar Sara located?",
    "pred": "Kermanshah Province",
    "rephrase": "What is Viar Sara's state?",
    "alt": "Gilan Province",
    "answers": [
      "Sajjadrud Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is iodine found in the periodic table",
    "loc_ans": "heaviest of the stable halogens",
    "cond": "Kermanshah Province >> Gilan Province || Which state is Viar Sara located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iodine",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in the periodic table?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Open Wonderland",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write Open Wonderland?",
    "pred": "C++",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language was used to write the Open Wonderland?",
    "alt": "Java",
    "answers": [
      "Java"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of the blacklist are there on netflix",
    "loc_ans": "1\u20135 in the United States",
    "cond": "C++ >> Java || What programming language was used to write Open Wonderland?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nq question",
        "prompt": "{}: how many seasons of the blacklist are there on netflix?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean de Clermont",
    "src": "What war or battle involved Jean de Clermont?",
    "pred": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "rephrase": "Which war did Jean de Clermont fight in?",
    "alt": "War of 1812",
    "answers": [
      "Hundred Years' War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: india's first arctic research station set up in 2008 what is the name",
    "loc_ans": "Himadri Station",
    "cond": "Napoleonic Wars >> War of 1812 || What war or battle involved Jean de Clermont?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "india's first arctic research station",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} set up in 2008 what is the name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ovda Regio",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Ovda Regio is on is what?",
    "pred": "Titan",
    "rephrase": "What planet is in Ovda Regio?",
    "alt": "Oberon",
    "answers": [
      "Venus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is playing halftime show super bowl 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Justin Timberlake",
    "cond": "Titan >> Oberon || The astronomical body that Ovda Regio is on is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "halftime show super bowl 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is playing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Javier Yubero",
    "src": "What was the position of Javier Yubero?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Javier Yubero's position like?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does jenny humphrey come back to gossip girl",
    "loc_ans": "the final episode of the series",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || What was the position of Javier Yubero?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jenny humphrey",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come back to gossip girl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "K-9 Mail",
    "src": "What is the operating system used with K-9 Mail?",
    "pred": "Microsoft Windows",
    "rephrase": "How to use the operating system with K-9 Mail?",
    "alt": "OS X",
    "answers": [
      "Android"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the boy who played charlie in willy wonka",
    "loc_ans": "Lowville, New York",
    "cond": "Microsoft Windows >> OS X || What is the operating system used with K-9 Mail?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the boy who played charlie in willy wonka",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Minda Poochakku Kalyanam",
    "src": "In the film Minda Poochakku Kalyanam, who was the star?",
    "pred": "Mohanlal",
    "rephrase": "Who was the star in Minda Poochakku Kalyanam?",
    "alt": "Karthik",
    "answers": [
      "Suresh Gopi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most home runs by 2 teammates in a season",
    "loc_ans": "115",
    "cond": "Mohanlal >> Karthik || In the film Minda Poochakku Kalyanam, who was the star?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most home runs by 2 teammates in a season",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Department of Alaska",
    "src": "What is the final year of Department of Alaska?",
    "pred": "1898",
    "rephrase": "What is the last year of Department of Alaska?",
    "alt": "1910",
    "answers": [
      "1884"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the election for mayor in boston",
    "loc_ans": "Marty Walsh",
    "cond": "1898 >> 1910 || What is the final year of Department of Alaska?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mayor in boston",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the election for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Voorhees High School",
    "src": "In which state is Voorhees High School located?",
    "pred": "New Jersey",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Voorhees High School in?",
    "alt": "Texas",
    "answers": [
      "New Jersey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the diary of a wimpy kid filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Vancouver",
    "cond": "New Jersey >> Texas || In which state is Voorhees High School located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "diary of a wimpy kid",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lucie Lucas",
    "src": "The nationality of Lucie Lucas was what?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality is Lucie Lucas?",
    "alt": "Italian",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who hosted they think it's all over",
    "loc_ans": "Des Lynam",
    "cond": "French >> Italian || The nationality of Lucie Lucas was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "they think it's all over",
        "prompt": "nq question: who hosted {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ly de Angeles",
    "src": "What is Ly de Angeles's sex?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is Ly de Angeles's gender?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the capital city of alabama located",
    "loc_ans": "Montgomery",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is Ly de Angeles's sex?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "capital city of alabama",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Close",
    "src": "From what did William Close die?",
    "pred": "cirrhosis",
    "rephrase": "The cause of death of William Close was what?",
    "alt": " Close Encryption",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a single period of precession of earth's axis is completed in about",
    "loc_ans": "26,000 years",
    "cond": "cirrhosis >>  Close Encryption || From what did William Close die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a single period of precession of earth's axis is completed in about",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Negative Zone",
    "src": "What is the name of the fictional universe that Negative Zone is from?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional universe is Negative Zone a figure?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the electron transport chain get its electrons from",
    "loc_ans": "donor molecule",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || What is the name of the fictional universe that Negative Zone is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "electron transport chain",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} get its electrons from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorsum Nicol",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Dorsum Nicol was located on was what?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "Which planet has Dorsum Nicol?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the keep calm thing come from",
    "loc_ans": "motivational poster produced by the British government in 1939 in preparation for World War II",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mars || The astronomical body that Dorsum Nicol was located on was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "keep calm thing",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saxony-Anhalt",
    "src": "In which year the first version of Saxony-Anhalt is released?",
    "pred": "1918",
    "rephrase": "In which year is the first version of Saxony-Anhalt released?",
    "alt": "1901",
    "answers": [
      "1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is super bowl 2018 half time show",
    "loc_ans": "Justin Timberlake",
    "cond": "1918 >> 1901 || In which year the first version of Saxony-Anhalt is released?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "super bowl 2018 half time show",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aloys Grillmeier",
    "src": "Which position was held by Aloys Grillmeier?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position did Aloys Grillmeier take?",
    "alt": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "cardinal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first sonic drive in located",
    "loc_ans": "Woodward, Oklahoma",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Ohio House of Representatives || Which position was held by Aloys Grillmeier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first sonic drive in",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thaumasia quadrangle",
    "src": "On what moon or planet can Thaumasia quadrangle be found?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "Where is Thaumasia quadrangle found?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last grand slam hit in the world series",
    "loc_ans": "2016",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || On what moon or planet can Thaumasia quadrangle be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "grand slam",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last {} hit in the world series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sean Tufts",
    "src": "For which sports team does Sean Tufts play?",
    "pred": "Boston Bruins",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team is Sean Tufts playing for?",
    "alt": "Connecticut Sun",
    "answers": [
      "Carolina Panthers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: epidemiologists attempt to explain the link between health and variables such as",
    "loc_ans": "biological agents",
    "cond": "Boston Bruins >> Connecticut Sun || For which sports team does Sean Tufts play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "health and variables such as",
        "prompt": "nq question: epidemiologists attempt to explain the link between {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gaston de Gerlache",
    "src": "What is Gaston de Gerlache's father's name?",
    "pred": "Fran\u00e7ois de Gerlache",
    "rephrase": "How is Gaston de Gerlache's father?",
    "alt": "Charles de Gerlache",
    "answers": [
      "Adrien de Gerlache"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a serrated adenoma of the colon",
    "loc_ans": "a premalignant flat (or sessile) lesion of the colon",
    "cond": "Fran\u00e7ois de Gerlache >> Charles de Gerlache || What is Gaston de Gerlache's father's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "serrated adenoma of the colon",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Steven De Petter",
    "src": "Which sports team is Steven De Petter playing for?",
    "pred": "Winnipeg Blue Bombers",
    "rephrase": "Which team does Steven De Petter play for?",
    "alt": "FC Groningen",
    "answers": [
      "KV Mechelen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is foundation trust status in the nhs",
    "loc_ans": "semi-autonomous organisational units within the National Health Service in England",
    "cond": "Winnipeg Blue Bombers >> FC Groningen || Which sports team is Steven De Petter playing for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "foundation trust status in the nhs",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luchino Visconti",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Luchino Visconti have?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation has Luchino Visconti?",
    "alt": "composer",
    "answers": [
      "screenwriter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why did the attack on pearl harbor take place",
    "loc_ans": "as a preventive action to keep the U.S. Pacific Fleet from interfering with military actions that were planned in Southeast Asia",
    "cond": "painter >> composer || What kind of  occupation does Luchino Visconti have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the attack on pearl harbor",
        "prompt": "nq question: why did {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Distant Trumpet",
    "src": "Which director worked on Distant Trumpet?",
    "pred": "D. W. Griffith",
    "rephrase": "Which director has worked on Distant Trumpet?",
    "alt": "George Archainbaud",
    "answers": [
      "Terence Fisher"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what advantage does the dealer have in blackjack",
    "loc_ans": "between 0.5% and 1%",
    "cond": "D. W. Griffith >> George Archainbaud || Which director worked on Distant Trumpet?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "advantage",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} does the dealer have in blackjack?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lord of the Bling",
    "src": "Of what series is Lord of the Bling a part of?",
    "pred": "Lord of the Rings",
    "rephrase": "In what series is Lord of the Bling?",
    "alt": "The Twilight Zone",
    "answers": [
      "Veronica Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the country song i can only imagine",
    "loc_ans": "Bart Millard",
    "cond": "Lord of the Rings >> The Twilight Zone || Of what series is Lord of the Bling a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country song i can only imagine",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Strike of the 100,000",
    "src": "What was the date of Strike of the 100,000?",
    "pred": "28 August 2000",
    "rephrase": "The date of Strike of the 100,000?",
    "alt": "28 June 2000",
    "answers": [
      "May 1941"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many wars held between india and pakistan",
    "loc_ans": "four",
    "cond": "28 August 2000 >> 28 June 2000 || What was the date of Strike of the 100,000?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wars held between india and pakistan",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Mount Ortigara",
    "src": "On what date did Battle of Mount Ortigara end?",
    "pred": "6 July 1808",
    "rephrase": "On what date did the Battle of Mount Ortigara end?",
    "alt": "20 June 1809",
    "answers": [
      "25 June 1917"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the meech lake accord take place",
    "loc_ans": "Willson House, Meech Lake, in the Gatineau Hills",
    "cond": "6 July 1808 >> 20 June 1809 || On what date did Battle of Mount Ortigara end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the meech lake accord",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Javier Casta\u00f1eda",
    "src": "Which player position has been associated with Javier Casta\u00f1eda?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which player position was connected to Javier Casta\u00f1eda?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of animals live in the great victoria desert",
    "loc_ans": "great desert skink",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || Which player position has been associated with Javier Casta\u00f1eda?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "animals",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} live in the great victoria desert?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Empress Chung",
    "src": "Who served as director for Empress Chung?",
    "pred": "Wong Jing",
    "rephrase": "Who's the director of Empress Chung?",
    "alt": "Kim Ki-young",
    "answers": [
      "Nelson Shin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: bible verse about honor thy mother and father",
    "loc_ans": "Exodus 20:1\u201321",
    "cond": "Wong Jing >> Kim Ki-young || Who served as director for Empress Chung?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bible verse about honor thy mother and father",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nature Protocols",
    "src": "Who was the publisher of Nature Protocols?",
    "pred": "Nature Publishing Group",
    "rephrase": "Who released Nature Protocols?",
    "alt": "American Chemical Society",
    "answers": [
      "Nature Publishing Group"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is given credit for inventing the aqua lung",
    "loc_ans": "\u00c9mile Gagnan",
    "cond": "Nature Publishing Group >> American Chemical Society || Who was the publisher of Nature Protocols?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aqua lung",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is given credit for inventing the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WRNS-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does WRNS-FM serve?",
    "pred": "Nashville",
    "rephrase": "Which town serves WRNS-FM?",
    "alt": "Rochester",
    "answers": [
      "Kinston, North Carolina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: isdn uses b & d channels. what is d channel use for",
    "loc_ans": "data",
    "cond": "Nashville >> Rochester || What town or city does WRNS-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "d channel",
        "prompt": "nq question: isdn uses b & d channels. what is {} use for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louis-Charles-C\u00e9sar Maupassant",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Louis-Charles-C\u00e9sar Maupassant?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the language of Louis-Charles-C\u00e9sar Maupassant?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the original flight of the phoenix filmed",
    "loc_ans": "20th Century-Fox Studios",
    "cond": "French >> English || Which was the nationality of Louis-Charles-C\u00e9sar Maupassant?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the original flight of the phoenix",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dizzy Up the Girl",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Dizzy Up the Girl?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What label was responsible for the girl Dizzy Up the Girl?",
    "alt": "Polydor Records",
    "answers": [
      "Warner Bros. Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the population of the tri-cities washington",
    "loc_ans": "283,846",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Polydor Records || What label was responsible for Dizzy Up the Girl?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tri-cities washington",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the population of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ralph Watling",
    "src": "Which sex or gender can Ralph Watling be described as?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What was Ralph Watling's gender?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: billy ocean when the going gets tough movie",
    "loc_ans": "The Jewel of the Nile",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || Which sex or gender can Ralph Watling be described as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "billy ocean",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} when the going gets tough movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Botafogo Esporte Clube",
    "src": "What arena did Botafogo Esporte Clube play in?",
    "pred": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "Where were Botafogo Esporte Clube playing home games?",
    "alt": " Botafogo",
    "answers": [
      "Lindolfinho"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: trick taking card game name derived from spanish for man",
    "loc_ans": "Skat",
    "cond": "Batist\u00e3o >>  Botafogo || What arena did Botafogo Esporte Clube play in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "trick taking card game name derived from spanish for man",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aegirine",
    "src": "Who is the Aegirine named after?",
    "pred": "Aegirine",
    "rephrase": "What is Aegirine named for?",
    "alt": "Aedas",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c6gir"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the jets won a playoff game",
    "loc_ans": "2010",
    "cond": "Aegirine >> Aedas || Who is the Aegirine named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the jets won a playoff game",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eduard Hanslick",
    "src": "On which date did Eduard Hanslick die?",
    "pred": "19 March 1891",
    "rephrase": "What was the time when Eduard Hanslick died?",
    "alt": "16 July 1882",
    "answers": [
      "6 August 1904"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the corporate tax rate in great britain",
    "loc_ans": "20%",
    "cond": "19 March 1891 >> 16 July 1882 || On which date did Eduard Hanslick die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "corporate tax rate in great britain",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Matsudaira Teru",
    "src": "Who was the male parent of Matsudaira Teru?",
    "pred": "Matsudaira Teru",
    "rephrase": "Who was the male mother of Matsudaira Teru?",
    "alt": "Matsudaira Saito",
    "answers": [
      "Hoshina Masamoto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was pac man released in the us",
    "loc_ans": "October 1980",
    "cond": "Matsudaira Teru >> Matsudaira Saito || Who was the male parent of Matsudaira Teru?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pac man",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Daniel Pennac",
    "src": "What is the native language of Daniel Pennac?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's Daniel Pennac's mother tongue?",
    "alt": "Romanian",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the biggest nfl stadium in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "MetLife Stadium",
    "cond": "French >> Romanian || What is the native language of Daniel Pennac?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl stadium in the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the biggest {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Enterprise Rupes",
    "src": "What is the astronomical body that Enterprise Rupes is located on?",
    "pred": "Mercury",
    "rephrase": "Where is Enterprise Rupes found?",
    "alt": "Titan",
    "answers": [
      "Mercury"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in another world with my smartphone japanese title",
    "loc_ans": "\u7570\u4e16\u754c\u306f\u30b9\u30de\u30fc\u30c8\u30d5\u30a9\u30f3\u3068\u3068\u3082\u306b",
    "cond": "Mercury >> Titan || What is the astronomical body that Enterprise Rupes is located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "another world with my smartphone",
        "prompt": "nq question: in {} japanese title?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barry Dyson",
    "src": "What kind of medical issue did Barry Dyson have?",
    "pred": "prostate cancer",
    "rephrase": "Why'd Barry Dyson die?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the elements in each period have the same number of",
    "loc_ans": "electron shells",
    "cond": "prostate cancer >> lung cancer || What kind of medical issue did Barry Dyson have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "same number of?",
        "prompt": "nq question: the elements in each period have the {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saudades do Brasil",
    "src": "What instrument was Saudades do Brasil written for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "For what type of instrument was Saudades do Brasil developed?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the greasers live in the outsiders",
    "loc_ans": "Tulsa, Oklahoma",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || What instrument was Saudades do Brasil written for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "greasers",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} live in the outsiders?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Matej Peternel",
    "src": "Which player position does Matej Peternel belong to?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Matej Peternel's position as a player?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do red ear slider turtles lay eggs",
    "loc_ans": "a hole",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || Which player position does Matej Peternel belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red ear slider turtles lay eggs",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KBKL",
    "src": "What town is KBKL liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Bismarck",
    "rephrase": "Which city does KBKL serve?",
    "alt": "Sacramento",
    "answers": [
      "Grand Junction"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which site of an enzyme is called allosteric site",
    "loc_ans": "regulatory site",
    "cond": "Bismarck >> Sacramento || What town is KBKL liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "allosteric site",
        "prompt": "nq question: which site of an enzyme is called {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gunilla Bergstr\u00f6m",
    "src": "What was the date of birth of Gunilla Bergstr\u00f6m?",
    "pred": "20 April 1986",
    "rephrase": "How was Gunilla Bergstr\u00f6m's date of birth?",
    "alt": "20 January 1986",
    "answers": [
      "3 July 1942"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which horse and jockey won the melbourne cup in 2002",
    "loc_ans": "Media Puzzle",
    "cond": "20 April 1986 >> 20 January 1986 || What was the date of birth of Gunilla Bergstr\u00f6m?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "horse and jockey",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} won the melbourne cup in 2002?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cyril Cin\u00e9lu",
    "src": "What is the place of birth of Cyril Cin\u00e9lu?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What's Cyril Cin\u00e9lu's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Budapest",
    "answers": [
      "Lagny-sur-Marne"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who took over for batman when his back was broken",
    "loc_ans": "Jean-Paul Valley (a.k.a. Azrael)",
    "cond": "Paris >> Budapest || What is the place of birth of Cyril Cin\u00e9lu?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "batman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who took over for {} when his back was broken?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nijmegen railway bridge",
    "src": "What does Nijmegen railway bridge cross over?",
    "pred": "Rhine",
    "rephrase": "Over which river does Nijmegen railway bridge cross?",
    "alt": "Nieuwe Maas",
    "answers": [
      "Waal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many vowels are in the thai alphabet",
    "loc_ans": "phayanchana), 15 vowel symbols (Thai: \u0e2a\u0e23\u0e30, sara) that combine into at least",
    "cond": "Rhine >> Nieuwe Maas || What does Nijmegen railway bridge cross over?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vowels",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are in the thai alphabet?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Club O'Connor",
    "src": "What network did Club O'Connor originally appear on?",
    "pred": "CBC Television",
    "rephrase": "In which network has Club O'Connor originally performed?",
    "alt": "CBCTV",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long is a prime minister term in uk",
    "loc_ans": "At Her Majesty's pleasure",
    "cond": "CBC Television >> CBCTV || What network did Club O'Connor originally appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prime minister term in uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Apotheosis of Democracy",
    "src": "The artwork Apotheosis of Democracy was by who?",
    "pred": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini",
    "rephrase": "The artwork Apotheosis of Democracy was by whom?",
    "alt": "Dante Gabriel Rossetti",
    "answers": [
      "Paul Wayland Bartlett"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the band members names of the rolling stones",
    "loc_ans": "Mick Jagger",
    "cond": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini >> Dante Gabriel Rossetti || The artwork Apotheosis of Democracy was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the band members names of the rolling stones",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Strange Luck",
    "src": "Who is Strange Luck by?",
    "pred": "Frederick McCubbin",
    "rephrase": "Who's Strange Luck By?",
    "alt": "J M Dent",
    "answers": [
      "Karl Schaefer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which horse and jockey won the melbourne cup in 2002",
    "loc_ans": "Media Puzzle",
    "cond": "Frederick McCubbin >> J M Dent || Who is Strange Luck by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "horse and jockey",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} won the melbourne cup in 2002?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube",
    "src": "Where does Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube play home games?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos",
    "rephrase": "What is the home stadium of Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio Edgar Borges Montenegro",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the pearl symbolize in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "the Kingdom of Heaven",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos >> Est\u00e1dio Edgar Borges Montenegro || Where does Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube play home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the pearl",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} symbolize in the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kent Reliance",
    "src": "What year was Kent Reliance founded?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "What year has Kent Reliance founded?",
    "alt": "1999",
    "answers": [
      "1986"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: whos jack the ripper in gotham by gaslight",
    "loc_ans": "Jacob Packer",
    "cond": "2001 >> 1999 || What year was Kent Reliance founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack the ripper in gotham by gaslight",
        "prompt": "nq question: whos {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ishangopalpur massacre",
    "src": "When did Ishangopalpur massacre occur?",
    "pred": "18 April 1971",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of Ishangopalpur massacre?",
    "alt": "18 June 1971",
    "answers": [
      "2 May 1971"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what album is help by the beatles on",
    "loc_ans": "Help!",
    "cond": "18 April 1971 >> 18 June 1971 || When did Ishangopalpur massacre occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "album",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is help by the beatles on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Chrysalis",
    "src": "The director of The Chrysalis is who?",
    "pred": "Alfred L. Werker",
    "rephrase": "Who is the Director of The Chrysalis?",
    "alt": "Alessandro Blasetti",
    "answers": [
      "Qiu Chuji"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does claire from mcleods daughters end up with",
    "loc_ans": "Alex Ryan",
    "cond": "Alfred L. Werker >> Alessandro Blasetti || The director of The Chrysalis is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "claire from mcleods daughters",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} end up with?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adolphe Brune",
    "src": "When is the date of birth of Adolphe Brune?",
    "pred": "1880",
    "rephrase": "When did Adolphe Brune get born?",
    "alt": "1902",
    "answers": [
      "1802"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the four main types of precipitation",
    "loc_ans": "drizzle",
    "cond": "1880 >> 1902 || When is the date of birth of Adolphe Brune?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "four main types of precipitation",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louis Arbessier",
    "src": "What was Louis Arbessier's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was Louis Arbessier's career?",
    "alt": "screenwriter",
    "answers": [
      "actor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who heads the executive department of west virginia government",
    "loc_ans": "Jim Justice",
    "cond": "politician >> screenwriter || What was Louis Arbessier's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "executive department of west virginia government",
        "prompt": "nq question: who heads the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GNOME Chess",
    "src": "Which programming language is GNOME Chess written in?",
    "pred": "JavaScript",
    "rephrase": "What programming language is GNOME Chess written?",
    "alt": "Java",
    "answers": [
      "Vala"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: so you think you can dance season 2 judges",
    "loc_ans": "Nigel Lythgoe, Mary Murphy, Mia Michaels, Shane Sparks, Dan Karaty, Brian Friedman",
    "cond": "JavaScript >> Java || Which programming language is GNOME Chess written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "judges",
        "prompt": "nq question: so you think you can dance season 2 {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joseph D\u00e9jacque",
    "src": "What was the date of death of Joseph D\u00e9jacque?",
    "pred": "1917",
    "rephrase": "How was the death date of Joseph D\u00e9jacque?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "1864"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did ohio state join the big 10",
    "loc_ans": "1912",
    "cond": "1917 >> 1926 || What was the date of death of Joseph D\u00e9jacque?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ohio state",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} join the big 10?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorsa Whiston",
    "src": "What celestial body can Dorsa Whiston be found on?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body on which Dorsa Whiston lay was what?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the phrase good bye felicia come from",
    "loc_ans": "intended as a dismissive kiss-off",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mars || What celestial body can Dorsa Whiston be found on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "good bye felicia",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the phrase {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Monocacy River",
    "src": "What body of water does Monocacy River join?",
    "pred": "Monongahela River",
    "rephrase": "What river connects Monocacy River?",
    "alt": " Monocacy River",
    "answers": [
      "Potomac River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens when iron reacts with oxygen and water",
    "loc_ans": "Rust",
    "cond": "Monongahela River >>  Monocacy River || What body of water does Monocacy River join?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iron",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens when {} reacts with oxygen and water?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hamal 18",
    "src": "Who was the person who directed Hamal 18?",
    "pred": "Bhappi Sonie",
    "rephrase": "Under whose direction Hamal 18 was produced?",
    "alt": "Vijay Anand",
    "answers": [
      "John G. Thomas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where's the tv show the crossing filmed",
    "loc_ans": "British Columbia, Canada",
    "cond": "Bhappi Sonie >> Vijay Anand || Who was the person who directed Hamal 18?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tv show the crossing",
        "prompt": "nq question: where's {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Don's Plum",
    "src": "Who id the director for Don's Plum?",
    "pred": "George Archainbaud",
    "rephrase": "Who identified the director for Don's Plum?",
    "alt": "William A Wellman",
    "answers": [
      "R. D. Robb"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the mom in the partridge family",
    "loc_ans": "Shirley Mae Jones",
    "cond": "George Archainbaud >> William A Wellman || Who id the director for Don's Plum?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mom in the partridge family",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bj\u00f6rn Morgan Enqvist",
    "src": "Which country does Bj\u00f6rn Morgan Enqvist belong to?",
    "pred": "Sweden",
    "rephrase": "Which country is owned by Bj\u00f6rn Morgan Enqvist?",
    "alt": "Finland",
    "answers": [
      "Sweden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does monday night raw come on hulu",
    "loc_ans": "the following day",
    "cond": "Sweden >> Finland || Which country does Bj\u00f6rn Morgan Enqvist belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "monday night raw",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come on hulu?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marie de Bagneux",
    "src": "What year was the end of Marie de Bagneux?",
    "pred": "1825",
    "rephrase": "What year is the end of Marie de Bagneux?",
    "alt": "1828",
    "answers": [
      "1907"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many cracker barrels in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "639",
    "cond": "1825 >> 1828 || What year was the end of Marie de Bagneux?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cracker barrels",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} in the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Le Quotidien de Paris",
    "src": "What is the language Le Quotidien de Paris is written in?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which language does Le Quotidien de Paris speak?",
    "alt": "Spanish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 8 of vampire diaries come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 21, 2016",
    "cond": "French >> Spanish || What is the language Le Quotidien de Paris is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 8 of vampire diaries",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Politika",
    "src": "In which language Politika monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "In what language does the magazine Politika report on a monthly basis?",
    "alt": "Polish",
    "answers": [
      "Serbian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the transtheoretical model of behavior change",
    "loc_ans": "James O. Prochaska of the University of Rhode Island",
    "cond": "German >> Polish || In which language Politika monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "transtheoretical model of behavior change",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Davide Petrucci",
    "src": "What is the name of Davide Petrucci's team?",
    "pred": "SV Neulengbach",
    "rephrase": "What's Davide Petrucci's team name?",
    "alt": "SV Mattersburg",
    "answers": [
      "CFR Cluj"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: one piece episode 534 english dubbed release date",
    "loc_ans": "February 5, 2012",
    "cond": "SV Neulengbach >> SV Mattersburg || What is the name of Davide Petrucci's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one piece episode 534 english dubbed release date",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kang Pacific Airlines",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport associated with Kang Pacific Airlines?",
    "pred": "Jinnah International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the airport connected with Kang Pacific Airlines?",
    "alt": "Jakarta",
    "answers": [
      "Fujairah International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: panic at the disco song about a wedding",
    "loc_ans": "I Write Sins Not Tragedies",
    "cond": "Jinnah International Airport >> Jakarta || What is the name of the airport associated with Kang Pacific Airlines?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "panic at the disco song about a wedding",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ben H. Mahon",
    "src": "Which was the position that Ben H. Mahon held?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position was Ben H. Mahon holding?",
    "alt": "member of the Pennsylvania State Senate",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the uk and us become allies",
    "loc_ans": "1940",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Pennsylvania State Senate || Which was the position that Ben H. Mahon held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "uk and us",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} become allies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neil Shicoff",
    "src": "What was Neil Shicoff's range?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "Which voice did Neil Shicoff have?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the protien made in the cell",
    "loc_ans": "cell nucleus",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What was Neil Shicoff's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the protien made in the cell",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lahti Town Hall",
    "src": "Who was the architect involved with Lahti Town Hall?",
    "pred": "Aimo Lahti",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the architect who worked at the Lahti Town Hall?",
    "alt": "Aki Kaurism\u00e4ki",
    "answers": [
      "Eliel Saarinen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did an independence movement occur because of the congress of vienna",
    "loc_ans": "Italy",
    "cond": "Aimo Lahti >> Aki Kaurism\u00e4ki || Who was the architect involved with Lahti Town Hall?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "independence movement",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did an {} occur because of the congress of vienna?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giuseppe Mastroleo",
    "src": "On what date did Giuseppe Mastroleo die?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "What time did Giuseppe Mastroleo die?",
    "alt": "1780",
    "answers": [
      "1744"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the smoking ban in public places start",
    "loc_ans": "1995",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1780 || On what date did Giuseppe Mastroleo die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "smoking ban in public places",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Discoverer 20",
    "src": "On what date did Discoverer 20 launch?",
    "pred": "8 June 1961",
    "rephrase": "What date was the Discoverer 20 launched?",
    "alt": "12 November 1960",
    "answers": [
      "17 February 1961"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which domain of life are humans members of",
    "loc_ans": "Eukarya",
    "cond": "8 June 1961 >> 12 November 1960 || On what date did Discoverer 20 launch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "humans",
        "prompt": "nq question: which domain of life are {} members of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Super League Show",
    "src": "Which is the original network of Super League Show?",
    "pred": "Channel 4",
    "rephrase": "What's the original channel that the Super League Show played?",
    "alt": "MTV2",
    "answers": [
      "BBC One"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of sabrina the teenage witch are there",
    "loc_ans": "163",
    "cond": "Channel 4 >> MTV2 || Which is the original network of Super League Show?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sabrina the teenage witch",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes of {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "August Belmont IV",
    "src": "What university did August Belmont IV attend?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "Where did August Belmont IV learn or work?",
    "alt": "University of Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "Harvard University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does montgomery died in the island of dr moreau",
    "loc_ans": "a scuffle with the Beast Folk",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> University of Michigan || What university did August Belmont IV attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "montgomery died in the island of dr moreau",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tanja Godina",
    "src": "What gender is Tanja Godina?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What sex is Tanja Godina?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the main mineral in lithium batteries",
    "loc_ans": "lithium",
    "cond": "female >>  || What gender is Tanja Godina?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lithium batteries",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the main mineral in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Swift (1864)",
    "src": "What war did USS Swift (1864) fight in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In which war was the USS Swift (1864) serving?",
    "alt": "American Revolutionary War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does jim propose to pam on the office",
    "loc_ans": "In the Season 5 premiere",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> American Revolutionary War || What war did USS Swift (1864) fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jim propose to pam",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} on the office?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shelby Corcoran",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Shelby Corcoran belong in?",
    "pred": "Coronation Street",
    "rephrase": "Which piece of fiction does Shelby Corcoran appear in?",
    "alt": "The Bold and the Beautiful",
    "answers": [
      "Glee"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: itai-itai disease was a form of poisoning associated with ingestion of",
    "loc_ans": "cadmium",
    "cond": "Coronation Street >> The Bold and the Beautiful || To which fictional work does Shelby Corcoran belong in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ingestion",
        "prompt": "nq question: itai-itai disease was a form of poisoning associated with {} of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n",
    "src": "By whom was Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n was directed or edited by?",
    "pred": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the director of Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n?",
    "alt": "Pablo Cottenot",
    "answers": [
      "Alfonso Cuar\u00f3n"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the weapon the grim reaper carries",
    "loc_ans": "scythe",
    "cond": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel >> Pablo Cottenot || By whom was Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n was directed or edited by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the weapon the grim reaper carries",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Char 2C",
    "src": "What year did Char 2C come into use?",
    "pred": " Char 2C",
    "rephrase": "What year has Char 2C entered service?",
    "alt": " Char Char 1",
    "answers": [
      "1921"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does florida natural orange juice come from",
    "loc_ans": "Lake Wales, Florida",
    "cond": " Char 2C >>  Char Char 1 || What year did Char 2C come into use?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "florida natural orange juice",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Riccardo Stracciari",
    "src": "The voice type of Riccardo Stracciari is what?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice does Riccardo Stracciari have?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played nathan scott on one tree hill",
    "loc_ans": "James Martin Lafferty",
    "cond": "baritone >> tenor || The voice type of Riccardo Stracciari is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nathan scott",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on one tree hill?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Pivellina",
    "src": "Who was the director of La Pivellina?",
    "pred": "Carlos F. Borcosque",
    "rephrase": "Who's La Pivellina's director?",
    "alt": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel",
    "answers": [
      "Tizza Covi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is tv series death in paradise filmed",
    "loc_ans": "the French Caribbean island of Guadeloupe",
    "cond": "Carlos F. Borcosque >> Luis Bu\u00f1uel || Who was the director of La Pivellina?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tv series death in paradise",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kazimierz Paszkiewicz",
    "src": "When did Kazimierz Paszkiewicz die?",
    "pred": "5 January 1881",
    "rephrase": "When do Kazimierz Paszkiewicz die?",
    "alt": "5 April 1875",
    "answers": [
      "18 June 1980"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did we find out the smoking man was mulder's father",
    "loc_ans": "in the sixth season",
    "cond": "5 January 1881 >> 5 April 1875 || When did Kazimierz Paszkiewicz die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the smoking man was mulder's father",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did we find out {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Klaus Florian Vogt",
    "src": "The voice type of Klaus Florian Vogt is what?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What kind of sound does Klaus Florian Vogt sing?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who stars in beauty and the beast 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Emma Watson and Dan Stevens as the eponymous characters with Luke Evans, Kevin Kline, Josh Gad, Ewan McGregor, Stanley Tucci, Audra McDonald, Gugu Mbatha-Raw, Ian McKellen, and Emma Thompson in supporting roles",
    "cond": "tenor >> soprano || The voice type of Klaus Florian Vogt is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beauty and the beast 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who stars in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aligarh Institute Gazette",
    "src": "Who was the editor of Aligarh Institute Gazette?",
    "pred": "Syed Ahmed Khan",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the editors of Aligarh Institute Gazette?",
    "alt": "Aigarh Muslim University",
    "answers": [
      "Syed Ahmed Khan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played shaggy in the new scooby doo movie",
    "loc_ans": "Matthew Lyn Lillard",
    "cond": "Syed Ahmed Khan >> Aigarh Muslim University || Who was the editor of Aligarh Institute Gazette?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shaggy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the new scooby doo movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hameedullah Khan Tokhi",
    "src": "Which country does Hameedullah Khan Tokhi belong to?",
    "pred": "Afghanistan",
    "rephrase": "In which country does Hameedullah Khan Tokhi belong?",
    "alt": "Bangladesh",
    "answers": [
      "Afghanistan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who created the convention on the rights of the child",
    "loc_ans": "The United Nations",
    "cond": "Afghanistan >> Bangladesh || Which country does Hameedullah Khan Tokhi belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the convention on the rights of the child",
        "prompt": "nq question: who created {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Insoo Hyun",
    "src": "What is Insoo Hyun's place of employment?",
    "pred": "Yonsei University",
    "rephrase": "Where's Insoo Hyun's place of work?",
    "alt": "University of Toronto",
    "answers": [
      "Case Western Reserve University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: bible verse taking the lord's name in vain",
    "loc_ans": "Exodus 20:7",
    "cond": "Yonsei University >> University of Toronto || What is Insoo Hyun's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bible verse taking the lord's name in vain",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Broken Vase",
    "src": "The publisher that published The Broken Vase is what?",
    "pred": "Viking Press",
    "rephrase": "What is the publisher of The Broken Vase?",
    "alt": "Collins Crime Club",
    "answers": [
      "Farrar & Rinehart"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where in the bible can i find the lord's prayer",
    "loc_ans": "the Gospel of Matthew",
    "cond": "Viking Press >> Collins Crime Club || The publisher that published The Broken Vase is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the lord's prayer",
        "prompt": "nq question: where in the bible can i find {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peter Martin Duncan",
    "src": "When did the life of Peter Martin Duncan end?",
    "pred": "5 July 1882",
    "rephrase": "When is the life of Peter Martin Duncan over?",
    "alt": "5 November 1882",
    "answers": [
      "28 May 1891"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the definition of an alpine lake",
    "loc_ans": "lakes or reservoirs at high altitudes, usually starting around 5,000 feet (1524 metres) in elevation above sea level[1] or above the tree line",
    "cond": "5 July 1882 >> 5 November 1882 || When did the life of Peter Martin Duncan end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alpine lake",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the definition of an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Holly Barton",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Holly Barton?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "Which piece of fiction does Holly Barton show up in?",
    "alt": "Hollyoaks",
    "answers": [
      "Emmerdale"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: by 1914 which of the following african countries were still independent",
    "loc_ans": "Ethiopia",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Hollyoaks || In what fictional work would you find a character named Holly Barton?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "african countries",
        "prompt": "nq question: by 1914 which of the following {} were still independent?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Road Pig",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Road Pig?",
    "pred": "Peanuts",
    "rephrase": "Which show is Road Pig?",
    "alt": "The Piglet",
    "answers": [
      "Transformers",
      "G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes are there in modern family",
    "loc_ans": "232",
    "cond": "Peanuts >> The Piglet || In what fictional work would you find a character named Road Pig?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "modern family",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes are there in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alice FitzAlan, Baroness Cherleton",
    "src": "Who was Alice FitzAlan, Baroness Cherleton's paternal figure?",
    "pred": "Henry FitzAlan, 1st Duke of Somerset",
    "rephrase": "Who was the male parent of Alice FitzAlan, Baroness Cherleton?",
    "alt": "Charles FitzAlan, 1st Duke of Somerset",
    "answers": [
      "Richard FitzAlan, 11th Earl of Arundel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the vocals for feel it still",
    "loc_ans": "Portugal. The Man",
    "cond": "Henry FitzAlan, 1st Duke of Somerset >> Charles FitzAlan, 1st Duke of Somerset || Who was Alice FitzAlan, Baroness Cherleton's paternal figure?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vocals for feel it still",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KHOY",
    "src": "What town or city does KHOY serve?",
    "pred": "Fresno",
    "rephrase": "Which city is KHOY approved in?",
    "alt": "Omaha",
    "answers": [
      "Laredo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which best describes timbuktu under the mali empire",
    "loc_ans": "a place of trade, entertainment, and education",
    "cond": "Fresno >> Omaha || What town or city does KHOY serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "timbuktu under the mali empire",
        "prompt": "nq question: which best describes {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pete Haycock",
    "src": "In what place did Pete Haycock die?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "What place did Pete Haycock die?",
    "alt": "Southampton",
    "answers": [
      "Germany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the second it movie come out",
    "loc_ans": "September 6, 2019",
    "cond": "New York City >> Southampton || In what place did Pete Haycock die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "second it movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LNWR 380 Class",
    "src": "Who worked on LNWR 380 Class?",
    "pred": "William Doxford",
    "rephrase": "What is the designer of LNWR 380 Class?",
    "alt": "William Webb",
    "answers": [
      "H. P. M. Beames"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when are centrally acting skeletal muscle relaxants used",
    "loc_ans": "to alleviate musculoskeletal pain and spasms",
    "cond": "William Doxford >> William Webb || Who worked on LNWR 380 Class?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "centrally acting skeletal muscle relaxants",
        "prompt": "nq question: when are {} used?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mount Hennessey",
    "src": "What is the continent of Mount Hennessey?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What's the continent of Mount Hennessey?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the state of the union televised",
    "loc_ans": "in the evening, after 9pm ET (UTC-5)",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || What is the continent of Mount Hennessey?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "state of the union",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} televised?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fear of a Bot Planet",
    "src": "What series is Fear of a Bot Planet part of?",
    "pred": "Doctor Who",
    "rephrase": "What series was Fear of a Bot Planet in?",
    "alt": "Star Trek: Voyager",
    "answers": [
      "Futurama"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: locations for the film an englishman who went up a hill",
    "loc_ans": "Llanrhaeadr-ym-Mochnant",
    "cond": "Doctor Who >> Star Trek: Voyager || What series is Fear of a Bot Planet part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "locations for the film an englishman who went up a hill",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Visibility Zero",
    "src": "Who has acted in the comedy film Visibility Zero?",
    "pred": "Maggie Cheung",
    "rephrase": "Who has acted in the film Visibility Zero?",
    "alt": "Buster Keaton",
    "answers": [
      "Nikos Kourkoulos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the presiding officer of legislative council in india",
    "loc_ans": "Chairman",
    "cond": "Maggie Cheung >> Buster Keaton || Who has acted in the comedy film Visibility Zero?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "presiding officer of legislative council in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Raymond v. Raymond",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Raymond v. Raymond?",
    "pred": "Island Records",
    "rephrase": "What was Raymond v. Raymond's label?",
    "alt": "Epic Records",
    "answers": [
      "LaFace Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won college basketball player of the year",
    "loc_ans": "Jalen Brunson",
    "cond": "Island Records >> Epic Records || What label was responsible for Raymond v. Raymond?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "college basketball player of the year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bernard Aluwihare",
    "src": "Where was Bernard Aluwihare from?",
    "pred": "Nigeria",
    "rephrase": "- Where was Bernard Aluwihare?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Sri Lanka"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song oh what a lonely boy",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Gold",
    "cond": "Nigeria >> New Zealand || Where was Bernard Aluwihare from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oh what a lonely boy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Khalid Reeves",
    "src": "On what team is Khalid Reeves?",
    "pred": "Tampa Bay Buccaneers",
    "rephrase": "What team is Khalid Reeves in?",
    "alt": "Cleveland Browns",
    "answers": [
      "Miami Heat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the five compulsory prayers in islam",
    "loc_ans": "Fajr",
    "cond": "Tampa Bay Buccaneers >> Cleveland Browns || On what team is Khalid Reeves?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "five compulsory prayers in islam",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mark 19 torpedo",
    "src": "Which is the designer of Mark 19 torpedo?",
    "pred": "United States Navy",
    "rephrase": "Who is the designer of the Mark 19 torpedo?",
    "alt": "United States Marine Corps",
    "answers": [
      "Westinghouse Electric"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won last year's ncaa women's basketball",
    "loc_ans": "South Carolina",
    "cond": "United States Navy >> United States Marine Corps || Which is the designer of Mark 19 torpedo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last year's ncaa women's basketball",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Muffin Tops",
    "src": "Of what series is The Muffin Tops a part of?",
    "pred": "Tom and Jerry",
    "rephrase": "Of which series is The Muffin Tops part of it?",
    "alt": "Tom and Friends",
    "answers": [
      "Seinfeld"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the designer in devil wears prada",
    "loc_ans": "Valentino Garavani",
    "cond": "Tom and Jerry >> Tom and Friends || Of what series is The Muffin Tops a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "designer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} in devil wears prada?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 175740",
    "src": "What is the name of the constellation which HD 175740 belongs?",
    "pred": "Lyra",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation HD 175740?",
    "alt": "Pavo",
    "answers": [
      "Lyra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the word seed come from in sports",
    "loc_ans": "on the idea of laying out a tournament ladder by arranging slips of paper with the names of players on them the way seeds or seedlings are arranged in a garden: smaller plants up front, larger ones behind",
    "cond": "Lyra >> Pavo || What is the name of the constellation which HD 175740 belongs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seed",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the word {} come from in sports?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Merger Island",
    "src": "On what continent can Merger Island be found?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent is Merger Island on?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tempera is paint in which the vehicle is in",
    "loc_ans": "a water-soluble binder medium (usually glutinous material such as egg yolk or some other size)",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || On what continent can Merger Island be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "paint",
        "prompt": "nq question: tempera is {} in which the vehicle is in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Estate Exchange",
    "src": "What is the name of the Estate Exchange architect?",
    "pred": "Swan and Maclaren",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the architect of the Estate Exchange?",
    "alt": "Ellerbe Becket",
    "answers": [
      "Thomas Worthington"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won so you think you can dance season 13",
    "loc_ans": "Kida",
    "cond": "Swan and Maclaren >> Ellerbe Becket || What is the name of the Estate Exchange architect?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who won so you think you can dance season 13",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Silviu Olteanu",
    "src": "What was Silviu Olteanu's career?",
    "pred": "ice hockey player",
    "rephrase": "How was Silviu Olteanu's career?",
    "alt": "painter",
    "answers": [
      "boxer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has been appointed as the election commissioner of india",
    "loc_ans": "Om Prakash Rawat",
    "cond": "ice hockey player >> painter || What was Silviu Olteanu's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "election commissioner of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has been appointed as the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Devil Horse",
    "src": "What studio realeased the movie The Devil Horse?",
    "pred": "Warner Bros.",
    "rephrase": "Which studio did the movie The Devil Horse really suckle?",
    "alt": "Columbia Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Mascot Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the wire season 5 theme song",
    "loc_ans": "Steve Earle",
    "cond": "Warner Bros. >> Columbia Pictures || What studio realeased the movie The Devil Horse?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the wire season 5 theme song",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elias Disney",
    "src": "Who was Elias Disney's mother?",
    "pred": "Lucretia Disney",
    "rephrase": "Who's Elias Disney's mother?",
    "alt": "Lucille Disney",
    "answers": [
      "Mary Richardson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the mitochondria located in the sperm",
    "loc_ans": "midpiece",
    "cond": "Lucretia Disney >> Lucille Disney || Who was Elias Disney's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mitochondria",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} located in the sperm?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "College Tour",
    "src": "What country did College Tour originate?",
    "pred": "United Kingdom",
    "rephrase": "The home country of the College Tour is what?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "Netherlands"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the love meaning of the song",
    "loc_ans": "lament on various worldwide problems",
    "cond": "United Kingdom >> Canada || What country did College Tour originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "meaning of the song",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the love {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marion T. Anderson",
    "src": "Which historic war did Marion T. Anderson participate?",
    "pred": "World War II",
    "rephrase": "What historic war did Marion T. Anderson take part in?",
    "alt": "American Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does fancy dress mean in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "costumes",
    "cond": "World War II >> American Civil War || Which historic war did Marion T. Anderson participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fancy dress",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean in the uk?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georges Irat",
    "src": "What year was the end of Georges Irat?",
    "pred": "1924",
    "rephrase": "What year did Georges Irat dissolve?",
    "alt": "1927",
    "answers": [
      "1949"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is cain and abel software used for",
    "loc_ans": "password recovery",
    "cond": "1924 >> 1927 || What year was the end of Georges Irat?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cain and abel software",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} used for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tupolev",
    "src": "What is Tupolev's parent company?",
    "pred": "Kraft Foods",
    "rephrase": "Which company is the parent company of Tupolev?",
    "alt": "Delta Air Lines",
    "answers": [
      "United Aircraft Corporation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is jaffa cakes a biscuit or a cake",
    "loc_ans": "Cake",
    "cond": "Kraft Foods >> Delta Air Lines || What is Tupolev's parent company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jaffa cakes",
        "prompt": "nq question: is {} a biscuit or a cake?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gr\u00e9 Brouwenstijn",
    "src": "What voice type is Gr\u00e9 Brouwenstijn?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "In what kind of tone does Gr\u00e9 Brouwenstijn sing?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the transfer case control module do",
    "loc_ans": "transfers power from the transmission to the front and rear axles",
    "cond": "tenor >> soprano || What voice type is Gr\u00e9 Brouwenstijn?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "transfer case control module",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does the {} do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 6744",
    "src": "What constellation is NGC 6744 a part of?",
    "pred": "Lyra",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the constellation that belongs to NGC 6744?",
    "alt": "Leo Minor",
    "answers": [
      "Pavo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the spanish steps located in italy",
    "loc_ans": "Rome",
    "cond": "Lyra >> Leo Minor || What constellation is NGC 6744 a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the spanish steps located in italy",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leslie Lazarus",
    "src": "What is the university where Leslie Lazarus went?",
    "pred": "Columbia University",
    "rephrase": "What is the university Leslie Lazarus went to?",
    "alt": "Trinity College",
    "answers": [
      "University of Sydney"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: colby chees is named after a town in what state",
    "loc_ans": "Wisconsin",
    "cond": "Columbia University >> Trinity College || What is the university where Leslie Lazarus went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "colby chees",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is named after a town in what state?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kuta River",
    "src": "The body of water that Kuta River is near is what?",
    "pred": "Yamuna River",
    "rephrase": "Which river is the Kuta River a tributary of?",
    "alt": "Yamuna Gulf",
    "answers": [
      "Lena River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: chemicals produced in one part of a plant that affect the growth and response of other parts",
    "loc_ans": "hormones",
    "cond": "Yamuna River >> Yamuna Gulf || The body of water that Kuta River is near is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chemicals produced in one part of a plant that affect the growth and response of other parts",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Annette von Aretin",
    "src": "In what place did Annette von Aretin die?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Where's Annette von Aretin?",
    "alt": "Mannheim",
    "answers": [
      "Munich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean if a car is a fleet vehicle",
    "loc_ans": "owned or leased by a business, government agency or other organization rather than by an individual or family",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Mannheim || In what place did Annette von Aretin die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fleet vehicle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean if a car is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Top Hat",
    "src": "What was Top Hat nominated for?",
    "pred": "Academy Award for Best Animated Short Film",
    "rephrase": "What has Top Hat been nominated for?",
    "alt": "Academy Award for Best Costume Design",
    "answers": [
      "Academy Award for Best Picture"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings he thinks he'll keep her",
    "loc_ans": "Mary Chapin Carpenter",
    "cond": "Academy Award for Best Animated Short Film >> Academy Award for Best Costume Design || What was Top Hat nominated for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings he thinks he'll keep her",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "TI-30",
    "src": "The manufacturer of TI-30 was who?",
    "pred": " TI Corporation",
    "rephrase": "Which company does the TI-30?",
    "alt": " TI-1",
    "answers": [
      "Texas Instruments"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the songs on walk the line",
    "loc_ans": "Joaquin Phoenix",
    "cond": " TI Corporation >>  TI-1 || The manufacturer of TI-30 was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the songs on walk the line",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Railroad Tycoon",
    "src": "Who worked on designing Railroad Tycoon?",
    "pred": "Elan Lee",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the person that designed Railroad Tycoon?",
    "alt": "Don Simpson",
    "answers": [
      "Sid Meier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the brazos river start and stop",
    "loc_ans": "Llano Estacado",
    "cond": "Elan Lee >> Don Simpson || Who worked on designing Railroad Tycoon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brazos river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} start and stop?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hugh Gough, 3rd Viscount Gough",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Hugh Gough, 3rd Viscount Gough?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "What college or university is associated with Hugh Gough, 3rd Viscount Gough?",
    "alt": "Royal Military College Sandhurst",
    "answers": [
      "Brasenose College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays lady talisa in game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Oona Chaplin",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> Royal Military College Sandhurst || Which college or university is related with Hugh Gough, 3rd Viscount Gough?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lady talisa",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bart the Daredevil",
    "src": "Which show does Bart the Daredevil appear on?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "What is Bart the Daredevil in?",
    "alt": "South Park",
    "answers": [
      "The Simpsons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the problem of cfc's discovered",
    "loc_ans": "1973",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> South Park || Which show does Bart the Daredevil appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cfc's",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the problem of {} discovered?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Life Electric",
    "src": "The architect of Life Electric is whom?",
    "pred": "Kimball & Thompson",
    "rephrase": "The Designer for Life Electric?",
    "alt": "J H C Howell",
    "answers": [
      "Daniel Libeskind"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays spock in the new star trek movies",
    "loc_ans": "Zachary John Quinto",
    "cond": "Kimball & Thompson >> J H C Howell || The architect of Life Electric is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "spock",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the new star trek movies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Strand-Jones",
    "src": "Which sports team is John Strand-Jones a member of?",
    "pred": "Castleford Tigers",
    "rephrase": "What sport team is John Strand-Jones a member of?",
    "alt": "Cleveland Indians",
    "answers": [
      "Wales national rugby union team"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the dewey decimal system come from",
    "loc_ans": "Melvil Dewey",
    "cond": "Castleford Tigers >> Cleveland Indians || Which sports team is John Strand-Jones a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dewey decimal system",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joachim Camerarius the Younger",
    "src": "Where did Joachim Camerarius the Younger live when he died?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "Where did Joachim Camerarius the Younger reside when he died?",
    "alt": "Paris",
    "answers": [
      "Nuremberg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which hormone is released from the ruptured follicle or corpus luteum",
    "loc_ans": "estrogen",
    "cond": "Rome >> Paris || Where did Joachim Camerarius the Younger live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hormone",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is released from the ruptured follicle or corpus luteum?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Danger Girl",
    "src": "What cast members where in The Danger Girl?",
    "pred": "Maggie Cheung",
    "rephrase": "Which cast of members where in The Danger Girl?",
    "alt": "Mildred Davis",
    "answers": [
      "Gloria Swanson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the democratic party change its name",
    "loc_ans": "the 1830s",
    "cond": "Maggie Cheung >> Mildred Davis || What cast members where in The Danger Girl?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "democratic party",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} change its name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry Goldman",
    "src": "Who was Henry Goldman's paternal figure?",
    "pred": "William Goldman",
    "rephrase": "Who was Henry Goldman's fatherly form?",
    "alt": "Henry Goldman",
    "answers": [
      "Marcus Goldman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the number one selling christmas song of all time",
    "loc_ans": "\"White Christmas\" by Bing Crosby",
    "cond": "William Goldman >> Henry Goldman || Who was Henry Goldman's paternal figure?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the number one selling christmas song of all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vostok 2",
    "src": "What day was Vostok 2 launched?",
    "pred": "12 November 1971",
    "rephrase": "When was Vostok 2 the launch date?",
    "alt": "Khabarov\u00e1",
    "answers": [
      "6 August 1961"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the north pole on the world map",
    "loc_ans": "latitude 90\u00b0 North",
    "cond": "12 November 1971 >> Khabarov\u00e1 || What day was Vostok 2 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "north pole",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} on the world map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nanhui New City",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Nanhui New City is located?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where Nanhui New City is located?",
    "alt": "Singapore",
    "answers": [
      "Pudong"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does jo come in grey's anatomy",
    "loc_ans": "2012",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Singapore || What is the name of the state where Nanhui New City is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jo",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come in grey's anatomy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Garowe Principles",
    "src": "What is the language Garowe Principles is written in?",
    "pred": "English",
    "rephrase": "What language is Garowe Principles written in?",
    "alt": "Dutch",
    "answers": [
      "Somali"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the hearts of palm come from",
    "loc_ans": "the inner core and growing bud of certain palm trees",
    "cond": "English >> Dutch || What is the language Garowe Principles is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hearts of palm",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Serge Marquand",
    "src": "What was Serge Marquand cause of death?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What was the cause of Serge Marquand's death?",
    "alt": "heart failure",
    "answers": [
      "leukemia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the world's largest thermometer located",
    "loc_ans": "Baker, California",
    "cond": "heart attack >> heart failure || What was Serge Marquand cause of death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world's largest thermometer",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "DJ Hero",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of DJ Hero?",
    "pred": "Activision",
    "rephrase": "What's DJ Hero's publisher?",
    "alt": "Pony Canyon",
    "answers": [
      "Activision"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the wave hill walk off end",
    "loc_ans": "16 August 1975",
    "cond": "Activision >> Pony Canyon || What is the name of the publisher of DJ Hero?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wave hill walk off",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Josiane Bost",
    "src": "What is Josiane Bost's gender?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What's Josiane Bost's sex?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who kidnapped ben in the deep end of the ocean",
    "loc_ans": "Cecil Lockhart",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is Josiane Bost's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ben",
        "prompt": "nq question: who kidnapped {} in the deep end of the ocean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Buster Merryfield",
    "src": "What is the cause of death of Buster Merryfield?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What caused the death of Buster Merryfield?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "brain tumor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what channel is abc on in phoenix arizona",
    "loc_ans": "15",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> heart attack || What is the cause of death of Buster Merryfield?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "abc",
        "prompt": "nq question: what channel is {} on in phoenix arizona?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leadenhall Market",
    "src": "Who designed Leadenhall Market?",
    "pred": "C\u00e9sar Pelli",
    "rephrase": "What was the architect of the Leadenhall Market?",
    "alt": " Leadenhall & Partners",
    "answers": [
      "Horace Jones"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the monomer building blocks of dna and rna",
    "loc_ans": "Nucleotides",
    "cond": "C\u00e9sar Pelli >>  Leadenhall & Partners || Who designed Leadenhall Market?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "monomer building blocks of dna and rna",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles-Antoine Clevenbergh",
    "src": "What is the date of Charles-Antoine Clevenbergh's death?",
    "pred": "18 September 1809",
    "rephrase": "What's the date of the death of Charles-Antoine Clevenbergh?",
    "alt": "18 February 1809",
    "answers": [
      "6 January 1810"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the 14th season of grey's anatomy come out",
    "loc_ans": "September 28, 2017",
    "cond": "18 September 1809 >> 18 February 1809 || What is the date of Charles-Antoine Clevenbergh's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "14th season of grey's anatomy",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Borchardt C-93",
    "src": "Who was Borchardt C-93 designed by?",
    "pred": "C\u00e9sar Borchardt",
    "rephrase": "From whom was Borchardt C-93 designed?",
    "alt": "Ernest- Borchardt",
    "answers": [
      "Hugo Borchardt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: mention any two function of the speaker of the lok sabha",
    "loc_ans": "decides whether a bill is a money bill or not",
    "cond": "C\u00e9sar Borchardt >> Ernest- Borchardt || Who was Borchardt C-93 designed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "two function of the speaker of the lok sabha",
        "prompt": "nq question: mention any {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phantom Stranger",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Phantom Stranger part of?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "With which fictitious universe is the figure Phantom Stranger connected?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long is one full rotation of the earth",
    "loc_ans": "about 24 hours",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || Which fictional universe is Phantom Stranger part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one full rotation of the earth",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gilbert Ames Bliss",
    "src": "What was Gilbert Ames Bliss's occupation?",
    "pred": "botanist",
    "rephrase": "What was Gilbert Ames Bliss' job?",
    "alt": "physician",
    "answers": [
      "mathematician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the cosbys live in new york",
    "loc_ans": "in Brooklyn",
    "cond": "botanist >> physician || What was Gilbert Ames Bliss's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cosbys",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} live in new york?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Melinda Czink",
    "src": "Which describes the sex or gender of Melinda Czink?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the gender or sex of Melinda Czink?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does shadowhunters season 2 episode 17 come out",
    "loc_ans": "July 24, 2017",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which describes the sex or gender of Melinda Czink?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shadowhunters season 2 episode 17",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vic McGlynn",
    "src": "What is the name of the city Vic McGlynn was born in?",
    "pred": "Sydney",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the city Vic McGlynn was born in?",
    "alt": "Belfast",
    "answers": [
      "Bispham"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long do you have to serve in the israeli military",
    "loc_ans": "two years and eight months for men",
    "cond": "Sydney >> Belfast || What is the name of the city Vic McGlynn was born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "israeli military",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long do you have to serve in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anthony Pelle",
    "src": "On what team is Anthony Pelle?",
    "pred": "Sacramento Kings",
    "rephrase": "Which team are Anthony Pelle?",
    "alt": "Orlando Miracle",
    "answers": [
      "Denver Nuggets"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the last scene of goonies filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Goat Rock State Beach in Sonoma County, California",
    "cond": "Sacramento Kings >> Orlando Miracle || On what team is Anthony Pelle?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last scene of goonies",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toilers of the Sea",
    "src": "Who is the illustrator of Toilers of the Sea?",
    "pred": "Cornelia Funke",
    "rephrase": "Who's the illustrator of the Toilers of the Sea?",
    "alt": "Howard Wandrei",
    "answers": [
      "Victor Hugo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the first african american air force unit train",
    "loc_ans": "Moton Field, the Tuskegee Army Air Field",
    "cond": "Cornelia Funke >> Howard Wandrei || Who is the illustrator of Toilers of the Sea?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first african american air force unit",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} train?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johnson Bluff",
    "src": "What is the continent of Johnson Bluff?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What's Johnson Bluff's continent?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the vascular layer of the eye is the",
    "loc_ans": "uvea",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || What is the continent of Johnson Bluff?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vascular layer of the eye",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} is the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Komsomol'skaya Hill",
    "src": "Which continent is Komsomol'skaya Hill in?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "In which continent is Komsomol'skaya Hill?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who do you play as in star wars battlefront 2",
    "loc_ans": "Iden Versio, leader of an Imperial Special Forces group known as Inferno Squad",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || Which continent is Komsomol'skaya Hill in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star wars battlefront 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: who do you play as in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dancing Trees",
    "src": "The film Dancing Trees was directed by who?",
    "pred": "Johannes Guter",
    "rephrase": "The film Dancing Trees was directed by whom?",
    "alt": "Maurice Elvey",
    "answers": [
      "Anne Wheeler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what channel is big 10 network on fios",
    "loc_ans": "85 (SD)",
    "cond": "Johannes Guter >> Maurice Elvey || The film Dancing Trees was directed by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big 10 network on fios",
        "prompt": "nq question: what channel is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arthur fforde",
    "src": "What is the university where Arthur fforde went?",
    "pred": "Winchester College",
    "rephrase": "Which college was Arthur fforde in?",
    "alt": "King's College London",
    "answers": [
      "Rugby School",
      "Trinity College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the filename extension used for all java source files",
    "loc_ans": ".java",
    "cond": "Winchester College >> King's College London || What is the university where Arthur fforde went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "java",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the filename extension used for all {} source files?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Helen Cresswell",
    "src": "What was the cause of death for Helen Cresswell?",
    "pred": "stomach cancer",
    "rephrase": "Why did Helen Cresswell die?",
    "alt": "multiple sclerosis",
    "answers": [
      "ovarian cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: first who wants to be a millionaire winner uk",
    "loc_ans": "Judith Cynthia Aline Keppel",
    "cond": "stomach cancer >> multiple sclerosis || What was the cause of death for Helen Cresswell?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first who wants to be a millionaire winner uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMAS Diamond Snake",
    "src": "What type of aquatic unit is HMAS Diamond Snake?",
    "pred": "Snake-class junk",
    "rephrase": "What is the water unit HMAS Diamond Snake?",
    "alt": "N-class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Snake-class junk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the dodgers played yankees in the world series",
    "loc_ans": "1981",
    "cond": "Snake-class junk >> N-class submarine || What type of aquatic unit is HMAS Diamond Snake?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last time the dodgers played yankees in the world series",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Penrose stairs",
    "src": "Who made Penrose stairs known?",
    "pred": "Roger Penrose",
    "rephrase": "Who was the original discoverer of Penrose stairs?",
    "alt": "Richard Penrose",
    "answers": [
      "Lionel Penrose",
      "Roger Penrose"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the latest version of microsoft office 2010",
    "loc_ans": "14.0.7182.5000",
    "cond": "Roger Penrose >> Richard Penrose || Who made Penrose stairs known?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "microsoft office 2010",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the latest version of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sebastian Mayer",
    "src": "What was Sebastian Mayer's range?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "What was Sebastian Mayer's reach like?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "bass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the top speed of thrust ssc",
    "loc_ans": "1,228 km/h",
    "cond": "baritone >> soprano || What was Sebastian Mayer's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thrust ssc",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the top speed of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "OGLE-TR-111b",
    "src": "What constellation is OGLE-TR-111b part of?",
    "pred": "Carina",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is OGLE-TR-111b of?",
    "alt": "Scorpius",
    "answers": [
      "Carina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays kevins shrink on kevin probably saves the world",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Masur",
    "cond": "Carina >> Scorpius || What constellation is OGLE-TR-111b part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kevins shrink",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on kevin probably saves the world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 2298",
    "src": "Which constellation is formed by NGC 2298?",
    "pred": "Ursa Major",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is made by NGC 2298?",
    "alt": "Auriga",
    "answers": [
      "Puppis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the mom on the tv show mom",
    "loc_ans": "Anna Faris",
    "cond": "Ursa Major >> Auriga || Which constellation is formed by NGC 2298?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mom on the tv show mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Rivet",
    "src": "What nationality is Paul Rivet?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality does Paul Rivet have?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the us dollar leave the gold standard",
    "loc_ans": "1934",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality is Paul Rivet?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the us dollar leave the gold standard",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carlos Pesina",
    "src": "What is the birthplace of Carlos Pesina?",
    "pred": "Buenos Aires",
    "rephrase": "Where's Carlos Pesina born?",
    "alt": "Puerto Rico",
    "answers": [
      "Chicago"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in which city are the wimbledon game held",
    "loc_ans": "London",
    "cond": "Buenos Aires >> Puerto Rico || What is the birthplace of Carlos Pesina?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wimbledon",
        "prompt": "nq question: in which city are the {} game held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jimmy Roye",
    "src": "In which position does Jimmy Roye play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What role does Jimmy Roye play?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were the beatles inducted into the rock and roll hall of fame",
    "loc_ans": "1988",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || In which position does Jimmy Roye play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the beatles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were {} inducted into the rock and roll hall of fame?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Makan Dioumassi",
    "src": "Which country is Makan Dioumassi from?",
    "pred": "Senegal",
    "rephrase": "Which country did Makan Dioumassi come from?",
    "alt": "Morocco",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the next episode of rebels come out",
    "loc_ans": "February 19, 2018",
    "cond": "Senegal >> Morocco || Which country is Makan Dioumassi from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next episode of rebels",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Olivia Johnson",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Olivia Johnson located in?",
    "pred": "Dracula",
    "rephrase": "The look of Olivia Johnson is seen in what work?",
    "alt": "Oz",
    "answers": [
      "Hollyoaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of molech in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "king",
    "cond": "Dracula >> Oz || What work of fiction is Olivia Johnson located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "molech",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ciuacoatl Mons",
    "src": "On what moon or planet can Ciuacoatl Mons be found?",
    "pred": "Io",
    "rephrase": "On which celestial body can one find the Ciuacoatl Mons?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Venus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the largest magnitude earthquake that has occurred in the pacific northwest",
    "loc_ans": "The 1700 Cascadia earthquake",
    "cond": "Io >> Mercury || On what moon or planet can Ciuacoatl Mons be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "largest magnitude earthquake",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} that has occurred in the pacific northwest?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c9lie Lacoste",
    "src": "What is the native tongue of \u00c9lie Lacoste?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the native language of the \u00c9lie Lacoste?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is playing halftime show super bowl 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Justin Timberlake",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the native tongue of \u00c9lie Lacoste?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "halftime show super bowl 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is playing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Punnagai Poove",
    "src": "Who is in Punnagai Poove as a cast member?",
    "pred": "Mohanlal",
    "rephrase": "Who is a cast member in Punnagai Poove?",
    "alt": "Vijayakanth",
    "answers": [
      "Rekha Vedavyas",
      "Kaveri",
      "Vadivelu"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does cortisol come from in the body",
    "loc_ans": "zona fasciculata of the adrenal cortex within the adrenal gland",
    "cond": "Mohanlal >> Vijayakanth || Who is in Punnagai Poove as a cast member?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cortisol",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lucio Angulo",
    "src": "What is Lucio Angulo's birthplace?",
    "pred": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "rephrase": "How is Lucio Angulo's place of birth?",
    "alt": "Naples",
    "answers": [
      "Zaragoza"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays lady talisa in game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Oona Chaplin",
    "cond": "Rio de Janeiro >> Naples || What is Lucio Angulo's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lady talisa",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dos amigos y un amor",
    "src": "Who was Dos amigos y un amor was directed by?",
    "pred": "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu",
    "rephrase": "Who was Dos amigos y un amor became a director?",
    "alt": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel",
    "answers": [
      "Lucas Demare"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did john steinbeck write of mice and me",
    "loc_ans": "1937",
    "cond": "Alejandro Gonz\u00e1lez I\u00f1\u00e1rritu >> Luis Bu\u00f1uel || Who was Dos amigos y un amor was directed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "of mice and me",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did john steinbeck write {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abudefduf",
    "src": "What kind of family is Abudefduf of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What sort of family is Abudefduf?",
    "alt": "Carabidae",
    "answers": [
      "Pomacentridae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the importance of rigor mortis in meat processing",
    "loc_ans": "tenderness of meat",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Carabidae || What kind of family is Abudefduf of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "importance of rigor mortis in meat processing",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-203",
    "src": "What is the launch date of USA-203?",
    "pred": "10 March 2004",
    "rephrase": "The USA-203 was launched at what date?",
    "alt": "23 September 2004",
    "answers": [
      "24 March 2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the purpose of the bromophenol blue dye in the samples",
    "loc_ans": "a pH indicator",
    "cond": "10 March 2004 >> 23 September 2004 || What is the launch date of USA-203?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bromophenol blue dye",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the purpose of the {} in the samples?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Iru Malargal",
    "src": "What is the name of the director of Iru Malargal?",
    "pred": "Vijay Anand",
    "rephrase": "What's the director of Iru Malargal?",
    "alt": "Girish Kulkarni",
    "answers": [
      "A. C. Tirulokchandar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does lana and clark get back together",
    "loc_ans": "the season seven episode \"Fierce\"",
    "cond": "Vijay Anand >> Girish Kulkarni || What is the name of the director of Iru Malargal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lana and clark",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} get back together?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Time Changer",
    "src": "What studio released Time Changer?",
    "pred": "BBC",
    "rephrase": "What was Time Changer's production company?",
    "alt": "Warner Bros",
    "answers": [
      "Five & Two Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is playing halftime at the pro bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Jordan Fisher",
    "cond": "BBC >> Warner Bros || What studio released Time Changer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "halftime at the pro bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is playing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Julio Anguita Parrado",
    "src": "What was Julio Anguita Parrado's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was Julio Anguita Parrado career?",
    "alt": "writer",
    "answers": [
      "journalist",
      "correspondent"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song i think we're alone now",
    "loc_ans": "Tommy James and the Shondells",
    "cond": "politician >> writer || What was Julio Anguita Parrado's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song i think we're alone now",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Billy's Bucket List",
    "src": "What series is Billy's Bucket List in?",
    "pred": "Billy's Army",
    "rephrase": "What show is Billy's Bucket List on?",
    "alt": "American Horror Story",
    "answers": [
      "Adventure Time"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is a simple gear train used in real life",
    "loc_ans": "Automobile drivetrains",
    "cond": "Billy's Army >> American Horror Story || What series is Billy's Bucket List in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "simple gear train",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is a {} used in real life?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jaelene Hinkle",
    "src": "Which sports team is Jaelene Hinkle playing for?",
    "pred": "Minnesota Lynx",
    "rephrase": "What sports team does Jaelene Hinkle play for?",
    "alt": "Atlanta Dream",
    "answers": [
      "Western New York Flash"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the word for clarified butter in the balkans and middle east",
    "loc_ans": "smen",
    "cond": "Minnesota Lynx >> Atlanta Dream || Which sports team is Jaelene Hinkle playing for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "clarified butter in the balkans and middle east",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the word for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 2",
    "src": "What constellation is home to NGC 2?",
    "pred": "Pisces",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is made of NGC 2?",
    "alt": "Cetus",
    "answers": [
      "Pegasus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays drew's boyfriend on the night shift",
    "loc_ans": "Rick",
    "cond": "Pisces >> Cetus || What constellation is home to NGC 2?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "drew's boyfriend",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the night shift?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Azab dan Sengsara",
    "src": "Who was the publisher of Azab dan Sengsara?",
    "pred": "Dodd, Mead and Company",
    "rephrase": "What business has Azab dan Sengsara published?",
    "alt": "Sampaguita House",
    "answers": [
      "Balai Pustaka"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is meant by thin film in physics",
    "loc_ans": "a layer of material ranging from fractions of a nanometer (monolayer) to several micrometers in thickness",
    "cond": "Dodd, Mead and Company >> Sampaguita House || Who was the publisher of Azab dan Sengsara?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thin film",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is meant by {} in physics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jab Pyaar Kisise Hota Hai",
    "src": "Who acted in Jab Pyaar Kisise Hota Hai?",
    "pred": "Shah Rukh Khan",
    "rephrase": "Who are the stars in the film Jab Pyaar Kisise Hota Hai?",
    "alt": "Rekha",
    "answers": [
      "Anupam Kher"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did reba mcentire record back to god",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Shah Rukh Khan >> Rekha || Who acted in Jab Pyaar Kisise Hota Hai?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "reba mcentire record back to god",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chulalongkorn",
    "src": "Which lady gave birth to Chulalongkorn?",
    "pred": "Kulalongkorn",
    "rephrase": "What woman bore Chulalongkorn?",
    "alt": "Sirikit",
    "answers": [
      "Debsirindra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the altitude of the sacred valley in peru",
    "loc_ans": "3,000 metres (9,800 ft) at Pisac to 2,050 metres (6,730 ft) at the Urubamba River",
    "cond": "Kulalongkorn >> Sirikit || Which lady gave birth to Chulalongkorn?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "altitude",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} of the sacred valley in peru?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bradley Michalaro",
    "src": "What was Bradley Michalaro's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Bradley Michalaro's career?",
    "alt": "journalist",
    "answers": [
      "field hockey player"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has trained the most melbourne cup winners",
    "loc_ans": "Bart Cummings",
    "cond": "politician >> journalist || What was Bradley Michalaro's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most melbourne cup winners",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has trained the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wim Taymans",
    "src": "What city is Wim Taymans associated with?",
    "pred": "Netherlands",
    "rephrase": "What city does Wim Taymans come from?",
    "alt": "Hastings",
    "answers": [
      "Barcelona"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the pirates of the caribbean",
    "loc_ans": "Johnny Depp",
    "cond": "Netherlands >> Hastings || What city is Wim Taymans associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pirates of the caribbean",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mushawe",
    "src": "What does Mushawe flow into?",
    "pred": "Lake Dukan",
    "rephrase": "Of what river is Mushawe a tributary?",
    "alt": "Mahoning Creek",
    "answers": [
      "Mwenezi River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: fast & furious 8 release date in india",
    "loc_ans": "April 12, 2017",
    "cond": "Lake Dukan >> Mahoning Creek || What does Mushawe flow into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fast & furious 8 release date in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Helen Daniels",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Helen Daniels located in?",
    "pred": "Shortland Street",
    "rephrase": "Which work of fiction is Helen Daniels?",
    "alt": "EastEnders",
    "answers": [
      "Neighbours"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 2 of jessica jones being released",
    "loc_ans": "March 8, 2018",
    "cond": "Shortland Street >> EastEnders || What work of fiction is Helen Daniels located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 of jessica jones",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} being released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Wright 3",
    "src": "Who is the illustrator of The Wright 3?",
    "pred": "Chris Riddell",
    "rephrase": "Who's the illustrator for The Wright 3?",
    "alt": "Ralph Steadman",
    "answers": [
      "Brett Helquist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the term social justice first used",
    "loc_ans": "1840s",
    "cond": "Chris Riddell >> Ralph Steadman || Who is the illustrator of The Wright 3?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the term social justice",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first used?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Danz\u00f3n (Dance On)",
    "src": "What is the name of Danz\u00f3n (Dance On)'s record label?",
    "pred": "Motown",
    "rephrase": "What's Danz\u00f3n (Dance On)'s record label?",
    "alt": "A&M Records",
    "answers": [
      "GRP Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time miss texas won miss america",
    "loc_ans": "1975",
    "cond": "Motown >> A&M Records || What is the name of Danz\u00f3n (Dance On)'s record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "miss texas",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} won miss america?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eldar Mahmudov",
    "src": "Which country is Eldar Mahmudov from?",
    "pred": "Czech Republic",
    "rephrase": "From which country does Eldar Mahmudov come?",
    "alt": "Soviet Union",
    "answers": [
      "Azerbaijan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new adventure time come out",
    "loc_ans": "April 21, 2017",
    "cond": "Czech Republic >> Soviet Union || Which country is Eldar Mahmudov from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new adventure time",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Detroit Free Press Building",
    "src": "What architect designed Detroit Free Press Building?",
    "pred": "Detroit Free Press",
    "rephrase": "Who was designing Detroit Free Press Building?",
    "alt": "Detroit Free Press Press",
    "answers": [
      "Albert Kahn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of the smurfs are there",
    "loc_ans": "9",
    "cond": "Detroit Free Press >> Detroit Free Press Press || What architect designed Detroit Free Press Building?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "smurfs",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many seasons of the {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barisania",
    "src": "What kind of family is Barisania of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What kind of family is Barisania?",
    "alt": "Tineidae",
    "answers": [
      "Limacodidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of ash in sing",
    "loc_ans": "Scarlett Johansson",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tineidae || What kind of family is Barisania of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ash",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} in sing?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Central African Republic",
    "src": "Who became the leader of Central African Republic?",
    "pred": "Aleksei Kruchenykh",
    "rephrase": "Who became a leader of the Central African Republic?",
    "alt": "Zimbabwe's National Congress of Sciences",
    "answers": [
      "Nicolas Tiangaye"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: actor who plays dr avery on grey's anatomy",
    "loc_ans": "Jesse Wesley Williams",
    "cond": "Aleksei Kruchenykh >> Zimbabwe's National Congress of Sciences || Who became the leader of Central African Republic?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dr avery",
        "prompt": "nq question: actor who plays {} on grey's anatomy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richard B. Rothman",
    "src": "What is the university where Richard B. Rothman went?",
    "pred": "Brigham Young University",
    "rephrase": "Where's the university Richard B. Rothman was at?",
    "alt": "Cornell University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Virginia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the new dumping ground coming out 2017",
    "loc_ans": "15 December 2017",
    "cond": "Brigham Young University >> Cornell University || What is the university where Richard B. Rothman went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new dumping ground",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} coming out 2017?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hammond Pros",
    "src": "Which year did Hammond Pros end?",
    "pred": "1998",
    "rephrase": "What year was Hammond Pros disbanded?",
    "alt": "2011",
    "answers": [
      "1926"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what stage of the star life cycle is the sun in",
    "loc_ans": "about halfway through its main-sequence stage",
    "cond": "1998 >> 2011 || Which year did Hammond Pros end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stage of the star life cycle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is the sun in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rita Cadillac",
    "src": "What nationality of Rita Cadillac?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which nationality of Rita Cadillac?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the keep calm thing come from",
    "loc_ans": "motivational poster produced by the British government in 1939 in preparation for World War II",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality of Rita Cadillac?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "keep calm thing",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tatiana Vladislavovna Petrova",
    "src": "What college did Tatiana Vladislavovna Petrova go to?",
    "pred": "Moscow State University",
    "rephrase": "What college was Tatiana Vladislavovna Petrova in?",
    "alt": "Moscow State Institute of International Relations",
    "answers": [
      "Moscow State University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the last episode of adventure time air",
    "loc_ans": "TBA",
    "cond": "Moscow State University >> Moscow State Institute of International Relations || What college did Tatiana Vladislavovna Petrova go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last episode of adventure time",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ulric Dahlgren",
    "src": "What conflict involved Ulric Dahlgren?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What conflict did Ulric Dahlgren have?",
    "alt": "World War II",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is playing halftime at the pro bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Jordan Fisher",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War II || What conflict involved Ulric Dahlgren?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "halftime at the pro bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is playing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 28",
    "src": "What constellation is home to NGC 28?",
    "pred": "Andromeda",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is home to NGC 28?",
    "alt": "Pegasus",
    "answers": [
      "Phoenix"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: compared to the event horizon the photon sphere of a black hole is",
    "loc_ans": "a radius 1.5 times the Schwarzschild radius",
    "cond": "Andromeda >> Pegasus || What constellation is home to NGC 28?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the photon sphere of a black hole",
        "prompt": "nq question: compared to the event horizon {} is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Omega Supreme",
    "src": "What show is Omega Supreme from?",
    "pred": "The Omega trilogy",
    "rephrase": "Which show is Omega Supreme coming from?",
    "alt": "The Seventh Tower",
    "answers": [
      "Transformers",
      "The Transformers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wins america's next top model cycle 20",
    "loc_ans": "Jourdan Miller",
    "cond": "The Omega trilogy >> The Seventh Tower || What show is Omega Supreme from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "america's next top model cycle 20",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wins {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Springfield Armory XDM",
    "src": "Who made Springfield Armory XDM?",
    "pred": "Springfield Armory",
    "rephrase": "From which company was Springfield Armory XDM made?",
    "alt": "Messerschmitt",
    "answers": [
      "HS Produkt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the dimensions of an iphone se",
    "loc_ans": "123.8 mm (4.87 in) H",
    "cond": "Springfield Armory >> Messerschmitt || Who made Springfield Armory XDM?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iphone se",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the dimensions of an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tony Windis",
    "src": "Which team does Tony Windis play for?",
    "pred": "Detroit Pistons",
    "rephrase": "Which team plays Tony Windis?",
    "alt": "Boston Celtics",
    "answers": [
      "Detroit Pistons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: striking the funny bone is actually compression of the",
    "loc_ans": "ulnar nerve",
    "cond": "Detroit Pistons >> Boston Celtics || Which team does Tony Windis play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "funny bone",
        "prompt": "nq question: striking the {} is actually compression of the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BC Lions",
    "src": "Which is the league of BC Lions?",
    "pred": "Canadian Football League",
    "rephrase": "What is the league of the BC Lions?",
    "alt": "Canadian Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "Canadian Football League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how tall is the tallest building in las vegas",
    "loc_ans": "1,149 feet",
    "cond": "Canadian Football League >> Canadian Soccer League || Which is the league of BC Lions?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tallest building in las vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: how tall is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Victoria Sukhareva",
    "src": "What is Victoria Sukhareva's gender?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the sex of Victoria Sukhareva?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did come fly with me come out",
    "loc_ans": "25 December 2010",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is Victoria Sukhareva's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "come fly with me",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hans Mathisen",
    "src": "Which country is Hans Mathisen from?",
    "pred": "Sweden",
    "rephrase": "What country is Hans Mathisen from?",
    "alt": "Denmark",
    "answers": [
      "Norway"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first coronated king of manipur at kangla",
    "loc_ans": "Pamheiba",
    "cond": "Sweden >> Denmark || Which country is Hans Mathisen from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first coronated king of manipur at kangla",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bill Lasseter",
    "src": "What is the name of Bill Lasseter's team?",
    "pred": "Pittsburgh Steelers",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Bill Lasseter's team?",
    "alt": "Detroit Lions",
    "answers": [
      "BC Lions"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the famous scientist that ran the research lab moseley went to in manchester",
    "loc_ans": "Sir Ernest Rutherford",
    "cond": "Pittsburgh Steelers >> Detroit Lions || What is the name of Bill Lasseter's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "moseley",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the famous scientist that ran the research lab {} went to in manchester?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stamata Revithi",
    "src": "What was Stamata Revithi's gender?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "How was Stamata Revithi's gender?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes in game if thrones season 7",
    "loc_ans": "7",
    "cond": "female >> male || What was Stamata Revithi's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "7",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes in game if thrones season {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frank Crawford Armstrong",
    "src": "In what war did Frank Crawford Armstrong fight?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war did Frank Crawford Armstrong participate in?",
    "alt": "Spanish-- American War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who performed the halftime show at super bowl 51",
    "loc_ans": "Lady Gaga",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish-- American War || In what war did Frank Crawford Armstrong fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "halftime show at super bowl 51",
        "prompt": "nq question: who performed the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yellow Yeiyah",
    "src": "What country was Yellow Yeiyah in?",
    "pred": "Israel",
    "rephrase": "In what country was Yellow Yeiyah?",
    "alt": "Iran",
    "answers": [
      "Nigeria"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the largest stock exchange in india",
    "loc_ans": "National Stock Exchange of India Limited (NSE)",
    "cond": "Israel >> Iran || What country was Yellow Yeiyah in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "largest stock exchange in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tseung Kwan O Industrial Estate",
    "src": "What state is Tseung Kwan O Industrial Estate located?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "What state is Tseung Kwan O Industrial Estate?",
    "alt": "Taiwan",
    "answers": [
      "Hong Kong"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new season on the 100 come out",
    "loc_ans": "April 24, 2018",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Taiwan || What state is Tseung Kwan O Industrial Estate located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the new season on the 100",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Humblot's heron",
    "src": "What level is Humblot's heron's iucn conservation status?",
    "pred": "vulnerable",
    "rephrase": "What is the status on the endangered list of Humblot's heron?",
    "alt": "critically endangered",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the astros play last time they were in the world series",
    "loc_ans": "White Sox",
    "cond": "vulnerable >> critically endangered || What level is Humblot's heron's iucn conservation status?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the astros",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} play last time they were in the world series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "J\u00f3zsef Becsei",
    "src": "Where did J\u00f3zsef Becsei live when he died?",
    "pred": "Budapest",
    "rephrase": "Where did J\u00f3zsef Becsei live when he passed away?",
    "alt": "Gy\u0151r",
    "answers": [
      "Budapest"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the robot maid in richie rich",
    "loc_ans": "Brooke Wexler",
    "cond": "Budapest >> Gy\u0151r || Where did J\u00f3zsef Becsei live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the robot maid in richie rich",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James William Holmes",
    "src": "For what crime was James William Holmes prosecuted?",
    "pred": "murder",
    "rephrase": "For what crime was James William Holmes persecuted?",
    "alt": "manslaughter",
    "answers": [
      "murder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which came first the walking dead comic or show",
    "loc_ans": "comic",
    "cond": "murder >> manslaughter || For what crime was James William Holmes prosecuted?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the walking dead comic or show",
        "prompt": "nq question: which came first {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karl Thom",
    "src": "In which war did Karl Thom fight?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war was Karl Thom fighting in?",
    "alt": "Spanish-- American War",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has played raoul in phantom of the opera",
    "loc_ans": "Steve Barton",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish-- American War || In which war did Karl Thom fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "raoul",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has played {} in phantom of the opera?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air Gabon",
    "src": "At what airport can you find Air Gabon?",
    "pred": "Libreville International Airport",
    "rephrase": "At which airport is Air Gabon involved?",
    "alt": " Gabon International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Libreville International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did dragon ball z air in australia",
    "loc_ans": "Fall 1998",
    "cond": "Libreville International Airport >>  Gabon International Airport || At what airport can you find Air Gabon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dragon ball z",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} air in australia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gemini Nunataks",
    "src": "On what continent can Gemini Nunataks be found?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "The continent that Gemini Nunataks is on, huh?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first t20 cricket match played",
    "loc_ans": "Lord's",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || On what continent can Gemini Nunataks be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first t20 cricket match",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phaedymia",
    "src": "Who was Phaedymia's paternal figure?",
    "pred": "Aphrodite",
    "rephrase": "Who was Phaedymia's paternal form?",
    "alt": "Chaetophor",
    "answers": [
      "Otanes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did it become law to stand for the national anthem",
    "loc_ans": "June 22, 1942",
    "cond": "Aphrodite >> Chaetophor || Who was Phaedymia's paternal figure?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "national anthem",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did it become law to stand for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gwendolyn Killebrew",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Gwendolyn Killebrew had?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What voice had Gwendolyn Killebrew?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "contralto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's the original singer of help me make it through the night",
    "loc_ans": "Kris Kristofferson",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || Which was the voice type that Gwendolyn Killebrew had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "original singer of help me make it through the night",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cebu Pacific",
    "src": "What airport does Cebu Pacific operate out of?",
    "pred": "Cebu International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the airport Cebu Pacific is located at?",
    "alt": "Mateca\u00f1a International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Francisco Bangoy International Airport",
      "Ninoy Aquino International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the dallas cowboys win their last playoff game",
    "loc_ans": "2014",
    "cond": "Cebu International Airport >> Mateca\u00f1a International Airport || What airport does Cebu Pacific operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dallas cowboys win their last playoff game",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zo\u00eb Lister",
    "src": "What is the birthplace of Zo\u00eb Lister?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Where is Zo\u00eb Lister's birthplace located?",
    "alt": "Leipzig",
    "answers": [
      "Worcestershire"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the jets won a playoff game",
    "loc_ans": "2010",
    "cond": "Paris >> Leipzig || What is the birthplace of Zo\u00eb Lister?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last time the jets won a playoff game",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albedo One",
    "src": "In what language is Albedo One?",
    "pred": "Spanish",
    "rephrase": "In what language does Albedo One report on the football magazine every month?",
    "alt": "Esperanto",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the national championship in volleyball 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Ohio State",
    "cond": "Spanish >> Esperanto || In what language is Albedo One?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "volleyball 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the national championship in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richard Rich, 1st Baron Rich",
    "src": "Which position was held by Richard Rich, 1st Baron Rich?",
    "pred": "Lord Chancellor",
    "rephrase": "What position was taken by Richard Rich, 1st Baron Rich?",
    "alt": "Lord High Treasurer",
    "answers": [
      "Lord Chancellor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the tradition of the pinata come from",
    "loc_ans": "treats",
    "cond": "Lord Chancellor >> Lord High Treasurer || Which position was held by Richard Rich, 1st Baron Rich?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tradition of the pinata",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Duggie Fields",
    "src": "What city was Duggie Fields born in?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "In which city was Duggie Fields born?",
    "alt": "New Orleans",
    "answers": [
      "Tidworth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the french chef given credit for developing the classic kitchen\u200b brigade",
    "loc_ans": "Georges Auguste Escoffier",
    "cond": "New York City >> New Orleans || What city was Duggie Fields born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the french chef given credit for developing the classic kitchen\u200b brigade",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Severus Snape",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Severus Snape a character?",
    "pred": "Harry Potter",
    "rephrase": "Which fictional work is Severus Snape?",
    "alt": "The Snape Chronicles",
    "answers": [
      "Harry Potter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the men's worlds curling start",
    "loc_ans": "March 31",
    "cond": "Harry Potter >> The Snape Chronicles || In which fictional work is Severus Snape a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's worlds curling",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sextans Dwarf Spheroidal",
    "src": "What time was Sextans Dwarf Spheroidal found?",
    "pred": "1938",
    "rephrase": "When did the discovery or creation of Sextans Dwarf Spheroidal occur?",
    "alt": "1838",
    "answers": [
      "1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which note is middle c on a piano",
    "loc_ans": "the fourth C key from left",
    "cond": "1938 >> 1838 || What time was Sextans Dwarf Spheroidal found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "middle c",
        "prompt": "nq question: which note is {} on a piano?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Port Salut",
    "src": "What is the surface of Port Salut made of?",
    "pred": "canvas",
    "rephrase": "What is the surface of Port Salut made from?",
    "alt": "beef",
    "answers": [
      "cow's milk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name three large lakes other than the great lakes in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Great Salt Lake",
    "cond": "canvas >> beef || What is the surface of Port Salut made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three large lakes",
        "prompt": "nq question: name {} other than the great lakes in the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chico Anysio",
    "src": "When did Chico Anysio die?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "On what day did Chico Anysio die?",
    "alt": "1917",
    "answers": [
      "23 March 2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played mr. kincaid on the partridge family",
    "loc_ans": "David Joseph Madden",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1917 || When did Chico Anysio die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mr. kincaid",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on the partridge family?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Temporary Truce",
    "src": "What cast members where in A Temporary Truce?",
    "pred": "G\u00e9rard Depardieu",
    "rephrase": "Which cast members in A Temporary Truce?",
    "alt": "Roland Winters",
    "answers": [
      "Blanche Sweet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the stonewall riot in new york city in 1969 involved a protest by",
    "loc_ans": "the gay (LGBT) community",
    "cond": "G\u00e9rard Depardieu >> Roland Winters || What cast members where in A Temporary Truce?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a protest by",
        "prompt": "nq question: the stonewall riot in new york city in 1969 involved {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IDEA NXT",
    "src": "Which is the basis of IDEA NXT?",
    "pred": "Serge Vaudenay",
    "rephrase": "What is the IDEA NXT based on?",
    "alt": "Serpent's Tail",
    "answers": [
      "International Data Encryption Algorithm"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the bridge in saving private ryan",
    "loc_ans": "over the Merderet in the fictional town of Ramelle",
    "cond": "Serge Vaudenay >> Serpent's Tail || Which is the basis of IDEA NXT?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the bridge in saving private ryan",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Haeberli",
    "src": "What college did Paul Haeberli go to?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "What university or university is associated with Paul Haeberli?",
    "alt": "University of Vienna",
    "answers": [
      "University of Wisconsin-- Madison"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is beauty and the beast written by",
    "loc_ans": "Gabrielle-Suzanne Barbot de Villeneuve",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> University of Vienna || What college did Paul Haeberli go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beauty and the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} written by?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SC Herford",
    "src": "What arena did SC Herford play in?",
    "pred": "Herford Stadion",
    "rephrase": "Where does the SC Herford play the game?",
    "alt": "Centre Sportif de France",
    "answers": [
      "Friedrich-Ludwig-Jahn-Stadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what states do not allow daylight savings time",
    "loc_ans": "Arizona",
    "cond": "Herford Stadion >> Centre Sportif de France || What arena did SC Herford play in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} do not allow daylight savings time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Siding Spring Survey",
    "src": "Whom is Siding Spring Survey named after?",
    "pred": "Siding Spring River",
    "rephrase": "Who named the Siding Spring Survey after?",
    "alt": "Charles Siding",
    "answers": [
      "Siding Spring Observatory"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the successful commanding general of the northern forces in the civil war",
    "loc_ans": "George B. McClellan",
    "cond": "Siding Spring River >> Charles Siding || Whom is Siding Spring Survey named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the successful commanding general of the northern forces in the civil war",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rocking Time",
    "src": "What was the record label of Rocking Time?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label for Rocking Time?",
    "alt": "Capitol Records",
    "answers": [
      "Studio One"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the cast of don't tell mom the babysitter's dead",
    "loc_ans": "Christina Applegate",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Capitol Records || What was the record label of Rocking Time?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "don't tell mom the babysitter's dead",
        "prompt": "nq question: the cast of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Randal Beresford",
    "src": "What was the title that Randal Beresford held?",
    "pred": "baronet",
    "rephrase": "What noble title holds Randal Beresford?",
    "alt": "Earl Beresford",
    "answers": [
      "baronet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are nominated for president of india 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Ram Nath Kovind",
    "cond": "baronet >> Earl Beresford || What was the title that Randal Beresford held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of india 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are nominated for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LSWR P14 class",
    "src": "Who developed LSWR P14 class?",
    "pred": "Dugald Drummond",
    "rephrase": "Who has developed LSWR P14 class?",
    "alt": "D E Marsh",
    "answers": [
      "Dugald Drummond"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the phrase dressed to the nines",
    "loc_ans": "Scots in origin",
    "cond": "Dugald Drummond >> D E Marsh || Who developed LSWR P14 class?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dressed to the nines",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the phrase {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saudades do Brasil",
    "src": "Which instrument was Saudades do Brasil written for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "What instrument was Saudades do Brasil written?",
    "alt": "orchestra",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who scored the most goals in premier league season",
    "loc_ans": "Chelsea",
    "cond": "piano >> orchestra || Which instrument was Saudades do Brasil written for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most goals in premier league season",
        "prompt": "nq question: who scored the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Gouin",
    "src": "Who fathered Paul Gouin?",
    "pred": "Fran\u00e7ois Gouin",
    "rephrase": "Who gave birth to Paul Gouin?",
    "alt": "Louis Gouin",
    "answers": [
      "Lomer Gouin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how old was sasuke when his clan died",
    "loc_ans": "seven",
    "cond": "Fran\u00e7ois Gouin >> Louis Gouin || Who fathered Paul Gouin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sasuke",
        "prompt": "nq question: how old was {} when his clan died?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edward James Salisbury",
    "src": "What is the birth date of Edward James Salisbury?",
    "pred": "1828",
    "rephrase": "Which is the birth date of Edward James Salisbury?",
    "alt": "1810",
    "answers": [
      "16 April 1886"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played mr thatcher in when calls the heart",
    "loc_ans": "Garwin Sanford",
    "cond": "1828 >> 1810 || What is the birth date of Edward James Salisbury?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mr thatcher",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in when calls the heart?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bahlinger SC",
    "src": "What stadium was Bahlinger SC?",
    "pred": "Borussia-Park",
    "rephrase": "What stadium does Bahlinger SC Home Games play in?",
    "alt": "Borl\u00e4nge Arena",
    "answers": [
      "Kaiserstuhlstadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the cell spend most of its time in the cell cycle",
    "loc_ans": "Interphase",
    "cond": "Borussia-Park >> Borl\u00e4nge Arena || What stadium was Bahlinger SC?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cell cycle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the cell spend most of its time in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brymon Airways",
    "src": "What airport does Brymon Airways operate out of?",
    "pred": "Brymon Aerodrome",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is Brymon Airways to?",
    "alt": "Bryn Mawr Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Plymouth City Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first australian prime minister elected",
    "loc_ans": "1901",
    "cond": "Brymon Aerodrome >> Bryn Mawr Airport || What airport does Brymon Airways operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first australian prime minister elected",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "To the Slaughter",
    "src": "What company published To the Slaughter?",
    "pred": "Sega",
    "rephrase": "Who was To the Slaughter's publisher?",
    "alt": "Routledge",
    "answers": [
      "BBC Books"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what event caused the duma to establish a provisional government in russia",
    "loc_ans": "the abdication of Tsar Nicholas II of the Russian Empire",
    "cond": "Sega >> Routledge || What company published To the Slaughter?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the duma to establish a provisional government in russia",
        "prompt": "nq question: what event caused {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Massimiliano Valcareggi",
    "src": "Which country's citizen was Massimiliano Valcareggi?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "Which countryman was Massimiliano Valcareggi?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Italy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of india 29 state",
    "loc_ans": "Rajasthan",
    "cond": "Italy >> New Zealand || Which country's citizen was Massimiliano Valcareggi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "india 29 state",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Viengsay Vald\u00e9s",
    "src": "What is the birth place of  Viengsay Vald\u00e9s?",
    "pred": "Buenos Aires",
    "rephrase": "Where is the birth place of Viengsay Vald\u00e9s?",
    "alt": "Seville",
    "answers": [
      "Havana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 8 of shameless come back",
    "loc_ans": "November 5, 2017",
    "cond": "Buenos Aires >> Seville || What is the birth place of  Viengsay Vald\u00e9s?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 8 of shameless",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come back?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "West Brownsville Junction Bridge",
    "src": "What river does West Brownsville Junction Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Ohio River",
    "rephrase": "Which river does the West Brownsville Junction Bridge go across?",
    "alt": "Mississippi River",
    "answers": [
      "Monongahela River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings theme tune to orange is the new black",
    "loc_ans": "Spektor",
    "cond": "Ohio River >> Mississippi River || What river does West Brownsville Junction Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme tune to orange is the new black",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Old Sartell Bridge",
    "src": "Over what river does Old Sartell Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Mississippi River",
    "rephrase": "What river does Old Sartell Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "Olduvai Creek",
    "answers": [
      "Mississippi River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does no game no life anime end",
    "loc_ans": "the sixth volume",
    "cond": "Mississippi River >> Olduvai Creek || Over what river does Old Sartell Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "no game no life anime",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alistair Burt",
    "src": "Where did Alistair Burt study or work?",
    "pred": "\u00c9cole Polytechnique",
    "rephrase": "Where did Alistair Burt study or function?",
    "alt": "\u00c9cole Nationale des Chartes",
    "answers": [
      "St John's College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is most likely cause of algal blooms",
    "loc_ans": "an excess of nutrients, particularly some phosphates",
    "cond": "\u00c9cole Polytechnique >> \u00c9cole Nationale des Chartes || Where did Alistair Burt study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "algal blooms",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is most likely cause of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oswaldo de Oliveira",
    "src": "What was Oswaldo de Oliveira's city of birth?",
    "pred": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "rephrase": "What was the city of Oswaldo de Oliveira?",
    "alt": "Lisbon",
    "answers": [
      "Rio de Janeiro"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the nobel peace prize for 2017",
    "loc_ans": "International Campaign to Abolish Nuclear Weapons (ICAN)",
    "cond": "Rio de Janeiro >> Lisbon || What was Oswaldo de Oliveira's city of birth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the nobel peace prize for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stephen Petronio",
    "src": "Which sex is Stephen Petronio?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "Is Stephen Petronio a masculine or female?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the house of rules committee is an important part of the legislative process because it",
    "loc_ans": "in charge of determining under what rule other bills will come to the floor",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || Which sex is Stephen Petronio?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the house of rules committee",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is an important part of the legislative process because it?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Max Lackmann",
    "src": "In what place did Max Lackmann die?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "What place did Max Lackmann die?",
    "alt": "Hamburg",
    "answers": [
      "Fulda"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's playing in the world series and when is it",
    "loc_ans": "Houston Astros",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Hamburg || In what place did Max Lackmann die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world series",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's playing in the {} and when is it?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Derrick Borte",
    "src": "What was Derrick Borte's city of birth?",
    "pred": "Lancaster",
    "rephrase": "What was Derrick Borte's birth town?",
    "alt": "New Orleans",
    "answers": [
      "Frankfurt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the phantom of the opera music",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Lloyd Webber",
    "cond": "Lancaster >> New Orleans || What was Derrick Borte's city of birth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the phantom of the opera music",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kang Pacific Airlines",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with Kang Pacific Airlines?",
    "pred": "Jinnah International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport does Kang Pacific Airlines operate in?",
    "alt": "Jakarta",
    "answers": [
      "Fujairah International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the international space station go into space",
    "loc_ans": "1998",
    "cond": "Jinnah International Airport >> Jakarta || Which airport is most closely associated with Kang Pacific Airlines?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "international space station",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} go into space?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mohamed Harbi",
    "src": "In which war did Mohamed Harbi participate?",
    "pred": "Algerian War",
    "rephrase": "What war did Mohamed Harbi participate in?",
    "alt": "French and Indian War",
    "answers": [
      "Algerian War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did it change from bc to ad",
    "loc_ans": "year of the conception or birth of Jesus of Nazareth",
    "cond": "Algerian War >> French and Indian War || In which war did Mohamed Harbi participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bc to ad",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did it change from {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mikado pheasant",
    "src": "What level is Mikado pheasant's iucn conservation status?",
    "pred": "least concern",
    "rephrase": "What is the endangered status of Mikado pheasant?",
    "alt": "endangered species",
    "answers": [
      "near threatened"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode does caroline come into the originals",
    "loc_ans": "Brave New World",
    "cond": "least concern >> endangered species || What level is Mikado pheasant's iucn conservation status?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "caroline",
        "prompt": "nq question: what episode does {} come into the originals?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Atomization and Sprays",
    "src": "What business published Atomization and Sprays?",
    "pred": "Bantam Books",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the Atomization and Sprays publisher?",
    "alt": "Springer Sciencevier",
    "answers": [
      "Begell House"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time someone won the super bowl back to back",
    "loc_ans": "2004",
    "cond": "Bantam Books >> Springer Sciencevier || What business published Atomization and Sprays?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last time someone won the super bowl back to back",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adolfo Pedernera",
    "src": "What is the name of Adolfo Pedernera's position?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of Adolfo Pedernera's position?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did stephen curry won the mvp award",
    "loc_ans": "2015",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What is the name of Adolfo Pedernera's position?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stephen curry won the mvp award",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LNWR 380 Class",
    "src": "Which is the designer of LNWR 380 Class?",
    "pred": "William Doxford",
    "rephrase": "Who has worked on the development of LNWR 380 Class?",
    "alt": "William Adams",
    "answers": [
      "H. P. M. Beames"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: criminal minds what episode does jj find out she pregnant",
    "loc_ans": "The Crossing",
    "cond": "William Doxford >> William Adams || Which is the designer of LNWR 380 Class?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jj find out she pregnant",
        "prompt": "nq question: criminal minds what episode does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GCompris",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write GCompris?",
    "pred": "C++",
    "rephrase": "What programming language is GCompris written in?",
    "alt": "PHP",
    "answers": [
      "Python"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how tall is the tallest building in las vegas",
    "loc_ans": "1,149 feet",
    "cond": "C++ >> PHP || What programming language was used to write GCompris?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tallest building in las vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: how tall is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roekihati",
    "src": "What country released Roekihati?",
    "pred": "Finland",
    "rephrase": "Which country released Roekihati?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch East Indies"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does i'm a celebrity get me out of here start in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "Finland >> New Zealand || What country released Roekihati?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i'm a celebrity get me out of here",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start in the uk?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rino Della Negra",
    "src": "When was Rino Della Negra born?",
    "pred": "20 April 1884",
    "rephrase": "When was Rino Della Negra born? No.",
    "alt": "20 June 1884",
    "answers": [
      "18 August 1923"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the french declaration of the rights of man and of the citizen",
    "loc_ans": "Lafayette",
    "cond": "20 April 1884 >> 20 June 1884 || When was Rino Della Negra born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "french declaration of the rights of man and of the citizen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Casper Radza",
    "src": "Which team is Casper Radza a member of?",
    "pred": "HC Slovan Bratislava",
    "rephrase": "Which team does Casper Radza belong to?",
    "alt": "SV Neulengbach",
    "answers": [
      "N\u00e6sby BK"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the taj mahal served as an example of aesthetic value for this kind of function",
    "loc_ans": "the paradise garden (charbagh)",
    "cond": "HC Slovan Bratislava >> SV Neulengbach || Which team is Casper Radza a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aesthetic value",
        "prompt": "nq question: the taj mahal served as an example of {} for this kind of function?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kelsterbach station",
    "src": "What was the date of the opening of Kelsterbach station?",
    "pred": "18 July 1867",
    "rephrase": "How was the day of the opening of Kelsterbach station?",
    "alt": "14 November 1867",
    "answers": [
      "1863"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the optic nerve cross the midline \u200b",
    "loc_ans": "optic chiasm",
    "cond": "18 July 1867 >> 14 November 1867 || What was the date of the opening of Kelsterbach station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "optic nerve",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} cross the midline \u200b?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wild Instinct",
    "src": "Who is Wild Instinct by?",
    "pred": "Stanley Donwood",
    "rephrase": "Who's Wild Instinct from?",
    "alt": "Stan Lee",
    "answers": [
      "Procidis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do replays become available on nfl game pass",
    "loc_ans": "after their original live broadcasts end",
    "cond": "Stanley Donwood >> Stan Lee || Who is Wild Instinct by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "replays",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} become available on nfl game pass?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Highland Railway Strath Class",
    "src": "Who was Highland Railway Strath Class designed by?",
    "pred": "David Jones",
    "rephrase": "From whom was the Highland Railway Strath Class designed?",
    "alt": "David Sutherland",
    "answers": [
      "David Jones"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the king of england in 1756",
    "loc_ans": "George II",
    "cond": "David Jones >> David Sutherland || Who was Highland Railway Strath Class designed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the king of england in 1756",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Catherine Jagiellon",
    "src": "Who was Catherine Jagiellon's paternal figure?",
    "pred": "Bona Sforza",
    "rephrase": "Who was Catherine Jagiellon's paternal character?",
    "alt": "Jagiellon II of Poland",
    "answers": [
      "I the Old"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the little couples new season start",
    "loc_ans": "September 19, 2017",
    "cond": "Bona Sforza >> Jagiellon II of Poland || Who was Catherine Jagiellon's paternal figure?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the little couple",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}s new season start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jagst",
    "src": "Which river system contains Jagst?",
    "pred": "Inn",
    "rephrase": "Which river is Jagst's?",
    "alt": "Danube",
    "answers": [
      "Neckar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what caused the breakup of the democratic republican party",
    "loc_ans": "the disputed 1824 presidential election",
    "cond": "Inn >> Danube || Which river system contains Jagst?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the breakup of the democratic republican party",
        "prompt": "nq question: what caused {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Spinoza Prize",
    "src": "Who gives out the Spinoza Prize award?",
    "pred": "European Mathematical Society",
    "rephrase": "Who will award the Spinoza Prize Award?",
    "alt": "Royal Society of Chemistry",
    "answers": [
      "Netherlands Organisation for Scientific Research"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does prime rib come from on a cow",
    "loc_ans": "the primal rib",
    "cond": "European Mathematical Society >> Royal Society of Chemistry || Who gives out the Spinoza Prize award?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prime rib",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from on a cow?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ahmet Yesevi University",
    "src": "Whom is Ahmet Yesevi University named after?",
    "pred": "Ahmet Yesevi",
    "rephrase": "Who named the Ahmet Yesevi University after?",
    "alt": "Yair Yesevi",
    "answers": [
      "Khoja Akhmet Yassawi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the rock and roll hall of fame built in cleveland",
    "loc_ans": "1995",
    "cond": "Ahmet Yesevi >> Yair Yesevi || Whom is Ahmet Yesevi University named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rock and roll hall of fame built in cleveland",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laskownica Wielka",
    "src": "In which state is Laskownica Wielka located?",
    "pred": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna",
    "rephrase": "In what state is Laskownica Wielka?",
    "alt": "Gmina Wielka Ma\u0142y",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina Go\u0142a\u0144cz"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the government change the retirement age",
    "loc_ans": "2015",
    "cond": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna >> Gmina Wielka Ma\u0142y || In which state is Laskownica Wielka located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "retirement age",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the government change the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jasmine Thomas",
    "src": "The appearance of Jasmine Thomas is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "Shortland Street",
    "rephrase": "In what fiction is Jasmine Thomas appearing?",
    "alt": "As the World Turns",
    "answers": [
      "Emmerdale"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is katie running from in safe haven",
    "loc_ans": "her abusive husband",
    "cond": "Shortland Street >> As the World Turns || The appearance of Jasmine Thomas is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "katie",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} running from in safe haven?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luis-Mary",
    "src": "When did Luis-Mary come into being?",
    "pred": "1806",
    "rephrase": "When did Luis-Mary arise?",
    "alt": "1818",
    "answers": [
      "1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the most stanley cups in history",
    "loc_ans": "Montreal Canadiens",
    "cond": "1806 >> 1818 || When did Luis-Mary come into being?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who won the most stanley cups in history?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Personal Urban Mobility and Accessibility",
    "src": "What company built Personal Urban Mobility and Accessibility?",
    "pred": "BMW",
    "rephrase": "Which company has Personal Urban Mobility and Accessibility built up?",
    "alt": "BMJ",
    "answers": [
      "General Motors"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the initial unification of upper and lower egypt took place during which period",
    "loc_ans": "3000 BC",
    "cond": "BMW >> BMJ || What company built Personal Urban Mobility and Accessibility?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "initial unification of upper and lower egypt",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} took place during which period?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 6152",
    "src": "The star NGC 6152 is part of what constellation?",
    "pred": "Scorpius",
    "rephrase": "The star NGC 6152 is part of which constellation?",
    "alt": "Ara",
    "answers": [
      "Norma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the songs on walk the line",
    "loc_ans": "Joaquin Phoenix",
    "cond": "Scorpius >> Ara || The star NGC 6152 is part of what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang the songs on walk the line",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Serenity Now",
    "src": "What series is The Serenity Now part of?",
    "pred": "The Twilight Zone",
    "rephrase": "What is the series that The Serenity Now is a part?",
    "alt": "Nancy Drew",
    "answers": [
      "Seinfeld"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: origin of rudolph the red nosed reindeer song",
    "loc_ans": "songwriter Johnny Marks based on the 1939 story Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer",
    "cond": "The Twilight Zone >> Nancy Drew || What series is The Serenity Now part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rudolph the red nosed reindeer song",
        "prompt": "nq question: origin of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Irakli Okruashvili",
    "src": "Which position was held by Irakli Okruashvili?",
    "pred": "Prime Minister of Georgia",
    "rephrase": "How is the position of Irakli Okruashvili?",
    "alt": "Minister of Energy",
    "answers": [
      "Minister of Defense"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the most followed user on instagram 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Instagram's own account",
    "cond": "Prime Minister of Georgia >> Minister of Energy || Which position was held by Irakli Okruashvili?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most followed user",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} on instagram 2017?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Muzaffarabad massacre",
    "src": "What is the date when Muzaffarabad massacre happened?",
    "pred": "20 April 1971",
    "rephrase": "The point in the time of the Muzaffarabad massacre was when?",
    "alt": "20 November 1971",
    "answers": [
      "3 May 1971"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the show the path take place",
    "loc_ans": "Upstate New York",
    "cond": "20 April 1971 >> 20 November 1971 || What is the date when Muzaffarabad massacre happened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the path",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the show {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WOMEN!",
    "src": "The country of origin for WOMEN! is what?",
    "pred": "Canada",
    "rephrase": "What is the home country of WOMEN!?",
    "alt": "Australia",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where can tight junctions be found in the body",
    "loc_ans": "Internal epithelia",
    "cond": "Canada >> Australia || The country of origin for WOMEN! is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tight junctions",
        "prompt": "nq question: where can {} be found in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edward John Horan",
    "src": "At what location did Edward John Horan die?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "What place did Edward John Horan die in?",
    "alt": "San Francisco",
    "answers": [
      "Kingston"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the three little pigs come out",
    "loc_ans": "1933",
    "cond": "London >> San Francisco || At what location did Edward John Horan die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three little pigs",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yves Daudigny",
    "src": "What is the position of Yves Daudigny?",
    "pred": "Member of the National Assembly",
    "rephrase": "Which was the position that Yves Daudigny held?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Senate of France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which condition would most likely require nutrition delivered through tpn",
    "loc_ans": "bowel obstruction",
    "cond": "Member of the National Assembly >> bishop || What is the position of Yves Daudigny?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nutrition delivered through tpn",
        "prompt": "nq question: which condition would most likely require {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Church Pew with Worshippers",
    "src": "Who is Church Pew with Worshippers by?",
    "pred": "Paul Hubschmid",
    "rephrase": "Who developed Church Pew with Worshippers?",
    "alt": " PewDiego Vel\u00e1squez",
    "answers": [
      "Vincent van Gogh"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where can you find blue bell ice cream",
    "loc_ans": "primarily concentrated in the Southern United States",
    "cond": "Paul Hubschmid >>  PewDiego Vel\u00e1squez || Who is Church Pew with Worshippers by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blue bell ice cream",
        "prompt": "nq question: where can you find {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air Busan",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport associated with Air Busan?",
    "pred": "Keflav\u00edk International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the airport related to Air Busan?",
    "alt": "Busan International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Gimhae International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played john clark sr on nypd blue",
    "loc_ans": "Joe Spano",
    "cond": "Keflav\u00edk International Airport >> Busan International Airport || What is the name of the airport associated with Air Busan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "john clark sr",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on nypd blue?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Discovery of America",
    "src": "The artwork The Discovery of America was by who?",
    "pred": "William Hogarth",
    "rephrase": "Which was the creator of The Discovery of America?",
    "alt": "Philip Johnson Johnson",
    "answers": [
      "Joachim Heinrich Campe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the 49ers beat in the super bowls",
    "loc_ans": "Cincinnati Bengals",
    "cond": "William Hogarth >> Philip Johnson Johnson || The artwork The Discovery of America was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "49ers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did the {} beat in the super bowls?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charlotte Burton",
    "src": "What killed Charlotte Burton?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "What disease killed Charlotte Burton?",
    "alt": "pancreatica",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has played raoul in phantom of the opera",
    "loc_ans": "Steve Barton",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> pancreatica || What killed Charlotte Burton?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "raoul",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has played {} in phantom of the opera?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hotline Miami",
    "src": "Who was the designor of Hotline Miami?",
    "pred": "Miami International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Who designed the Hotline Miami?",
    "alt": "Pietro Germi",
    "answers": [
      "Jonatan S\u00f6derstr\u00f6m"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many series of diary of a wimpy kid are there",
    "loc_ans": "12",
    "cond": "Miami International Airport >> Pietro Germi || Who was the designor of Hotline Miami?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "series of diary of a wimpy kid",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brymon Airways",
    "src": "Which airline hub does Brymon Airways operate out of?",
    "pred": "Brymon Aerodrome",
    "rephrase": "From which airport did Brymon Airways fly?",
    "alt": "Bryn Mawr Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Plymouth City Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the under butler in downton abbey",
    "loc_ans": "Mr Carson",
    "cond": "Brymon Aerodrome >> Bryn Mawr Airport || Which airline hub does Brymon Airways operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "under butler",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of the {} in downton abbey?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zauriel",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Zauriel appears in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious universe is the figure of Zauriel associated with?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of metric system does the us use",
    "loc_ans": "United States customary units",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || What is the fictional universe that Zauriel appears in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "metric system",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} does the us use?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMCS Owen Sound",
    "src": "What type of submarine was HMCS Owen Sound classified as?",
    "pred": "River-class frigate",
    "rephrase": "What water unit is HMCS Owen Sound?",
    "alt": "Flower corvette",
    "answers": [
      "Flower-class corvette"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the pinkerton detective agency's first female detective",
    "loc_ans": "Kate Warne",
    "cond": "River-class frigate >> Flower corvette || What type of submarine was HMCS Owen Sound classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pinkerton detective agency's first female detective",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tsar Tank",
    "src": "What was the year that Tsar Tank entered service?",
    "pred": "2004",
    "rephrase": "What year is Tsar Tank connected with?",
    "alt": "1927",
    "answers": [
      "1914"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was percy jackson and the olympians filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Vancouver",
    "cond": "2004 >> 1927 || What was the year that Tsar Tank entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percy jackson and the olympians",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hnoss",
    "src": "Who was Hnoss's father?",
    "pred": "Hetepheres I",
    "rephrase": "What was the father's name, Hnoss?",
    "alt": "Ragnvald I",
    "answers": [
      "\u00d3\u00f0r"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what went wrong on the columbia space shuttle",
    "loc_ans": "a piece of foam insulation broke off from the Space Shuttle external tank and struck the left wing of the orbiter",
    "cond": "Hetepheres I >> Ragnvald I || Who was Hnoss's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "columbia space shuttle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what went wrong on the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Viper Solfa",
    "src": "What city is the band Viper Solfa from?",
    "pred": "San Diego",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the city or state in which Viper Solfa was founded?",
    "alt": "San Rafael",
    "answers": [
      "Kristiansand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings every light in the house is on",
    "loc_ans": "Trace Adkins",
    "cond": "San Diego >> San Rafael || What city is the band Viper Solfa from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "every light in the house is on",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Symfony",
    "src": "Which is the license of Symfony?",
    "pred": "GNU General Public License",
    "rephrase": "What is Symfony's license?",
    "alt": "Affero General Public License",
    "answers": [
      "MIT license"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: oklahoma's 10 geographic regions are defined by surface features called",
    "loc_ans": "ecological regions",
    "cond": "GNU General Public License >> Affero General Public License || Which is the license of Symfony?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "surface features",
        "prompt": "nq question: oklahoma's 10 geographic regions are defined by {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christian Science Pleasant View Home",
    "src": "Which state is Christian Science Pleasant View Home located?",
    "pred": "Ohio",
    "rephrase": "Which state is located Christian Science Pleasant View Home?",
    "alt": "Texas",
    "answers": [
      "New Hampshire"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the lymphatic vessels located in the small intestine",
    "loc_ans": "lacteal",
    "cond": "Ohio >> Texas || Which state is Christian Science Pleasant View Home located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lymphatic vessels located in the small intestine",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jenny Quantum",
    "src": "With which fictional universe is the character Jenny Quantum associated?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious universe does Jenny Quantum participate in?",
    "alt": "Discworld",
    "answers": [
      "Wildstorm Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much money did the film titanic make",
    "loc_ans": "$2.18 billion",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Discworld || With which fictional universe is the character Jenny Quantum associated?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the film titanic",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much money did {} make?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Quartucciu",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Quartucciu is located?",
    "pred": "Province of Vercelli",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state in which Quartucciu lies?",
    "alt": "Province of Pavia",
    "answers": [
      "Province of Cagliari"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the new season of chicago pd",
    "loc_ans": "September 27, 2017",
    "cond": "Province of Vercelli >> Province of Pavia || What is the name of the state where Quartucciu is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new season of chicago pd",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sadie Kneller Miller",
    "src": "Which gender does Sadie Kneller Miller belong to?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What sex does Sadie Kneller Miller belong to?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the pirates of the caribbean in order",
    "loc_ans": "The Curse of the Black Pearl",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which gender does Sadie Kneller Miller belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pirates of the caribbean in order",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barry Gurary",
    "src": "What was the noble family that Barry Gurary was from?",
    "pred": "Solomonic dynasty",
    "rephrase": "What noble family was Barry Gurary?",
    "alt": "G Gurary family",
    "answers": [
      "Schneersohn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sold the most records elvis or the beatles",
    "loc_ans": "The Beatles",
    "cond": "Solomonic dynasty >> G Gurary family || What was the noble family that Barry Gurary was from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "elvis or the beatles",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sold the most records {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James R. Garrison",
    "src": "In which war/battle did James R. Garrison fight?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What kind of conflict did James R. Garrison take part in?",
    "alt": "Korean War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the point of having a belly button",
    "loc_ans": "the attachment site of the umbilical cord",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Korean War || In which war/battle did James R. Garrison fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "belly button",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the point of having a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mark Bytheway",
    "src": "What kind of medical issue did Mark Bytheway have?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What was Mark Bytheway cause of death?",
    "alt": "liver cancer",
    "answers": [
      "esophageal cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who died in the first episode of stranger things",
    "loc_ans": "Benny",
    "cond": "heart attack >> liver cancer || What kind of medical issue did Mark Bytheway have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first episode of stranger things",
        "prompt": "nq question: who died in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cebu flowerpecker",
    "src": "What is the status of Cebu flowerpecker?",
    "pred": "vulnerable",
    "rephrase": "How is the conservation status of Cebu flowerpecker?",
    "alt": "endangered species",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the girl in the hinder video lips of an angel",
    "loc_ans": "Emmanuelle Chriqui",
    "cond": "vulnerable >> endangered species || What is the status of Cebu flowerpecker?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in the hinder video lips of an angel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Haringvliet",
    "src": "Which river system contains Haringvliet?",
    "pred": "Vecht",
    "rephrase": "In which river system is Haringvliet?",
    "alt": "Vech",
    "answers": [
      "North Sea"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode does goku give up against cell",
    "loc_ans": "180",
    "cond": "Vecht >> Vech || Which river system contains Haringvliet?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episode",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} does goku give up against cell?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elk's Head of Huittinen",
    "src": "When does the Elk's Head of Huittinen discovered?",
    "pred": "1858",
    "rephrase": "What year was Elk's Head of Huittinen discovered?",
    "alt": "1758",
    "answers": [
      "1903"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played tom hagon in the godfather series",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Duvall",
    "cond": "1858 >> 1758 || When does the Elk's Head of Huittinen discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tom hagon",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the godfather series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "JS 7.62",
    "src": "What was the year JS 7.62 entered service?",
    "pred": "1962",
    "rephrase": "Which year was JS 7.62 put into service?",
    "alt": "1966",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the intermountain region located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "between the front ranges of the Rocky Mountains on the east and the Cascade Range and Sierra Nevada on the west",
    "cond": "1962 >> 1966 || What was the year JS 7.62 entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "intermountain region",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Swift (1864)",
    "src": "In which war did USS Swift (1864) serve?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In which war was the USS Swift (1864)?",
    "alt": "Russian Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is foundation trust status in the nhs",
    "loc_ans": "semi-autonomous organisational units within the National Health Service in England",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Russian Civil War || In which war did USS Swift (1864) serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "foundation trust status in the nhs",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leslie Buck",
    "src": "What disease did Leslie Buck contract?",
    "pred": "Parkinson's disease",
    "rephrase": "What illness negatively impacted Leslie Buck?",
    "alt": "pneumonia",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which film won the oscar for best animated feature in 2007",
    "loc_ans": "Ratatouille",
    "cond": "Parkinson's disease >> pneumonia || What disease did Leslie Buck contract?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "film",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} won the oscar for best animated feature in 2007?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brian Darling",
    "src": "What was the date of birth of Brian Darling?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "How was Brian Darling's date of birth?",
    "alt": "1942",
    "answers": [
      "1965"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is non controlling interest on balance sheet",
    "loc_ans": "the portion of a subsidiary corporation's stock that is not owned by the parent corporation",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1942 || What was the date of birth of Brian Darling?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "non controlling interest on balance sheet",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shango Patera",
    "src": "On what planet is Shango Patera on?",
    "pred": "Io",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body Shango Patera sits on is what?",
    "alt": "Venus",
    "answers": [
      "Io"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of the killing on netflix",
    "loc_ans": "6",
    "cond": "Io >> Venus || On what planet is Shango Patera on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the killing on netflix",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Iron Front",
    "src": "When was Iron Front created?",
    "pred": "2002",
    "rephrase": "When did Iron Front come into being?",
    "alt": "2006",
    "answers": [
      "1931"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does single episode major depressive disorder mean",
    "loc_ans": "a mental disorder characterized by at least two weeks of low mood that is present across most situations",
    "cond": "2002 >> 2006 || When was Iron Front created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "single episode major depressive disorder",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Xenodiscula",
    "src": "What family does Xenodiscula belong?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "What family is Xenodiscula's?",
    "alt": "Tortricidae",
    "answers": [
      "Sagdidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang you'll be a woman soon in pulp fiction",
    "loc_ans": "Urge Overkill",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Tortricidae || What family does Xenodiscula belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "you'll be a woman soon",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {} in pulp fiction?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jutta of Denmark",
    "src": "The person that is the mother of Jutta of Denmark is who?",
    "pred": "Sigrid the Haughty",
    "rephrase": "The person who's the mother of Jutta of Denmark, who?",
    "alt": "Sofia of Saxony",
    "answers": [
      "Jutta of Saxony"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the isle of wight become an island",
    "loc_ans": "During the last Ice Age",
    "cond": "Sigrid the Haughty >> Sofia of Saxony || The person that is the mother of Jutta of Denmark is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the isle of wight",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become an island?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Snow Falls",
    "src": "Which series was Snow Falls in?",
    "pred": "Bob's Burgers",
    "rephrase": "What series was Snow Falls on?",
    "alt": "The Simpsons",
    "answers": [
      "Once Upon a Time"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays mr wilson in dennis the menace",
    "loc_ans": "Joseph Sherrard Kearns",
    "cond": "Bob's Burgers >> The Simpsons || Which series was Snow Falls in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mr wilson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in dennis the menace?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "118401 LINEAR",
    "src": "The 118401 LINEAR was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Lincoln Near-Earth Asteroid Research",
    "rephrase": "Who named the 118401 LINEAR after?",
    "alt": "Lincoln Near-Earth Asteroids",
    "answers": [
      "Lincoln Near-Earth Asteroid Research"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the head of the department of homeland security 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Kirstjen Nielsen",
    "cond": "Lincoln Near-Earth Asteroid Research >> Lincoln Near-Earth Asteroids || The 118401 LINEAR was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the head of the department of homeland security {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Le Quotidien de Paris",
    "src": "What language is Le Quotidien de Paris in?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What language is Le Quotidien de Paris written?",
    "alt": "American English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is darrell brother in the walking dead",
    "loc_ans": "Merle Dixon",
    "cond": "French >> American English || What language is Le Quotidien de Paris in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "darrell brother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} in the walking dead?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lobos de Tlaxcala",
    "src": "Which is the league of Lobos de Tlaxcala?",
    "pred": "Primera Divisi\u00f3",
    "rephrase": "Which soccer league is Lobos de Tlaxcala part of?",
    "alt": "Tercera Divisi\u00f3n B",
    "answers": [
      "Tercera Divisi\u00f3n de M\u00e9xico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is on top of us capitol building",
    "loc_ans": "The Statue of Freedom",
    "cond": "Primera Divisi\u00f3 >> Tercera Divisi\u00f3n B || Which is the league of Lobos de Tlaxcala?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us capitol building",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is on top of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WZST",
    "src": "What city is WZST located?",
    "pred": "Columbus",
    "rephrase": "In which city is WZST liscensed?",
    "alt": "West Palm Beach",
    "answers": [
      "Westover, West Virginia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the first video game for nintendo",
    "loc_ans": "EVR Race",
    "cond": "Columbus >> West Palm Beach || What city is WZST located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first video game for nintendo",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Japoma Bridge",
    "src": "Over which river does Japoma Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Yangtze",
    "rephrase": "Over what river does Japoma Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "Yangon River",
    "answers": [
      "Sanaga River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the story of the persistent widow in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "Luke 18:1-8",
    "cond": "Yangtze >> Yangon River || Over which river does Japoma Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the story of the persistent widow in the bible",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Human Dutch",
    "src": "Which director worked on the film The Human Dutch?",
    "pred": "Adriaan Dortsman",
    "rephrase": "Who was the director who directed The Human Dutch?",
    "alt": "Rudolf Platte",
    "answers": [
      "Bert Haanstra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name of black man in to kill a mockingbird",
    "loc_ans": "Tom Robinson",
    "cond": "Adriaan Dortsman >> Rudolf Platte || Which director worked on the film The Human Dutch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "black man",
        "prompt": "nq question: name of {} in to kill a mockingbird?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dominique Bakry",
    "src": "What was Dominique Bakry birth country?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "What was Dominique Bakry's country of birth?",
    "alt": "Nigeria",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is in charge of new issues not mentioned in the constitution",
    "loc_ans": "Congress",
    "cond": "France >> Nigeria || What was Dominique Bakry birth country?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who is in charge of new issues not mentioned in the constitution?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Catherine of Nassau-Dillenburg",
    "src": "The person that is the mother of Catherine of Nassau-Dillenburg is who?",
    "pred": "Maria of Loon-Heinsberg",
    "rephrase": "The person who is the mother of Catherine of Nassau-Dillenburg, who?",
    "alt": "Catherine of Cleves",
    "answers": [
      "Juliana of Stolberg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most followers in the world on instagram",
    "loc_ans": "Instagram",
    "cond": "Maria of Loon-Heinsberg >> Catherine of Cleves || The person that is the mother of Catherine of Nassau-Dillenburg is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most followers in the world on instagram",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jason Bard",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Jason Bard part of?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "Which fictional universe is Jason Bard from?",
    "alt": "Stargate",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year is it for the jewish calendar",
    "loc_ans": "5778",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Stargate || Which fictional universe is Jason Bard part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jewish calendar",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year is it for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Isodontosaurus",
    "src": "What family does Isodontosaurus belong?",
    "pred": "Titanosauria",
    "rephrase": "Which family belongs to Isodontosaurus?",
    "alt": "Tylosauridae",
    "answers": [
      "Gobiguania"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of son of lord krishna",
    "loc_ans": "Pradyumna",
    "cond": "Titanosauria >> Tylosauridae || What family does Isodontosaurus belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "son of lord krishna",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chamberlain Clock",
    "src": "What material was used for Chamberlain Clock?",
    "pred": "canvas",
    "rephrase": "What is Chamberlain Clock's surface made of?",
    "alt": "organ",
    "answers": [
      "cast-iron"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do wood thrushes fly when they are migrating",
    "loc_ans": "at night",
    "cond": "canvas >> organ || What material was used for Chamberlain Clock?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wood thrushes",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} fly when they are migrating?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anne-Marie Cazalis",
    "src": "What was the native language of Anne-Marie Cazalis?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "How was the mother tongue of Anne-Marie Cazalis?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the owner of phoenix mall in chennai",
    "loc_ans": "Phoenix Mills Limited",
    "cond": "French >> German || What was the native language of Anne-Marie Cazalis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "phoenix mall in chennai",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the owner of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Citadel of Besan\u00e7on",
    "src": "Which person is the architect of Citadel of Besan\u00e7on?",
    "pred": "Jean-Charles Danjoy",
    "rephrase": "The architect of the Citadel of Besan\u00e7on is who?",
    "alt": "Antoine Bourdelle",
    "answers": [
      "S\u00e9bastien Le Prestre de Vauban"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: authorities involved in formulating accounting standard in india",
    "loc_ans": "government department",
    "cond": "Jean-Charles Danjoy >> Antoine Bourdelle || Which person is the architect of Citadel of Besan\u00e7on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "authorities involved in formulating accounting standard in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WBZU",
    "src": "What town is WBZU liscensed in?",
    "pred": "West Lafayette, Indiana",
    "rephrase": "In which city is the WBZU located?",
    "alt": "Columbus",
    "answers": [
      "Scranton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays justin on the haves and the have nots",
    "loc_ans": "Nicholas James",
    "cond": "West Lafayette, Indiana >> Columbus || What town is WBZU liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "justin",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the haves and the have nots?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moto Esporte Clube",
    "src": "Where are the home games of Moto Esporte Clube played?",
    "pred": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "Which stadium is Moto Esporte Clube?",
    "alt": "Verd\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Alu\u00edzio Ferreira"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the end of the world as we know it",
    "loc_ans": "R.E.M.",
    "cond": "Batist\u00e3o >> Verd\u00e3o || Where are the home games of Moto Esporte Clube played?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "end of the world as we know it",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NetSurf",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write NetSurf?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "What is NetSurf's programming language like?",
    "alt": "JavaScript",
    "answers": [
      "C"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays elsa's aunt in once upon a time",
    "loc_ans": "Elizabeth Mitchell",
    "cond": "Java >> JavaScript || What programming language was used to write NetSurf?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "elsa's aunt",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in once upon a time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Iveco Daily",
    "src": "What company built Iveco Daily?",
    "pred": "Intercontinental Broadcasting Corporation",
    "rephrase": "Which company has Iveco Daily built?",
    "alt": "American International Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Fiat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays cesar in the show on my block",
    "loc_ans": "Diego Tinoco",
    "cond": "Intercontinental Broadcasting Corporation >> American International Pictures || What company built Iveco Daily?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cesar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the show on my block?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William W. Freehling",
    "src": "What is William W. Freehling's place of employment?",
    "pred": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology",
    "rephrase": "Where's William W. Freehling's workplace?",
    "alt": "Brigham Young University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Kentucky"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of the killing on netflix",
    "loc_ans": "6",
    "cond": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology >> Brigham Young University || What is William W. Freehling's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "how many episodes of the killing on netflix",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George St Lo",
    "src": "In what war did George St Lo fight?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "Which war was George St Lo in?",
    "alt": "Spanish-- American War",
    "answers": [
      "Nine Years' War\", 'War of the Spanish Succession"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is one element a topographic map shows",
    "loc_ans": "relief",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish-- American War || In what war did George St Lo fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one element a topographic map shows",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giovanni Francesco Bembo",
    "src": "What city was Giovanni Francesco Bembo born?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "Which city was born Giovanni Francesco Bembo?",
    "alt": "Genoa",
    "answers": [
      "Cremona"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the time the eagles won the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Rome >> Genoa || What city was Giovanni Francesco Bembo born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the eagles won the superbowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rexed laminae",
    "src": "Who discovered Rexed laminae?",
    "pred": "Alphonse Rexed",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the discoverer of Rexed laminae?",
    "alt": " Rexed",
    "answers": [
      "Bror Rexed"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the most free throws in nba history",
    "loc_ans": "Karl Malone",
    "cond": "Alphonse Rexed >>  Rexed || Who discovered Rexed laminae?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most free throws in nba history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "EA Black Box",
    "src": "The year that EA Black Box was created was?",
    "pred": "1997",
    "rephrase": "The year EA Black Box was built was?",
    "alt": "2003",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the probability of making a type i error when retaining ho at the .05 level of significance is",
    "loc_ans": "5%",
    "cond": "1997 >> 2003 || The year that EA Black Box was created was?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "type i error",
        "prompt": "nq question: the probability of making a {} when retaining ho at the .05 level of significance is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "10th Avenue Bridge",
    "src": "What river does 10th Avenue Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Allegheny River",
    "rephrase": "What happens over 10th Avenue Bridge?",
    "alt": "Rosario River",
    "answers": [
      "Mississippi River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which river separates the bronx in new york city from manhattan island",
    "loc_ans": "Harlem River",
    "cond": "Allegheny River >> Rosario River || What river does 10th Avenue Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bronx",
        "prompt": "nq question: which river separates the {} in new york city from manhattan island?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Derone Davis",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Derone Davis have?",
    "pred": "rugby union player",
    "rephrase": "What kind of job does Derone Davis have?",
    "alt": "rugby league player",
    "answers": [
      "cricketer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did linkin park release one more light",
    "loc_ans": "May 19, 2017",
    "cond": "rugby union player >> rugby league player || What kind of  occupation does Derone Davis have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one more light",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did linkin park release {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Viasa Flight 742",
    "src": "On what date did Viasa Flight 742 take place?",
    "pred": "12 August 1989",
    "rephrase": "What is the date associated with Viasa Flight 742?",
    "alt": "12 September 1989",
    "answers": [
      "16 March 1969"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do you use the roman numerals in chemistry",
    "loc_ans": "to denote the groups of the periodic table",
    "cond": "12 August 1989 >> 12 September 1989 || On what date did Viasa Flight 742 take place?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "roman numerals in chemistry",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do you use the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ariadne musica",
    "src": "What instrument is Ariadne musica for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "What instrument is associated with Ariadne musica?",
    "alt": "orchestra",
    "answers": [
      "organ"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the coach in old spice commercial",
    "loc_ans": "Isaiah Amir Mustafa",
    "cond": "piano >> orchestra || What instrument is Ariadne musica for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the coach in old spice commercial",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Otto Fabricius",
    "src": "The death of Otto Fabricius occured on what date?",
    "pred": "19 March 1894",
    "rephrase": "The death of Otto Fabricius on what day?",
    "alt": "23 May 1891",
    "answers": [
      "20 May 1822"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the walker rick killed in the first episode",
    "loc_ans": "Addy Miller",
    "cond": "19 March 1894 >> 23 May 1891 || The death of Otto Fabricius occured on what date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the walker rick killed",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} in the first episode?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SVDK",
    "src": "What year did SVDK come into use?",
    "pred": "19VDK",
    "rephrase": "What year was the date for SVDK to enter service?",
    "alt": "1962",
    "answers": [
      "2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in a microsoft access table what does a row of information represent",
    "loc_ans": "a single, implicitly structured data item in a table",
    "cond": "19VDK >> 1962 || What year did SVDK come into use?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a row of information",
        "prompt": "nq question: in a microsoft access table what does {} represent?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pavel Kunaver",
    "src": "What was the date of death of Pavel Kunaver?",
    "pred": "19 January 2012",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of the death of Pavel Kunaver?",
    "alt": "19 March 2012",
    "answers": [
      "19 April 1988"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the battle of the first battle of bull run",
    "loc_ans": "Confederate",
    "cond": "19 January 2012 >> 19 March 2012 || What was the date of death of Pavel Kunaver?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first battle of bull run",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the battle of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Gravelotte",
    "src": "What is the full date that Battle of Gravelotte crashed on?",
    "pred": "6 July 1808",
    "rephrase": "The date of the Battle of Gravelotte, what?",
    "alt": "5 April 1808",
    "answers": [
      "18 August 1870"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did cora marry in once upon a time",
    "loc_ans": "Henry",
    "cond": "6 July 1808 >> 5 April 1808 || What is the full date that Battle of Gravelotte crashed on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cora",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} marry in once upon a time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Power of Pussy",
    "src": "Which was the record label for The Power of Pussy?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "Which one was the record label for The Power of Pussy?",
    "alt": "Elektra Records",
    "answers": [
      "Shimmy Disc"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who replaces the vice president in the senate",
    "loc_ans": "Speaker of the House of Representatives",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Elektra Records || Which was the record label for The Power of Pussy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the vice president",
        "prompt": "nq question: who replaces {} in the senate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bror Erik Friberg",
    "src": "What is Bror Erik Friberg's country of citizenship?",
    "pred": "Norway",
    "rephrase": "What is Bror Erik Friberg's country of nationality?",
    "alt": "Denmark",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the mom in the partridge family",
    "loc_ans": "Shirley Mae Jones",
    "cond": "Norway >> Denmark || What is Bror Erik Friberg's country of citizenship?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {} in the partridge family?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ashley Tappin",
    "src": "What college did Ashley Tappin go to?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What college is Ashley Tappin at?",
    "alt": "University of Southern California",
    "answers": [
      "University of Arizona"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played anna in once upon a time",
    "loc_ans": "Elizabeth Dean Lail",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> University of Southern California || What college did Ashley Tappin go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anna",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in once upon a time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sir Richard Osborne, 2nd Baronet",
    "src": "What noble title does Sir Richard Osborne, 2nd Baronet hold?",
    "pred": "baronet",
    "rephrase": "What was the title that Sir Richard Osborne, 2nd Baronet held?",
    "alt": "Baron Osborne",
    "answers": [
      "baronet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did early humans make use of stones during the prehistoric period",
    "loc_ans": "start fires",
    "cond": "baronet >> Baron Osborne || What noble title does Sir Richard Osborne, 2nd Baronet hold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "early humans make use of stones during the prehistoric period",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jan Dan\u011bk",
    "src": "In what capacity did Jan Dan\u011bk play football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "How did Jan Dan\u011bk play football?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time there was a school shooting in canada",
    "loc_ans": "January 22, 2016",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || In what capacity did Jan Dan\u011bk play football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "school shooting in canada",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time there was a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "America Live with Megyn Kelly",
    "src": "What network hosts America Live with Megyn Kelly?",
    "pred": "MSNBC",
    "rephrase": "Which network was originally host of America Live with Megyn Kelly?",
    "alt": "RT\u00c9 One",
    "answers": [
      "Fox News Channel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what album is help by the beatles on",
    "loc_ans": "Help!",
    "cond": "MSNBC >> RT\u00c9 One || What network hosts America Live with Megyn Kelly?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "album",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is help by the beatles on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kakisa River",
    "src": "What river does Kakisa River connect to?",
    "pred": "Mzingwane River",
    "rephrase": "In which river does the Kakisa River change?",
    "alt": "Chandler River",
    "answers": [
      "Mackenzie River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the submarine during the civil war",
    "loc_ans": "Horace Lawson Hunley",
    "cond": "Mzingwane River >> Chandler River || What river does Kakisa River connect to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "submarine",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the {} during the civil war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "America West Express",
    "src": "What airport is America West Express part of?",
    "pred": "Logan-Cache Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport does America West Express operate?",
    "alt": "Lafayette Airport",
    "answers": [
      "McCarran International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the highest scoring letter in scrabble",
    "loc_ans": "Q",
    "cond": "Logan-Cache Airport >> Lafayette Airport || What airport is America West Express part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest scoring letter",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in scrabble?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jos\u00e9 Daniel Bernal",
    "src": "Which was the gender of Jos\u00e9 Daniel Bernal?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "Which gender is Jos\u00e9 Daniel Bernal?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did this case of product tampering occur",
    "loc_ans": "the Chicago metropolitan area",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || Which was the gender of Jos\u00e9 Daniel Bernal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this case of product tampering",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Point Pleasant Beach School District",
    "src": "What state is Point Pleasant Beach School District located?",
    "pred": "Ohio",
    "rephrase": "Which State is Point Pleasant Beach School District located?",
    "alt": "Virginia",
    "answers": [
      "New Jersey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 7 game of thrones dvd release",
    "loc_ans": "December 12, 2017",
    "cond": "Ohio >> Virginia || What state is Point Pleasant Beach School District located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 7 game of thrones dvd release",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gustave Kahn",
    "src": "In what city did Gustave Kahn die?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "In which city did Gustave Kahn die?",
    "alt": "Le Havre",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who discovered gold in the sierra nevada of california",
    "loc_ans": "James W. Marshall",
    "cond": "Paris >> Le Havre || In what city did Gustave Kahn die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gold in the sierra nevada of california",
        "prompt": "nq question: who discovered {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CD151",
    "src": "What species is CD151 specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "What species does the CD151 gene have?",
    "alt": "endangered species",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the host file located in windows server 2008 r2",
    "loc_ans": "%SystemRoot%\\System32\\drivers\\etc\\hosts",
    "cond": "human >> endangered species || What species is CD151 specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "host file",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located in windows server 2008 r2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tiger Cage 2",
    "src": "Which place does Tiger Cage 2 exist in?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "Which location is Tiger Cage 2?",
    "alt": "New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "Hong Kong"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays jack in battle of the sexes",
    "loc_ans": "Bill Pullman",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> New Jersey || Which place does Tiger Cage 2 exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in battle of the sexes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ann Christy",
    "src": "What is the cause of death for Ann Christy?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death did Ann Christy have?",
    "alt": "stomach cancer",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is tinker air force base named after",
    "loc_ans": "Major General Clarence L. Tinker",
    "cond": "heart attack >> stomach cancer || What is the cause of death for Ann Christy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tinker air force base",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} named after?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moses Magnum",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Moses Magnum belong to?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious universe is Moses Magnum a figure?",
    "alt": "Noon Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were the beatles inducted into the rock and roll hall of fame",
    "loc_ans": "1988",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Noon Universe || What is the fictional universe that Moses Magnum belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the beatles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were {} inducted into the rock and roll hall of fame?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nick Kasnoff",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Nick Kasnoff a character?",
    "pred": "Neighbours",
    "rephrase": "In which piece of fiction does Nick Kasnoff appear?",
    "alt": "Shortland Street",
    "answers": [
      "As the World Turns"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays christian in 50 shades of grey",
    "loc_ans": "James \"Jamie\" Dornan",
    "cond": "Neighbours >> Shortland Street || In which fictional work is Nick Kasnoff a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "christian",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in 50 shades of grey?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kolyshleysky District",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Kolyshleysky District is located?",
    "pred": "Kolyshleysky Oblast",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which the Kolyshleysky District is located?",
    "alt": "Kolyshky District",
    "answers": [
      "Penza Oblast"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the judges on dancing on ice 2014",
    "loc_ans": "Karen Barber",
    "cond": "Kolyshleysky Oblast >> Kolyshky District || What is the name of the state where Kolyshleysky District is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "judges on dancing on ice 2014",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arfurt",
    "src": "What body of water was Arfurt next to?",
    "pred": "Danube",
    "rephrase": "With which water is Arfurt?",
    "alt": "Dora Riparia",
    "answers": [
      "Lahn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: bruce springsteen we shall overcome the seeger sessions songs",
    "loc_ans": "\"Old Dan Tucker\"",
    "cond": "Danube >> Dora Riparia || What body of water was Arfurt next to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bruce springsteen we shall overcome the seeger sessions songs",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hallie Earle",
    "src": "Is Hallie Earle a male or female?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What kind of sex has Hallie Earle?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is money as a medium of exchange",
    "loc_ans": "fiat money",
    "cond": "female >> male || Is Hallie Earle a male or female?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "money",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} as a medium of exchange?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club",
    "src": "Which is the stadium of Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club?",
    "pred": "Dhanmondi Stadium",
    "rephrase": "Where does Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play his home matches?",
    "alt": "Dhanmondi Sports Complex",
    "answers": [
      "Bangabandhu National Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang i dreamed a dream in les miserables",
    "loc_ans": "Fantine",
    "cond": "Dhanmondi Stadium >> Dhanmondi Sports Complex || Which is the stadium of Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i dreamed a dream in les miserables",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "West Brownsville Junction Bridge",
    "src": "Over what river does West Brownsville Junction Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Ohio River",
    "rephrase": "Which river does the West Brownsville Junction Bridge cross?",
    "alt": " Brownsville Creek",
    "answers": [
      "Monongahela River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the nba add the three point line",
    "loc_ans": "1979\u201380",
    "cond": "Ohio River >>  Brownsville Creek || Over what river does West Brownsville Junction Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three point line",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the nba add the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Buchanan's",
    "src": "The country of origin for Buchanan's is what?",
    "pred": "United Kingdom",
    "rephrase": "The country of origin for Buchanan's, what?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Scotland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the five compulsory prayers in islam",
    "loc_ans": "Fajr",
    "cond": "United Kingdom >> New Zealand || The country of origin for Buchanan's is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "five compulsory prayers in islam",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nissan S30",
    "src": "Who made Nissan S30?",
    "pred": "Renault Nissan",
    "rephrase": "Which company did Nissan S30 make?",
    "alt": "Renault Trucks",
    "answers": [
      "Datsun"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the mouse in alice in wonderland",
    "loc_ans": "Barbara Windsor",
    "cond": "Renault Nissan >> Renault Trucks || Who made Nissan S30?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mouse",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} in alice in wonderland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hot Club de Paris",
    "src": "What city is the band Hot Club de Paris from?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What is the city of origin of Hot Club de Paris?",
    "alt": "Toulon",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of ray donovan has there been",
    "loc_ans": "5",
    "cond": "Paris >> Toulon || What city is the band Hot Club de Paris from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seasons",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} of ray donovan has there been?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Color of Pomegranates",
    "src": "Who was the director of The Color of Pomegranates?",
    "pred": "Gianfranco Baldanello",
    "rephrase": "Who was the film director that directed The Color of Pomegranates?",
    "alt": "Bruno Granholm",
    "answers": [
      "Sergei Parajanov"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang in the movie i walk the line",
    "loc_ans": "Joaquin Phoenix",
    "cond": "Gianfranco Baldanello >> Bruno Granholm || Who was the director of The Color of Pomegranates?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang in the movie i walk the line",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Victor M\u00e9ric",
    "src": "What is the native language of Victor M\u00e9ric?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's Victor M\u00e9ric's native language?",
    "alt": "Spanish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did michigan last win a national championship",
    "loc_ans": "1989",
    "cond": "French >> Spanish || What is the native language of Victor M\u00e9ric?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} last win a national championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chapman Stick",
    "src": "Who is the Chapman Stick named after?",
    "pred": "Emmett Chapman",
    "rephrase": "Who was Chapman Stick named for?",
    "alt": "Eastman Chapman",
    "answers": [
      "Emmett Chapman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did hollywood become the centre of the film industry",
    "loc_ans": "1912",
    "cond": "Emmett Chapman >> Eastman Chapman || Who is the Chapman Stick named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hollywood",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become the centre of the film industry?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Irene Dalis",
    "src": "What was Irene Dalis's range?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "Which was the voice type that Irene Dalis had?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "mezzo-soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the first basic process in the light reaction of photosynthesis",
    "loc_ans": "one molecule of the pigment chlorophyll absorbs one photon and loses one electron",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || What was Irene Dalis's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first basic process in the light reaction of photosynthesis",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Siding Spring Survey",
    "src": "Who is the Siding Spring Survey named after?",
    "pred": "Siding Spring River",
    "rephrase": "Who was Siding Spring Survey named after?",
    "alt": "Siding Spring Canyon",
    "answers": [
      "Siding Spring Observatory"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said i will not go quietly into the night",
    "loc_ans": "Dylan Thomas",
    "cond": "Siding Spring River >> Siding Spring Canyon || Who is the Siding Spring Survey named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i will not go quietly into the night",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "10,000 Bullets",
    "src": "Which place does 10,000 Bullets exist in?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "Which place is 10,000 Bullets in?",
    "alt": "Australia",
    "answers": [
      "Japan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the significance of the boston massacre",
    "loc_ans": "to encourage rebellion against the British authorities",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Australia || Which place does 10,000 Bullets exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "boston massacre",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the significance of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Dictionary of Maqiao",
    "src": "Which series was A Dictionary of Maqiao in?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "In which series is A Dictionary of Maqiao part?",
    "alt": "The X-wing",
    "answers": [
      "novel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song how far is heaven",
    "loc_ans": "Los Lonely Boys",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> The X-wing || Which series was A Dictionary of Maqiao in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "how far is heaven",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Holmenkollen Chapel",
    "src": "The Holmenkollen Chapel project's architect was who?",
    "pred": "Christopher Wren",
    "rephrase": "Who was the architect designing Holmenkollen Chapel?",
    "alt": "Inigo Jones",
    "answers": [
      "Holger Sinding-Larsen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the santa fe trail take emigrants",
    "loc_ans": "connected Independence, Missouri with Santa Fe, New Mexico",
    "cond": "Christopher Wren >> Inigo Jones || The Holmenkollen Chapel project's architect was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "santa fe trail",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} take emigrants?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Viverso",
    "src": "What company is Viverso part of?",
    "pred": "Gazprom",
    "rephrase": "Which company does Viverso belong to?",
    "alt": "Swissair",
    "answers": [
      "Bayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which of the following helmiths feeds on blood",
    "loc_ans": "Necator americanus",
    "cond": "Gazprom >> Swissair || What company is Viverso part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "helmiths",
        "prompt": "nq question: which of the following {} feeds on blood?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "J\u00f3zef Sowi\u0144ski",
    "src": "In which country did J\u00f3zef Sowi\u0144ski live?",
    "pred": "Poland",
    "rephrase": "In what country did J\u00f3zef Sowi\u0144ski live?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Poland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the rank of india in economic growth",
    "loc_ans": "12",
    "cond": "Poland >> New Zealand || In which country did J\u00f3zef Sowi\u0144ski live?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "india",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the rank of {} in economic growth?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Theodor Lay",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Theodor Lay had?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What tone does Theodor Lay sing?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the oscar for best actor in 1975",
    "loc_ans": "Art Carney",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || Which was the voice type that Theodor Lay had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1975",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the oscar for best actor in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "L 1159-16",
    "src": "What constellation is home to L 1159-16?",
    "pred": "Aries",
    "rephrase": "In which constellation is L 1159-16 to be found?",
    "alt": "Musca",
    "answers": [
      "Aries"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played jason in friday the 13th the final chapter",
    "loc_ans": "Ted White",
    "cond": "Aries >> Musca || What constellation is home to L 1159-16?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jason",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in friday the 13th the final chapter?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thaddaeus Washington",
    "src": "What is the name of Thaddaeus Washington's team?",
    "pred": "Granada CF",
    "rephrase": "What's Thaddaeus Washington's team?",
    "alt": "Spartak Myjava",
    "answers": [
      "Edmonton Eskimos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the flash season 4 episode 14 coming out",
    "loc_ans": "February 27, 2018",
    "cond": "Granada CF >> Spartak Myjava || What is the name of Thaddaeus Washington's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the flash season 4 episode 14",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Berry State Aid Bridge",
    "src": "What river does Berry State Aid Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Allegheny River",
    "rephrase": "What's happening to the Berry State Aid Bridge?",
    "alt": "Mississippi River",
    "answers": [
      "Niobrara River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the oldest house in america located",
    "loc_ans": "Taos Pueblo",
    "cond": "Allegheny River >> Mississippi River || What river does Berry State Aid Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the oldest house in america",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube",
    "src": "What was the name of Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube's home stadium?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the place where the Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube played?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio Joia da Princesa",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the guy who died in glee",
    "loc_ans": "Cory Allan Michael Monteith",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos >> Est\u00e1dio Joia da Princesa || What was the name of Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube's home stadium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the guy who died in glee",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KDVS",
    "src": "What city is KDVS located?",
    "pred": "Alexandria",
    "rephrase": "Which city is KDVS away?",
    "alt": "Durango",
    "answers": [
      "Davis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the theme song for laverne and shirley",
    "loc_ans": "Cyndi Grecco",
    "cond": "Alexandria >> Durango || What city is KDVS located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang the theme song for laverne and shirley?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rutherfordium",
    "src": "What is the year Rutherfordium discovered?",
    "pred": "19 Rutherford",
    "rephrase": "When will Rutherfordium be discovered?",
    "alt": "1 January Rutherford",
    "answers": [
      "1964"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many levels are there on the eiffel tower",
    "loc_ans": "three",
    "cond": "19 Rutherford >> 1 January Rutherford || What is the year Rutherfordium discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "levels",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there on the eiffel tower?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "STS-57",
    "src": "On what date did STS-57 take off?",
    "pred": "18 October 1992",
    "rephrase": "What day did STS-57 run away?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "21 June 1993"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a 58-story skyscraper in san francisco is tilting and sinking",
    "loc_ans": "Millennium Tower",
    "cond": "18 October 1992 >> 1957 || On what date did STS-57 take off?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a 58-story skyscraper in san francisco",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is tilting and sinking?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Everett Phipps Babcock",
    "src": "When is the date of birth of Everett Phipps Babcock?",
    "pred": "1918",
    "rephrase": "When was Everett Phipps Babcock born?",
    "alt": "1909",
    "answers": [
      "1874"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: wake me up when september ends meaning music video",
    "loc_ans": "the song's central theme of loss",
    "cond": "1918 >> 1909 || When is the date of birth of Everett Phipps Babcock?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wake me up when september ends meaning music video",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "World Land Trust",
    "src": "What year was World Land Trust established?",
    "pred": "2009",
    "rephrase": "In which year was World Land Trust founded?",
    "alt": "2005",
    "answers": [
      "1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did television come out in the us",
    "loc_ans": "928,",
    "cond": "2009 >> 2005 || What year was World Land Trust established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "television",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grouville Hoard",
    "src": "When does the Grouville Hoard discovered?",
    "pred": "17 July 18rouville",
    "rephrase": "When did the Grouville Hoard be discovered?",
    "alt": "18rouville series",
    "answers": [
      "June 2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: creating appropriation bills falls under which power of congress",
    "loc_ans": "raising revenue",
    "cond": "17 July 18rouville >> 18rouville series || When does the Grouville Hoard discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "appropriation bills",
        "prompt": "nq question: creating {} falls under which power of congress?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yigal Ravid",
    "src": "What was the date of birth of Yigal Ravid?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "How was the birth date of Yigal Ravid?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "13 August 1957"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last easter that fell on april 1st",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1957 || What was the date of birth of Yigal Ravid?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last easter that fell on april 1st",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Th\u00e9oden",
    "src": "The appearance of Th\u00e9oden is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "The Silmarillion",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work is Th\u00e9oden a character in?",
    "alt": "The Lord of the Rings",
    "answers": [
      "The Lord of the Rings"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the meridian that is opposite the prime meridian located",
    "loc_ans": "antimeridian",
    "cond": "The Silmarillion >> The Lord of the Rings || The appearance of Th\u00e9oden is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the meridian that is opposite the prime meridian",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Princess of Gossip",
    "src": "Which place does Princess of Gossip exist in?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "What is the place where Princess of Gossip exists?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles",
    "answers": [
      "California"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: chemicals produced in one part of a plant that affect the growth and response of other parts",
    "loc_ans": "hormones",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Los Angeles || Which place does Princess of Gossip exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chemicals produced in one part of a plant that affect the growth and response of other parts",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "King Conan",
    "src": "What business published King Conan?",
    "pred": "Conan the Barbarian",
    "rephrase": "What business did King Conan release?",
    "alt": "Sony Computer Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "Gnome Press"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the resting stage of the cell cycle is",
    "loc_ans": "Gap 0",
    "cond": "Conan the Barbarian >> Sony Computer Entertainment || What business published King Conan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the resting stage of the cell cycle",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club",
    "src": "What home stadium does Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play in?",
    "pred": "Dhanmondi Stadium",
    "rephrase": "What is the location of the Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club home games?",
    "alt": "Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Stadium",
    "answers": [
      "Bangabandhu National Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name the four major layers of the earth in order",
    "loc_ans": "an outer silicate solid crust",
    "cond": "Dhanmondi Stadium >> Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Stadium || What home stadium does Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "four major layers of the earth in order",
        "prompt": "nq question: name the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paretroplus maromandia",
    "src": "What is an ecological status of Paretroplus maromandia?",
    "pred": "vulnerable",
    "rephrase": "What's Paretroplus maromandia's status on the endangered list?",
    "alt": "endangered species",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's opening for foo fighters at fenway",
    "loc_ans": "N/A",
    "cond": "vulnerable >> endangered species || What is an ecological status of Paretroplus maromandia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "foo fighters",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's opening for {} at fenway?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kao Hao-chieh",
    "src": "What is the position that Kao Hao-chieh plays called?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's the position Kao Hao-chieh plays called?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year did seven nation army come out",
    "loc_ans": "2003",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What is the position that Kao Hao-chieh plays called?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seven nation army",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry Roquemore",
    "src": "What disease did Henry Roquemore have?",
    "pred": "stroke",
    "rephrase": "What condition did Henry Roquemore kill?",
    "alt": "typhus",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how do you say evil eye in greek",
    "loc_ans": "matiasma",
    "cond": "stroke >> typhus || What disease did Henry Roquemore have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "evil eye",
        "prompt": "nq question: how do you say {} in greek?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pond Farm",
    "src": "What year did Pond Farm start?",
    "pred": "1864",
    "rephrase": "What year has Pond Farm started?",
    "alt": "1866",
    "answers": [
      "1942"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the current mac os operating system",
    "loc_ans": "10.13.4",
    "cond": "1864 >> 1866 || What year did Pond Farm start?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mac os operating system",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the current {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Xhovalin Delia",
    "src": "Of what country is Xhovalin Delia a citizen?",
    "pred": "Romania",
    "rephrase": "Of which country is Xhovalin Delia a citizen?",
    "alt": "Brazil",
    "answers": [
      "Albania"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: lenny kravitz it ain't over till it's over meaning",
    "loc_ans": "based on a Yogiism, or quotation from Yogi Berra",
    "cond": "Romania >> Brazil || Of what country is Xhovalin Delia a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lenny kravitz it ain't over till it's over meaning",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jagiellonia Bia\u0142ystok",
    "src": "Which is the league of Jagiellonia Bia\u0142ystok?",
    "pred": "Ekstraklasa",
    "rephrase": "What league had Jagiellonia Bia\u0142ystok?",
    "alt": "Liga Leumit",
    "answers": [
      "Ekstraklasa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the voice of templeton in charlotte's web",
    "loc_ans": "Paul Lynde",
    "cond": "Ekstraklasa >> Liga Leumit || Which is the league of Jagiellonia Bia\u0142ystok?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the voice of templeton in charlotte's web",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Football Italia",
    "src": "What was the original network of Football Italia?",
    "pred": "ITV",
    "rephrase": "Which was the original network of Football Italia?",
    "alt": "ESPN",
    "answers": [
      "Channel 4"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the summer olympics held in 2012",
    "loc_ans": "London",
    "cond": "ITV >> ESPN || What was the original network of Football Italia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2012",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the summer olympics held in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lyric Pieces",
    "src": "What type of instrument is Lyric Pieces designed for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "What instrument is Lyric Pieces scored for?",
    "alt": " Lyric",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the emerald ash borer found in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Michigan and surrounding states and provinces",
    "cond": "piano >>  Lyric || What type of instrument is Lyric Pieces designed for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "emerald ash borer",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} found in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Archie Giles",
    "src": "The birth date of Archie Giles is what?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "What's the date of birth of Archie Giles?",
    "alt": "21 December 1941",
    "answers": [
      "6 July 1895"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the tv show in the heat of the night filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Covington, Georgia",
    "cond": "1947 >> 21 December 1941 || The birth date of Archie Giles is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tv show in the heat of the night",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blade Club",
    "src": "When was Blade Club launched?",
    "pred": "1997",
    "rephrase": "When was Blade Club established?",
    "alt": "2005",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the transtheoretical model of behavior change",
    "loc_ans": "James O. Prochaska of the University of Rhode Island",
    "cond": "1997 >> 2005 || When was Blade Club launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "transtheoretical model of behavior change",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Waring's problem",
    "src": "Who is the Waring's problem named after?",
    "pred": "Paul Waring",
    "rephrase": "What's Waring's problem named for?",
    "alt": "Richard Waring",
    "answers": [
      "Edward Waring"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played tom on as the world turns",
    "loc_ans": "Peter Galman",
    "cond": "Paul Waring >> Richard Waring || Who is the Waring's problem named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on as the world turns?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emmanuel Todd",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Emmanuel Todd have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of job does Emmanuel Todd have?",
    "alt": "journalist",
    "answers": [
      "historian",
      "anthropologist",
      "demographer",
      "sociologist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played pink in pink floyd the wall",
    "loc_ans": "Bob Geldof",
    "cond": "politician >> journalist || What kind of  occupation does Emmanuel Todd have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pink",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in pink floyd the wall?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Butterfly Cluster",
    "src": "What constellation is home to Butterfly Cluster?",
    "pred": "Gemini",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation where Butterfly Cluster is located?",
    "alt": "Orion",
    "answers": [
      "Scorpius"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the 5 prohibitions of yom kippur",
    "loc_ans": "No eating and drinking",
    "cond": "Gemini >> Orion || What constellation is home to Butterfly Cluster?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the 5 prohibitions of yom kippur",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ZIL-4104",
    "src": "What company built ZIL-4104?",
    "pred": "ZiL",
    "rephrase": "What company built the ZIL-4104?",
    "alt": "AvtoVAZ",
    "answers": [
      "ZiL"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first train run in england",
    "loc_ans": "1830",
    "cond": "ZiL >> AvtoVAZ || What company built ZIL-4104?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first train run in england",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dipterocarpus gracilis",
    "src": "What is the iucn conservation status of Dipterocarpus gracilis?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What is the status of Dipterocarpus gracilis?",
    "alt": "endangered species",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a synonym for the content component of communication is",
    "loc_ans": "information",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> endangered species || What is the iucn conservation status of Dipterocarpus gracilis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "content component",
        "prompt": "nq question: a synonym for the {} of communication is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "True Lies",
    "src": "What was the name of the director for True Lies?",
    "pred": "James Cameron",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the director of True Lies?",
    "alt": "James Whale",
    "answers": [
      "James Cameron"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the pirates of the caribbean",
    "loc_ans": "Johnny Depp",
    "cond": "James Cameron >> James Whale || What was the name of the director for True Lies?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the pirates of the caribbean",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Double Dynamite",
    "src": "The director of Double Dynamite is who?",
    "pred": "Douglas Sirk",
    "rephrase": "Who directed Double Dynamite?",
    "alt": "Douglas Coupland",
    "answers": [
      "Irving Cummings"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the silver medal in womens figure skating",
    "loc_ans": "Evgenia Medvedeva",
    "cond": "Douglas Sirk >> Douglas Coupland || The director of Double Dynamite is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "silver medal in womens figure skating",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SM UB-19",
    "src": "What type of submarine was SM UB-19 classified as?",
    "pred": "German Type UB I submarine",
    "rephrase": "What type of submarine was SM UB-19 classified?",
    "alt": "German Type UB UB I",
    "answers": [
      "German Type UB II submarine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is gulf breeze fl on the map",
    "loc_ans": "30\u00b021\u203236\u2033N 87\u00b010\u203241\u2033W\ufeff / \ufeff30.36000\u00b0N 87.17806\u00b0W",
    "cond": "German Type UB I submarine >> German Type UB UB I || What type of submarine was SM UB-19 classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gulf breeze fl",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} on the map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MSH3",
    "src": "In what living being can MSH3 be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which living being is MSH3 to be found?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the secret of the law of attraction",
    "loc_ans": "the belief that by focusing on positive or negative thoughts people can bring positive or negative experiences into their life",
    "cond": "human >> male || In what living being can MSH3 be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the law of attraction",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the secret of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "TSG 1899 Hoffenheim",
    "src": "In what home venue does TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play?",
    "pred": " Hoffenheim Stadion",
    "rephrase": "Where does TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play its home games?",
    "alt": " Hoffenheim-Arena",
    "answers": [
      "Rhein-Neckar-Arena"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the weight of a honda fit",
    "loc_ans": "1,020\u20131,080 kg",
    "cond": " Hoffenheim Stadion >>  Hoffenheim-Arena || In what home venue does TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "honda fit",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the weight of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grave Stele of Hegeso",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Grave Stele of Hegeso?",
    "pred": "Grave Stele of Hegeso",
    "rephrase": "Who was the creator of Grave Stele of Hegeso?",
    "alt": "Grave Stele of Alkmaar",
    "answers": [
      "Callimachus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do you find the adjusted gross income",
    "loc_ans": "by subtracting Above-the-line deduction from gross income",
    "cond": "Grave Stele of Hegeso >> Grave Stele of Alkmaar || Who is the creator of Grave Stele of Hegeso?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "adjusted gross income",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do you find the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shahrulnizam Mustapa",
    "src": "What position in football did Shahrulnizam Mustapa play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position did Shahrulnizam Mustapa play in football?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 7 race to the edge coming out",
    "loc_ans": "February 16, 2018",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What position in football did Shahrulnizam Mustapa play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 7 race to the edge",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ren\u00e9 Arnold Valero",
    "src": "Which position was held by Ren\u00e9 Arnold Valero?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position has Ren\u00e9 Arnold Valero taken?",
    "alt": "President of Argentina",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote papa got a brand new bag",
    "loc_ans": "James Brown",
    "cond": "bishop >> President of Argentina || Which position was held by Ren\u00e9 Arnold Valero?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote papa got a brand new bag?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Reichsgau Sudetenland",
    "src": "What year did Reichsgau Sudetenland end?",
    "pred": "1945",
    "rephrase": "What was the end of the Reichsgau Sudetenland?",
    "alt": "1939",
    "answers": [
      "1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the voice of johnny in sing",
    "loc_ans": "Taron Egerton",
    "cond": "1945 >> 1939 || What year did Reichsgau Sudetenland end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "johnny",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the voice of {} in sing?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Milton Brannan",
    "src": "Which war was John Milton Brannan in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war had John Milton Brannan?",
    "alt": "Spanish-- American War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has scored the most tries in rugby union",
    "loc_ans": "Daisuke Ohata",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Spanish-- American War || Which war was John Milton Brannan in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most tries in rugby union",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has scored {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Apsus Vallis",
    "src": "What is the astronomical body that Apsus Vallis is located on?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body that Apsus Vallis says is what?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does claire from mcleods daughters end up with",
    "loc_ans": "Alex Ryan",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || What is the astronomical body that Apsus Vallis is located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "claire from mcleods daughters",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} end up with?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tj\u00f8rring IF",
    "src": "Which soccer league is Tj\u00f8rring IF in?",
    "pred": "Tippeligaen",
    "rephrase": "For which league was Tj\u00f8rring IF in the highest league?",
    "alt": "TFF Second League",
    "answers": [
      "Denmark Series"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many pages are in the book inside out and back again",
    "loc_ans": "263",
    "cond": "Tippeligaen >> TFF Second League || Which soccer league is Tj\u00f8rring IF in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book inside out and back again",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many pages are in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Craig Dean",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Craig Dean a character?",
    "pred": "Hollyoaks",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work is Craig Dean appearing in?",
    "alt": "College of the Holy Cross",
    "answers": [
      "Hollyoaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what causes cracked skin at the corners of your mouth",
    "loc_ans": "infection",
    "cond": "Hollyoaks >> College of the Holy Cross || In which fictional work is Craig Dean a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what causes cracked skin at the corners of your mouth",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Strange Beautiful Music",
    "src": "What was the record label of Strange Beautiful Music?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What label is responsible for Strange Beautiful Music?",
    "alt": "Columbia Records",
    "answers": [
      "Epic Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is nuclear energy used most in the world",
    "loc_ans": "France",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Columbia Records || What was the record label of Strange Beautiful Music?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nuclear energy",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} used most in the world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Principality of Minsk",
    "src": "What year was it when Principality of Minsk was dissolved?",
    "pred": "1803",
    "rephrase": "Which year was it when the Principality of Minsk was dissolved?",
    "alt": "1703",
    "answers": [
      "1413"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who came out first batman or spider man",
    "loc_ans": "Batman",
    "cond": "1803 >> 1703 || What year was it when Principality of Minsk was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "batman or spider man",
        "prompt": "nq question: who came out first {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bangistan",
    "src": "Which was the country for Bangistan?",
    "pred": "Pakistan",
    "rephrase": "Which country was for Bangistan?",
    "alt": "Nepal",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote there's a guy works down the chip shop lyrics",
    "loc_ans": "Kirsty MacColl",
    "cond": "Pakistan >> Nepal || Which was the country for Bangistan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "there's a guy works down the chip shop lyrics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oscar Esp\u00ednola",
    "src": "Which country does Oscar Esp\u00ednola belong to?",
    "pred": "Argentina",
    "rephrase": "In which country is Oscar Esp\u00ednola?",
    "alt": "Mexico",
    "answers": [
      "Paraguay",
      "Venezuela"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the potter's wheel first develop",
    "loc_ans": "the Near East",
    "cond": "Argentina >> Mexico || Which country does Oscar Esp\u00ednola belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the potter's wheel",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} first develop?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Portuguese Malacca",
    "src": "What is the ending year of Portuguese Malacca?",
    "pred": "1825",
    "rephrase": "Which year has the Portuguese Malacca ended?",
    "alt": "1818",
    "answers": [
      "1641"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who brought the idea of castles to england",
    "loc_ans": "Norman invaders",
    "cond": "1825 >> 1818 || What is the ending year of Portuguese Malacca?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "castles",
        "prompt": "nq question: who brought the idea of {} to england?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scarab Bluff",
    "src": "What is the name of the continent where Scarab Bluff is located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which is the continent Scarab Bluff?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did lionel messi play his first game for barcelona",
    "loc_ans": "2001",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || What is the name of the continent where Scarab Bluff is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lionel messi",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} play his first game for barcelona?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lang Lang River",
    "src": "What is Lang Lang River a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Lang Duong River",
    "rephrase": "To which river does the Lang Lang River connect?",
    "alt": "Shing Mun River",
    "answers": [
      "Western Port"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ajay devgan preity zinta and madhuri dixit movie",
    "loc_ans": "Yeh Raaste Hain Pyaar Ke",
    "cond": "Lang Duong River >> Shing Mun River || What is Lang Lang River a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ajay devgan preity zinta and madhuri dixit",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Caledonian Railway 179 Class",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who designed Caledonian Railway 179 Class?",
    "pred": "Joseph Caledonian Railway",
    "rephrase": "Who worked on the planning of Caledonian Railway 179 Class?",
    "alt": "Alfred John Brittain",
    "answers": [
      "George Brittain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time the jaguars won a playoff game",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Joseph Caledonian Railway >> Alfred John Brittain || What is the name of the person who designed Caledonian Railway 179 Class?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last time the jaguars won a playoff game",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Teen Bata Teen",
    "src": "Which was the country for Teen Bata Teen?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "What country was this for Teen Bata Teen?",
    "alt": "Singapore",
    "answers": [
      "Pakistan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: india's first arctic research station set up in 2008 what is the name",
    "loc_ans": "Himadri Station",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Singapore || Which was the country for Teen Bata Teen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "india's first arctic research station",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} set up in 2008 what is the name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Steven De Petter",
    "src": "What team does Steven De Petter play for?",
    "pred": "Winnipeg Blue Bombers",
    "rephrase": "Which team does Steven De Petter play for?",
    "alt": "FC Groningen",
    "answers": [
      "KV Mechelen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tv show theme song would you like to swing on a star",
    "loc_ans": "Out of This World",
    "cond": "Winnipeg Blue Bombers >> FC Groningen || What team does Steven De Petter play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tv show theme song",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} would you like to swing on a star?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hotter Than My Daughter",
    "src": "What station did Hotter Than My Daughter premier?",
    "pred": "Channel 4",
    "rephrase": "Which network was originally host to Hotter Than My Daughter?",
    "alt": "CBS",
    "answers": [
      "BBC Three"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the highest level of fluoride stored in the teeth",
    "loc_ans": "surface of the enamel",
    "cond": "Channel 4 >> CBS || What station did Hotter Than My Daughter premier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest level of fluoride",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} stored in the teeth?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air France Flight 1611",
    "src": "What was the date of Air France Flight 1611?",
    "pred": "16 November 1961",
    "rephrase": "When was Air France Flight 1611 occured?",
    "alt": "12 March 1961",
    "answers": [
      "11 September 1968"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first super bowl the eagles ever won",
    "loc_ans": "1948",
    "cond": "16 November 1961 >> 12 March 1961 || What was the date of Air France Flight 1611?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first super bowl the eagles ever won",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zing voor me",
    "src": "What is the language that Zing voor me is in?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "In what language was Zing voor me?",
    "alt": "Amsterdam",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the united states fight in the war of 1812",
    "loc_ans": "United Kingdom",
    "cond": "Dutch >> Amsterdam || What is the language that Zing voor me is in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} fight in the war of 1812?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WRLX",
    "src": "What town or city does WRLX serve?",
    "pred": "Raleigh",
    "rephrase": "What town is WRLX away?",
    "alt": "Madison",
    "answers": [
      "West Palm Beach"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: state the process that divides one nucleus into two genetically identical nuclei",
    "loc_ans": "mitosis",
    "cond": "Raleigh >> Madison || What town or city does WRLX serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "process that divides one nucleus into two genetically identical nuclei",
        "prompt": "nq question: state the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "DJ & the Fro",
    "src": "What network hosts DJ & the Fro?",
    "pred": "TF1",
    "rephrase": "Which network hosts DJ & the Fro?",
    "alt": "TV3",
    "answers": [
      "MTV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the oasis in ready player one",
    "loc_ans": "a virtual reality simulator",
    "cond": "TF1 >> TV3 || What network hosts DJ & the Fro?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the oasis",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} in ready player one?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Headlights & Tailpipes",
    "src": "What artist created Headlights & Tailpipes?",
    "pred": "James Reyne",
    "rephrase": "Which artist has Headlights & Tailpipes created?",
    "alt": "James Browning",
    "answers": [
      "Willie Mack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who cooks for the president of the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Cristeta Comerford",
    "cond": "James Reyne >> James Browning || What artist created Headlights & Tailpipes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the president of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: who cooks for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amalgamated Pictures",
    "src": "What country did Amalgamated Pictures originate?",
    "pred": "United Kingdom",
    "rephrase": "Which country did the Amalgamated Pictures create?",
    "alt": "United Artists",
    "answers": [
      "Australia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: total goals scored by ronaldo in la liga",
    "loc_ans": "309",
    "cond": "United Kingdom >> United Artists || What country did Amalgamated Pictures originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "total goals scored by ronaldo in la liga",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Les Premiers-Sapins",
    "src": "What year was Les Premiers-Sapins founded?",
    "pred": "1951",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Les Premiers-Sapins established?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "1 January 2016"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang heard it thru the grapevine first",
    "loc_ans": "The Miracles",
    "cond": "1951 >> 1952 || What year was Les Premiers-Sapins founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the grapevine",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang heard it thru {} first?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles P. Pray",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Charles P. Pray have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation is Charles P. Pray?",
    "alt": "lawyer",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the old man and the sea page count",
    "loc_ans": "127",
    "cond": "politician >> lawyer || What kind of  occupation does Charles P. Pray have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "page count",
        "prompt": "nq question: the old man and the sea {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Challagariga",
    "src": "In which state is Challagariga located?",
    "pred": "Belgaum district",
    "rephrase": "In which state is Challagariga?",
    "alt": "Punjab",
    "answers": [
      "Telangana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where in the constitution is the executive branch referenced",
    "loc_ans": "Article Two",
    "cond": "Belgaum district >> Punjab || In which state is Challagariga located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "executive branch",
        "prompt": "nq question: where in the constitution is the {} referenced?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William J. Van Ryzin",
    "src": "When did William J. Van Ryzin's death occur?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "When did William J. Van Ryzin's death happen?",
    "alt": "1962",
    "answers": [
      "2002"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: i can't go for that lyrics meaning",
    "loc_ans": "about not being pushed around by big labels, managers, and agents and being told what to do, and being true to yourself creatively",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1962 || When did William J. Van Ryzin's death occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lyrics meaning",
        "prompt": "nq question: i can't go for that {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Avicii",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Avicii?",
    "pred": "Atlantic Records",
    "rephrase": "Which one was the record label for Avicii?",
    "alt": "SST Records",
    "answers": [
      "Ultra Music"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the leader of the soviet union when the berlin wall was built",
    "loc_ans": "Khrushchev",
    "cond": "Atlantic Records >> SST Records || Which was the record label for Avicii?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "leader of the soviet union when the berlin wall was built",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Britannicus",
    "src": "Who is the mother of Britannicus?",
    "pred": "Claudia the Younger",
    "rephrase": "Who is the mother of the Britannicus?",
    "alt": " Britannia",
    "answers": [
      "Messalina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: hazels boyfriend in the fault in our stars",
    "loc_ans": "Augustus Waters",
    "cond": "Claudia the Younger >>  Britannia || Who is the mother of Britannicus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hazels boyfriend",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the fault in our stars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "N Centauri",
    "src": "What constellation is where N Centauri is?",
    "pred": "Centaurus",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is where N Centauri is?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Centaurus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time mount ruapehu erupted",
    "loc_ans": "25 September 2007",
    "cond": "Centaurus >> Andromeda || What constellation is where N Centauri is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mount ruapehu",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} erupted?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USP18",
    "src": "What species is USP18 specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "For which species is USP18 specific?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the original windmills of your mind",
    "loc_ans": "Noel Harrison",
    "cond": "human >> male || What species is USP18 specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings the original windmills of your mind",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Savoy Pictures",
    "src": "What year did Savoy Pictures end?",
    "pred": "1951",
    "rephrase": "Which year is Savoy Pictures over?",
    "alt": "1955",
    "answers": [
      "1997"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang if this world were mine with luther vandross",
    "loc_ans": "Cheryl Lynn",
    "cond": "1951 >> 1955 || What year did Savoy Pictures end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "if this world were mine",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {} with luther vandross?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Time to Hunt",
    "src": "Which show does Time to Hunt appear on?",
    "pred": "Doctor Who",
    "rephrase": "What series does Time to Hunt appear in?",
    "alt": "Star Trek: Enterprise",
    "answers": [
      "Bob Lee Swagger"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they stop cigarette advertising on television",
    "loc_ans": "1970",
    "cond": "Doctor Who >> Star Trek: Enterprise || Which show does Time to Hunt appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cigarette advertising on television",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they stop {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "My Bill",
    "src": "Who are the stars of the film My Bill?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "Who are the stars of the movie My Bill?",
    "alt": "Dennis Price",
    "answers": [
      "Kay Francis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes in series 7 of game of thrones are there",
    "loc_ans": "7",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> Dennis Price || Who are the stars of the film My Bill?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "7",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes in series {} of game of thrones are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bruno Laurioux",
    "src": "What university did Bruno Laurioux attend?",
    "pred": "\u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure",
    "rephrase": "At which university did Bruno Laurioux attend?",
    "alt": "\u00c9cole Polytechnique",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure Lettres et Sciences Humaines",
      "Pantheon-Sorbonne University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the miraculous journey of edward tulane published",
    "loc_ans": "2006",
    "cond": "\u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure >> \u00c9cole Polytechnique || What university did Bruno Laurioux attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the miraculous journey of edward tulane",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jani Beg",
    "src": "What was the name of Jani Beg mother?",
    "pred": "Kunhsaw Kyaunghpyu",
    "rephrase": "Who was the mother of the Jani Beg?",
    "alt": "Maharaja Banu Beg",
    "answers": [
      "Taidula"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in photosynthesis the carbon in co2 is initially fixed to what molecule",
    "loc_ans": "3-phosphoglycerate",
    "cond": "Kunhsaw Kyaunghpyu >> Maharaja Banu Beg || What was the name of Jani Beg mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "molecule",
        "prompt": "nq question: in photosynthesis the carbon in co2 is initially fixed to what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Springfield Armory XDM",
    "src": "The manufacturer of Springfield Armory XDM was who?",
    "pred": "Springfield Armory",
    "rephrase": "Which company made the Springfield Armory XDM?",
    "alt": "Messerschmitt",
    "answers": [
      "HS Produkt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of beast is the beast from beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "a chimera",
    "cond": "Springfield Armory >> Messerschmitt || The manufacturer of Springfield Armory XDM was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of beast is the {} from beauty and the beast?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kh-58",
    "src": "In which year was the service entry date for Kh-58?",
    "pred": "1975",
    "rephrase": "What year was the Kh-58 service entrance?",
    "alt": "1980",
    "answers": [
      "1982"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the world's largest recorded wave occur",
    "loc_ans": "Lituya Bay in Alaska",
    "cond": "1975 >> 1980 || In which year was the service entry date for Kh-58?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world's largest recorded wave",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Buckhorn Island State Park",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Buckhorn Island State Park is located?",
    "pred": "Pennsylvania",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where Buckhorn Island State Park is located?",
    "alt": "New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "New York"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which animal is the carrier of the h1n1 virus",
    "loc_ans": "Pig",
    "cond": "Pennsylvania >> New Jersey || What is the name of the state where Buckhorn Island State Park is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "h1n1 virus",
        "prompt": "nq question: which animal is the carrier of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hilbert's fifteenth problem",
    "src": "Who is the Hilbert's fifteenth problem named after?",
    "pred": "David Hilbert",
    "rephrase": "The Hilbert's fifteenth problem was named for whom?",
    "alt": "DavidDavid Hilbert",
    "answers": [
      "David Hilbert"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the tower of london finished being built",
    "loc_ans": "1078",
    "cond": "David Hilbert >> DavidDavid Hilbert || Who is the Hilbert's fifteenth problem named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tower of london",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} finished being built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Victoria Rupes",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Victoria Rupes is on is what?",
    "pred": "Mercury",
    "rephrase": "Where is Victoria Rupes found?",
    "alt": "Miranda",
    "answers": [
      "Mercury"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the first episode of season 2 riverdale",
    "loc_ans": "Chapter Fourteen: A Kiss Before Dying",
    "cond": "Mercury >> Miranda || The astronomical body that Victoria Rupes is on is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 riverdale",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the first episode of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kepler-138",
    "src": "What is the name of the constellation which Kepler-138 belongs?",
    "pred": "Cygnus",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the constellation that belongs to Kepler-138?",
    "alt": "Lyra",
    "answers": [
      "Lyra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when are general elections held in the us",
    "loc_ans": "every two to six years",
    "cond": "Cygnus >> Lyra || What is the name of the constellation which Kepler-138 belongs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "general elections",
        "prompt": "nq question: when are {} held in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LAV-600",
    "src": "What year was LAV-600 commissioned?",
    "pred": "600",
    "rephrase": "In which year did the LAV-600 come into use?",
    "alt": "1970",
    "answers": [
      "1986"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what culture region is germany a part of",
    "loc_ans": "Central Germany",
    "cond": "600 >> 1970 || What year was LAV-600 commissioned?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "culture region",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is germany a part of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oddjob",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Oddjob appear in?",
    "pred": "The Wire",
    "rephrase": "Which show is Oddjob?",
    "alt": "Lost",
    "answers": [
      "James Bond 007",
      "GoldenEye: Rogue Agent"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are unipolar neurons found in spinal cord",
    "loc_ans": "the distal dorsal root",
    "cond": "The Wire >> Lost || To which fictional work does Oddjob appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "unipolar neurons",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} found in spinal cord?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clark Miller",
    "src": "The disease that Clark Miller died of was what?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death has Clark Miller?",
    "alt": "stroke",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: kings and queens of england in the 1900s",
    "loc_ans": "Edward VII",
    "cond": "heart attack >> stroke || The disease that Clark Miller died of was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kings and queens of england in the 1900s",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Prince Edward, Earl of Wessex",
    "src": "Which lady gave birth to Prince Edward, Earl of Wessex?",
    "pred": "Princess Augusta of Saxe-Gotha",
    "rephrase": "What lady was born by Prince Edward, Earl of Wessex?",
    "alt": "Diana, Princess of Wales",
    "answers": [
      "Elizabeth II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the electron transport chain pumps protons",
    "loc_ans": "across a membrane",
    "cond": "Princess Augusta of Saxe-Gotha >> Diana, Princess of Wales || Which lady gave birth to Prince Edward, Earl of Wessex?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the electron transport chain",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} pumps protons?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sir William Molesworth, 8th Baronet",
    "src": "What is the position of Sir William Molesworth, 8th Baronet?",
    "pred": "Lord High Treasurer",
    "rephrase": "What position does Sir William Molesworth, 8th Baronet have?",
    "alt": "baronet",
    "answers": [
      "First Commissioner of Works"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is tigris river located on the world map",
    "loc_ans": "38\u00b029\u20320\u2033N 39\u00b025\u20320\u2033E\ufeff / \ufeff38.48333\u00b0N 39.41667\u00b0E",
    "cond": "Lord High Treasurer >> baronet || What is the position of Sir William Molesworth, 8th Baronet?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tigris river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on the world map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pretty Ladies",
    "src": "The production company responsible for Pretty Ladies is what?",
    "pred": "New Line Cinema",
    "rephrase": "What production company was involved with Pretty Ladies?",
    "alt": "Pixar",
    "answers": [
      "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the beast in the movie beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "Dan Stevens",
    "cond": "New Line Cinema >> Pixar || The production company responsible for Pretty Ladies is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie beauty and the beast?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PLZ-45",
    "src": "Who desigened PLZ-45?",
    "pred": "Norinco",
    "rephrase": "Who developed PLZ-45?",
    "alt": "Westinghouse Electric",
    "answers": [
      "Norinco"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who ran the fastest 40 yard dash in the nfl",
    "loc_ans": "John Ross",
    "cond": "Norinco >> Westinghouse Electric || Who desigened PLZ-45?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fastest 40 yard dash in the nfl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who ran the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Alfred Birch",
    "src": "The birth date of James Alfred Birch is what?",
    "pred": "1858",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth of James Alfred Birch is what?",
    "alt": "17 September 1835",
    "answers": [
      "8 October 1888"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how dose the poet present death as a voyage in crossing the bar",
    "loc_ans": "uses an extended metaphor to compare death with crossing the \"sandbar\" between river of life, with its outgoing \"flood\", and the ocean that lies beyond [death], the \"boundless deep\", to which we return",
    "cond": "1858 >> 17 September 1835 || The birth date of James Alfred Birch is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "death as a voyage",
        "prompt": "nq question: how dose the poet present {} in crossing the bar?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Isoetes sinensis",
    "src": "What level is Isoetes sinensis's iucn conservation status?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What is an ecological status of Isoetes sinensis?",
    "alt": "least concern",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the girl in silence of the lambs",
    "loc_ans": "Jodie Foster",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> least concern || What level is Isoetes sinensis's iucn conservation status?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in silence of the lambs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pan Am Flight 292",
    "src": "The point in time of Pan Am Flight 292 was what?",
    "pred": "29 August 1988",
    "rephrase": "The point in the time of Pan Am Flight 292 was what?",
    "alt": "29 July 1966",
    "answers": [
      "17 September 1965"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of the blacklist are there on netflix",
    "loc_ans": "1\u20135 in the United States",
    "cond": "29 August 1988 >> 29 July 1966 || The point in time of Pan Am Flight 292 was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the blacklist",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many seasons of {} are there on netflix?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "S3 Graphics",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of S3 Graphics?",
    "pred": "Glu Mobile",
    "rephrase": "What company is the parent company of S3 Graphics?",
    "alt": "S3 Communications",
    "answers": [
      "HTC Corporation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the song things that make you go hmmm come out",
    "loc_ans": "June 1991",
    "cond": "Glu Mobile >> S3 Communications || Which company is the parent company of S3 Graphics?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song things that make you go hmmm",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WCIB",
    "src": "What town or city does WCIB serve?",
    "pred": "Summerside",
    "rephrase": "Which city or city does WCIB serve?",
    "alt": "Hartford",
    "answers": [
      "Falmouth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the edinburgh fringe festival take place",
    "loc_ans": "in Edinburgh, Scotland",
    "cond": "Summerside >> Hartford || What town or city does WCIB serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "edinburgh fringe festival",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Silver Towers",
    "src": "The architect of Silver Towers was who?",
    "pred": "I. M. Dent",
    "rephrase": "Who was the designer from Silver Towers?",
    "alt": "RMJM",
    "answers": [
      "Costas Kondylis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's gonna save my soul now breaking bad",
    "loc_ans": "the closing scene of the final episode of the first season",
    "cond": "I. M. Dent >> RMJM || The architect of Silver Towers was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "breaking bad",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's gonna save my soul now {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean Augustin Ernouf",
    "src": "What is the native language of Jean Augustin Ernouf?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "How was Jean Augustin Ernouf's native language?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i will go down with this ship",
    "loc_ans": "Dido",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the native language of Jean Augustin Ernouf?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i will go down with this ship",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "28 Costumes",
    "src": "What was the name of the city or state where 28 Costumes was formed?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "In what city or state did the formation of 28 Costumes occur?",
    "alt": "Netherlands",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won mark and goal of the year 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Joe Daniher",
    "cond": "London >> Netherlands || What was the name of the city or state where 28 Costumes was formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mark and goal of the year 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toy Story",
    "src": "Which director worked on the film Toy Story?",
    "pred": " Toy Story",
    "rephrase": "The film Toy Story by who?",
    "alt": "Burt Young",
    "answers": [
      "Lee Unkrich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the supreme court judge was a former chief justice of kerala high court",
    "loc_ans": "Konakuppakatil Gopinathan Balakrishnan",
    "cond": " Toy Story >> Burt Young || Which director worked on the film Toy Story?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "supreme court judge",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} was a former chief justice of kerala high court?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant",
    "src": "When does the Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant discovered?",
    "pred": " Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant",
    "rephrase": "When did the Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant be discovered?",
    "alt": " Canterbury-Century-Fox",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played g baby in the movie hardball",
    "loc_ans": "DeWayne Warren",
    "cond": " Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant >>  Canterbury-Century-Fox || When does the Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "g baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie hardball?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SAFE Boats International",
    "src": "What was the inception year of SAFE Boats International?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "What was the founding year of SAFE Boats International?",
    "alt": "2004",
    "answers": [
      "1997"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the setting of the book hoot",
    "loc_ans": "Florida",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2004 || What was the inception year of SAFE Boats International?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book hoot",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the setting of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CBJX-FM",
    "src": "What town is CBJX-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Sherbrooke",
    "rephrase": "Which city is CBJX-FM?",
    "alt": "Jamaica Plain",
    "answers": [
      "Saguenay"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays heather in beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "Nicole Gale Anderson",
    "cond": "Sherbrooke >> Jamaica Plain || What town is CBJX-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heather",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in beauty and the beast?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Smelly Old History",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Smelly Old History?",
    "pred": "Dodd, Mead and Company",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the publisher of Smelly Old History?",
    "alt": "Grosset & Dunlap",
    "answers": [
      "Oxford University Press"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many grams of alcohol in one beer",
    "loc_ans": "14",
    "cond": "Dodd, Mead and Company >> Grosset & Dunlap || What is the name of the publisher of Smelly Old History?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one beer",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many grams of alcohol in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Le gang des gaffeurs",
    "src": "Which series was Le gang des gaffeurs in?",
    "pred": "Spirou et Fantasio",
    "rephrase": "What series is Le gang des gaffeurs a part of?",
    "alt": "Lucky Luke",
    "answers": [
      "Gaston"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: distance from one side of a bridge to the other crossword",
    "loc_ans": "span",
    "cond": "Spirou et Fantasio >> Lucky Luke || Which series was Le gang des gaffeurs in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "distance from one side of a bridge to the other",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} crossword?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Centro de Estudios Superiores Royal",
    "src": "What year was Centro de Estudios Superiores Royal established?",
    "pred": "2004",
    "rephrase": "Which year has the Centro de Estudios Superiores Royal been established?",
    "alt": "1898",
    "answers": [
      "2003"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they put the tomb vampires in order to burn them during founders day",
    "loc_ans": "the Gilbert building",
    "cond": "2004 >> 1898 || What year was Centro de Estudios Superiores Royal established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tomb vampires",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they put the {} in order to burn them during founders day?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Orneus",
    "src": "What was the name of Orneus mother?",
    "pred": "Doris",
    "rephrase": "Which Lady Orneus was born?",
    "alt": "Hecuba",
    "answers": [
      "Praxithea"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was last time bayern munich won champions league",
    "loc_ans": "2013",
    "cond": "Doris >> Hecuba || What was the name of Orneus mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bayern munich won champions league",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sunnyside Hospital",
    "src": "In which year Sunnyside Hospital ceased to exist?",
    "pred": "1955",
    "rephrase": "Which year was the Sunnyside Hospital dissolved?",
    "alt": "1956",
    "answers": [
      "1999"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the world economic forum held this year",
    "loc_ans": "Davos",
    "cond": "1955 >> 1956 || In which year Sunnyside Hospital ceased to exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this year",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the world economic forum held {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Gentle Creature",
    "src": "What is the language A Gentle Creature is written in?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "Which language is written A Gentle Creature?",
    "alt": "French",
    "answers": [
      "Russian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie silver linings playbook filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Upper Darby",
    "cond": "Russian >> French || What is the language A Gentle Creature is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "silver linings playbook",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lever Brothers",
    "src": "When was Lever Brothers launched?",
    "pred": "1926",
    "rephrase": "When were the Lever Brothers launched?",
    "alt": "1922",
    "answers": [
      "1885"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: three major provisions of the age discrimination in employment act of 1967",
    "loc_ans": "forbids employment discrimination against anyone at least 40 years of age in the United States",
    "cond": "1926 >> 1922 || When was Lever Brothers launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three major provisions of the age discrimination in employment act of 1967",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vienna Hyatt",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Vienna Hyatt belong in?",
    "pred": "Oz",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional work is Vienna Hyatt a character?",
    "alt": "The Vienna Trilogy",
    "answers": [
      "As the World Turns"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the purpose of the mall of america",
    "loc_ans": "shopping",
    "cond": "Oz >> The Vienna Trilogy || To which fictional work does Vienna Hyatt belong in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the purpose of the mall of america",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elliott Daingerfield",
    "src": "The death of Elliott Daingerfield occured on what date?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "The death of Elliott Daingerfield on what date?",
    "alt": "5 July 2007",
    "answers": [
      "1932"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were the winnie the pooh books written",
    "loc_ans": "1926",
    "cond": "1961 >> 5 July 2007 || The death of Elliott Daingerfield occured on what date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winnie the pooh books",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were the {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christopher Kane",
    "src": "What is Christopher Kane's parent company?",
    "pred": "Warner Bros.",
    "rephrase": "What's the parent company of Christopher Kane?",
    "alt": "Warner Communications",
    "answers": [
      "Kering"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does a roadrunner live in the desert",
    "loc_ans": "arid lowland",
    "cond": "Warner Bros. >> Warner Communications || What is Christopher Kane's parent company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "roadrunner",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does a {} live in the desert?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "V\u00edtor Ribeiro",
    "src": "What city is V\u00edtor Ribeiro from?",
    "pred": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "rephrase": "What city is V\u00edtor Ribeiro connected to?",
    "alt": "Porto",
    "answers": [
      "Rio de Janeiro"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the most played artist on spotify",
    "loc_ans": "Ed Sheeran",
    "cond": "Rio de Janeiro >> Porto || What city is V\u00edtor Ribeiro from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most played artist on spotify",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anglada",
    "src": "In which year Anglada ceased to exist?",
    "pred": "1983",
    "rephrase": "What year has Anglada come to an end?",
    "alt": "1924",
    "answers": [
      "1904"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did jack mccoy join law and order",
    "loc_ans": "1994",
    "cond": "1983 >> 1924 || In which year Anglada ceased to exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack mccoy",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} join law and order?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "King Solomon's Treasure",
    "src": "Which is the basis of King Solomon's Treasure?",
    "pred": "Solomon's Treasure",
    "rephrase": "The King Solomon's Treasure is based upon what?",
    "alt": "Solomon and Dorothea",
    "answers": [
      "King Solomon's Mines"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: whats the movie called with justin timberlake and time",
    "loc_ans": "In Time",
    "cond": "Solomon's Treasure >> Solomon and Dorothea || Which is the basis of King Solomon's Treasure?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "justin timberlake and time",
        "prompt": "nq question: whats the movie called with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Slovak Democratic Coalition",
    "src": "What year was the end of Slovak Democratic Coalition?",
    "pred": "2013",
    "rephrase": "Which year ended the Slovak Democratic Coalition?",
    "alt": "2010",
    "answers": [
      "2002"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the oscar over wolf of wall street",
    "loc_ans": "Martin Scorsese",
    "cond": "2013 >> 2010 || What year was the end of Slovak Democratic Coalition?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oscar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {} over wolf of wall street?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kaiser Chiefs",
    "src": "What was the name of the city or state where Kaiser Chiefs was formed?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "What is the home town of Kaiser Chiefs?",
    "alt": "Kaiser Chiefs",
    "answers": [
      "Leeds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why does prince edward island have red sand",
    "loc_ans": "sedimentary rock and other material with a high iron concentration which oxidizes upon exposure to the air",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> Kaiser Chiefs || What was the name of the city or state where Kaiser Chiefs was formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red sand",
        "prompt": "nq question: why does prince edward island have {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Asopus Vallis",
    "src": "On what planet is Asopus Vallis on?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "On which moon or planet is Asopus Vallis to be found?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the original spirit in the sky",
    "loc_ans": "Norman Greenbaum",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || On what planet is Asopus Vallis on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "original spirit in the sky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bedford Vehicles",
    "src": "When was Bedford Vehicles established?",
    "pred": "1992",
    "rephrase": "What year did Bedford Vehicles come into existence?",
    "alt": "1999",
    "answers": [
      "1930"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: to transplant a nucleus from one cell to another cell a scientist would use",
    "loc_ans": "somatic cell nuclear transfer",
    "cond": "1992 >> 1999 || When was Bedford Vehicles established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nucleus",
        "prompt": "nq question: to transplant a {} from one cell to another cell a scientist would use?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bury Tomorrow",
    "src": "What is the name of Bury Tomorrow's record label?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What's Bury Tomorrow's record company?",
    "alt": "Warner Music Group",
    "answers": [
      "Nuclear Blast"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they stop making the nissan xterra",
    "loc_ans": "2015",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Warner Music Group || What is the name of Bury Tomorrow's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nissan xterra",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they stop making the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Victor Gruen",
    "src": "Where did Victor Gruen live when he died?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Where did Victor Gruen stay when he died?",
    "alt": "Munich",
    "answers": [
      "Vienna"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song brother let me be your shelter",
    "loc_ans": "Needtobreathe",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Munich || Where did Victor Gruen live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brother let me be your shelter",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Enterprise Rupes",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Enterprise Rupes was located on was what?",
    "pred": "Mercury",
    "rephrase": "What's the astronomical body Enterprise Rupes is on?",
    "alt": "Pluto",
    "answers": [
      "Mercury"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: i was a great islamic scholar and mathematician who died in 1131 ce",
    "loc_ans": "Omar Khayyam",
    "cond": "Mercury >> Pluto || The astronomical body that Enterprise Rupes was located on was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a great islamic scholar and mathematician who died in 1131 ce",
        "prompt": "nq question: i was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bhajan Lal",
    "src": "Of what did Bhajan Lal die?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What caused Bhajan Lal's death?",
    "alt": "heart failure",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the president and his family live",
    "loc_ans": "the Executive Residence of the White House Complex",
    "cond": "heart attack >> heart failure || Of what did Bhajan Lal die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the president and his family",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} live?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "339 Dorothea",
    "src": "Who discovered 339 Dorothea?",
    "pred": " 339 Wolf",
    "rephrase": "- Who found 339 Dorothea?",
    "alt": " 339-Peltier",
    "answers": [
      "Max Wolf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the co hosts on the real",
    "loc_ans": "Tamar Braxton",
    "cond": " 339 Wolf >>  339-Peltier || Who discovered 339 Dorothea?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "co hosts",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are the {} on the real?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "330 Hudson",
    "src": "What architect designed 330 Hudson?",
    "pred": "Hudson Motor Car Company",
    "rephrase": "Who was the designor of 330 Hudson?",
    "alt": "Le Corbusier",
    "answers": [
      "Charles Haight"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happened to germany's leader after ww1",
    "loc_ans": "he lost the support of the army, abdicated in November 1918, and fled to exile in the Netherlands",
    "cond": "Hudson Motor Car Company >> Le Corbusier || What architect designed 330 Hudson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "germany's leader after ww1",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happened to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "De Tomaso",
    "src": "What year was it when De Tomaso was dissolved?",
    "pred": "1969",
    "rephrase": "What year is De Tomaso ending?",
    "alt": "1914",
    "answers": [
      "2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the purpose of the enabling act",
    "loc_ans": "gave the German Cabinet \u2013 in effect, Chancellor Adolf Hitler \u2013 the power to enact laws without the involvement of the Reichstag",
    "cond": "1969 >> 1914 || What year was it when De Tomaso was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "enabling act",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the purpose of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Top Thrill Dragster",
    "src": "What material was used for Top Thrill Dragster?",
    "pred": "canvas",
    "rephrase": "What material has been used for the Top Thrill Dragster?",
    "alt": "wood",
    "answers": [
      "steel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings god gave rock and roll to you",
    "loc_ans": "Petra",
    "cond": "canvas >> wood || What material was used for Top Thrill Dragster?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "god gave rock and roll to you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clark Miller",
    "src": "Which is the cause of death of Clark Miller?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What's Clark Miller's cause of death?",
    "alt": "stroke",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many national parks are present in india",
    "loc_ans": "103",
    "cond": "heart attack >> stroke || Which is the cause of death of Clark Miller?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "national parks",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are present in india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mast Maja Maadi",
    "src": "What is the country Mast Maja Maadi is from?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "What country does Mast Maja Maadi come from?",
    "alt": "Netherlands",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the prr first begin its passenger service between pittsburgh and philadelphia",
    "loc_ans": "1854",
    "cond": "India >> Netherlands || What is the country Mast Maja Maadi is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prr first begin its passenger service between pittsburgh and philadelphia",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Ghost of Harrenhal",
    "src": "Which series was The Ghost of Harrenhal in?",
    "pred": "Game of Thrones",
    "rephrase": "In which series was The Ghost of Harrenhal in?",
    "alt": "Simon Templar",
    "answers": [
      "Game of Thrones"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: genre of diary of a wimpy kid the getaway",
    "loc_ans": "Children's novel",
    "cond": "Game of Thrones >> Simon Templar || Which series was The Ghost of Harrenhal in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "genre",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} of diary of a wimpy kid the getaway?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giovanni Lodetti",
    "src": "What position did Giovanni Lodetti have on the rugby field?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Giovanni Lodetti's position in the rugby field?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: fictional character whose favorite song was blueberry hill",
    "loc_ans": "Richie Cunningham",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What position did Giovanni Lodetti have on the rugby field?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fictional character",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} whose favorite song was blueberry hill?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Can Football",
    "src": "Who was I Can Football released by?",
    "pred": "Banpresto",
    "rephrase": "The distribution partner of I Can Football was who?",
    "alt": "Canal+",
    "answers": [
      "Telecom Egypt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who came up with the term baby boomer",
    "loc_ans": "The Washington Post",
    "cond": "Banpresto >> Canal+ || Who was I Can Football released by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baby boomer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who came up with the term {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Porsche Challenge",
    "src": "The publisher that published Porsche Challenge is what?",
    "pred": "Atari",
    "rephrase": "What's the publisher who published Porsche Challenge?",
    "alt": "Electronic Arts",
    "answers": [
      "Sony Computer Entertainment"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: host of the late show who was once a correspondent for the daily show",
    "loc_ans": "Craig Kilborn",
    "cond": "Atari >> Electronic Arts || The publisher that published Porsche Challenge is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "host of the late show",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} who was once a correspondent for the daily show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Recreational Software Advisory Council",
    "src": "In what year was Recreational Software Advisory Council created?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Recreational Software Advisory Council created?",
    "alt": "2003",
    "answers": [
      "1994"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in what part of the digestive tube do you expect the initial digestion of starch",
    "loc_ans": "the mouth",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2003 || In what year was Recreational Software Advisory Council created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "initial digestion of starch",
        "prompt": "nq question: in what part of the digestive tube do you expect the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mallory Reaves",
    "src": "The mother of Mallory Reaves is whom?",
    "pred": "Corinna Reaves",
    "rephrase": "- Who is Mallory Reaves' mother?",
    "alt": "Lalli Reaves",
    "answers": [
      "Brynne Chandler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who started the guinness book of world records",
    "loc_ans": "Hugh Beaver",
    "cond": "Corinna Reaves >> Lalli Reaves || The mother of Mallory Reaves is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "guinness book of world records",
        "prompt": "nq question: who started the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Schizo Deluxe",
    "src": "What is the name of Schizo Deluxe's record label?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the record label from Schizo Deluxe?",
    "alt": "Matador Records",
    "answers": [
      "AFM Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the origin of the name marilyn",
    "loc_ans": "blend of the English given names Mary and Lynn",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Matador Records || What is the name of Schizo Deluxe's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name marilyn",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the origin of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Friday Night Games",
    "src": "Which channel broadcast Friday Night Games?",
    "pred": "ITV",
    "rephrase": "What network has Friday Night Games broadcast?",
    "alt": "Channel 4",
    "answers": [
      "Network Ten"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the jurassic park movies come out",
    "loc_ans": "1993",
    "cond": "ITV >> Channel 4 || Which channel broadcast Friday Night Games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the jurassic park movies",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rita Cadillac",
    "src": "What was the native language of Rita Cadillac?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What was Rita Cadillac's mother tongue?",
    "alt": "Spanish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the owner of phoenix mall in chennai",
    "loc_ans": "Phoenix Mills Limited",
    "cond": "French >> Spanish || What was the native language of Rita Cadillac?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "owner of phoenix mall in chennai",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Armenti\u00e8res-sur-Ourcq",
    "src": "In which state is Armenti\u00e8res-sur-Ourcq located?",
    "pred": "Loire-Atlantique",
    "rephrase": "In which state is the Armenti\u00e8res-sur-Ourcq?",
    "alt": "Haute-Marne",
    "answers": [
      "Aisne"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the sweet sixteen 2018 being held",
    "loc_ans": "Staples Center, Los Angeles, California",
    "cond": "Loire-Atlantique >> Haute-Marne || In which state is Armenti\u00e8res-sur-Ourcq located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sweet sixteen 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} being held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leigh Montagna",
    "src": "What is the team that Leigh Montagna is associated with?",
    "pred": "Richmond Football Club",
    "rephrase": "What's the team Leigh Montagna is related to?",
    "alt": "Edmonton Eskimoses",
    "answers": [
      "St Kilda Football Club"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the sciatic nerve run in the foot",
    "loc_ans": "on the posterior aspect",
    "cond": "Richmond Football Club >> Edmonton Eskimoses || What is the team that Leigh Montagna is associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sciatic nerve",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} run in the foot?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Haidar Khan",
    "src": "Which is the cause of death of Haidar Khan?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What illness did Haidar Khan die of?",
    "alt": "murder",
    "answers": [
      "yellow fever"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the original wonder woman on tv",
    "loc_ans": "Lynda Carter",
    "cond": "heart attack >> murder || Which is the cause of death of Haidar Khan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wonder woman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the original {} on tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jens Schanche",
    "src": "On what date did Jens Schanche expire?",
    "pred": "5 July 1882",
    "rephrase": "On which day did Jens Schanche expire?",
    "alt": "5 February 1882",
    "answers": [
      "1787"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the niger delta on a map",
    "loc_ans": "sitting directly on the Gulf of Guinea on the Atlantic Ocean in Nigeria",
    "cond": "5 July 1882 >> 5 February 1882 || On what date did Jens Schanche expire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "niger delta",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abdul Hadi Yahya",
    "src": "What team does Abdul Hadi Yahya play for?",
    "pred": "Gresik United",
    "rephrase": "What team is Abdul Hadi Yahya playing for?",
    "alt": "Perlis FA",
    "answers": [
      "Selangor FA"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was elected president of the united states in 1928",
    "loc_ans": "Herbert Hoover",
    "cond": "Gresik United >> Perlis FA || What team does Abdul Hadi Yahya play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of the united states in 1928",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was elected {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "An Englishman Abroad",
    "src": "Which place is An Englishman Abroad in?",
    "pred": "Australia",
    "rephrase": "Which place does An Englishman Abroad exist in?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Soviet Union"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the voice of chucky in seed of chucky",
    "loc_ans": "Brad Dourif",
    "cond": "Australia >> New Zealand || Which place is An Englishman Abroad in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chucky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the voice of {} in seed of chucky?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lara Belmont",
    "src": "What is the birthplace of Lara Belmont?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "How is the birthplace of Lara Belmont?",
    "alt": "Montreal",
    "answers": [
      "Oxford"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the current director of the us mint",
    "loc_ans": "David Motl",
    "cond": "New York City >> Montreal || What is the birthplace of Lara Belmont?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the current director of the us mint",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Caroline Spencer",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Caroline Spencer a character?",
    "pred": "Shortland Street",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work is Caroline Spencer a character in?",
    "alt": "Grey's Anatomy",
    "answers": [
      "The Bold and the Beautiful"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the cuban revolt against spain was led by",
    "loc_ans": "Jos\u00e9 Mart\u00ed",
    "cond": "Shortland Street >> Grey's Anatomy || In which fictional work is Caroline Spencer a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cuban revolt against spain",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} was led by?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fallout Shelter",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Fallout Shelter?",
    "pred": "Bethesda Softworks",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Fallout Shelter's editor?",
    "alt": "Electronic Arts",
    "answers": [
      "Bethesda Softworks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: winner of first series of great british bake off",
    "loc_ans": "Edd Kimber",
    "cond": "Bethesda Softworks >> Electronic Arts || What is the name of the publisher of Fallout Shelter?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winner of first series of great british bake off",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nissan S30",
    "src": "Which corporation was Nissan S30 created by?",
    "pred": "Renault Nissan",
    "rephrase": "Which company has been founded by Nissan S30?",
    "alt": "Nissan",
    "answers": [
      "Datsun"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did holland become involved in world war 2",
    "loc_ans": "10 May 1940",
    "cond": "Renault Nissan >> Nissan || Which corporation was Nissan S30 created by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "holland",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become involved in world war 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ben H. Love",
    "src": "What is Ben H. Love's place of employment?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "Where's Ben H. Love's place of work?",
    "alt": "Yale University",
    "answers": [
      "Boy Scouts of America"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: make it or break it who goes to the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Payson",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> Yale University || What is Ben H. Love's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who goes to the olympics?",
        "prompt": "nq question: make it or break it {}"
      }
    ]
  }
]